clappersama: hi
gmabreak: hi$
ajgorspl: yooo
codsane: I come in and hear “and I’m never gonna stream again” monkaS
Klingenwetzer: C :)
erichtp: LETS GOOOOO
luandevecchi: HeyGuys
logi6000: yo
rafbyraf: Heeeyyyy
Quev1337: PogChamp
clappersama: @georgehotz will you hack iphone if you you get 1* million usd
JaeGeeTee: Hello, World!
logi6000: I cought a stream finally
Nnotm: hey
foxubu: Yaaaaaaaay
frederik_diamond: hey
clappersama: you will get*
fatboyruuuun: Hi all
geracao_7a1: java 8 plz
masterw1tcher: Hi
Quev1337: webcam is laggin a bit
ProfessorMagikarp0: codewars > HackerRank Kappa
tharda18: @georgehotz I'm not living America Feels bad men
Nnotm: do you get a hundred gold if you go to a monastery
rafbyraf: Merch?!
fatboyruuuun: is this CMD????
tybutnowyoudie: 200 iq
davidsit_site: Come live in my basement. You can mediate whenever.
Klingenwetzer: Phyton Wowee
quillford: when am I getting my toyota impatience?
serhejenos: so glad to see you again
clappersama: Python > ALL
tybutnowyoudie: professional obviously
Klingenwetzer: Student TriHard
gmabreak: is the t-shirt sale worldwide ?
supplydemand88: Ahahah the best
codsane: Hmm
serhejenos: You shoud Stream more often
c19946: who is this influencer ???
erikjoelalexander: Looks empty in yyour appartment lol
MickInHburg: MickInHburg subscribed at Tier 1.
clappersama: @serhejenos 1
selcuktatar: hi broo
sebiyy: look who is online
Klingenwetzer: LUL doesn't look hard at all :)
sebiyy: the bigest nerd on the planet
Quev1337: LUL
clappersama: baqim türkçe yasak mı test edem
DevZhav: too many words
Quev1337: !keyboard
codevisionary: is this the stream where we figure out geohotz phone number?
bgeast: hello my next multi billionair ceo <3
clappersama: !hardware
logicunit1: I wanna buy EON. When will it be available for Lincoln MKZ?
alluxua: Geo, happy Saturday
tybutnowyoudie: cant see because of webcam
logi6000: what is hackerrank
Klingenwetzer: kiwianGG lamboEZ
luandevecchi: pogs 4Head
clappersama: guys can anybody explain to me whats the deal of this website ?
edoin21: pog
Cluwe: gg
dorkmo: boiiiis
ImAventus: what it do!
鼻史: what just happen..
tybutnowyoudie: move it to the right
gazny: PogChamp Actual Hacker Stream
sebiyy: what website is this
foxubu: noo other side
supplydemand88: Yeahhhhhh
birrdd: ratirlSmile
erikjoelalexander: No you needd to buy furrniture
jrrbls: right bottom
sebiyy: leetcode ?
mh1996mh: Website:
Klingenwetzer: BOOIS FeelsAmazingMan
mh1996mh: ?
Super_saiyan_3: hack the world
mh1996mh: !website
reyy911: Can you explain at least lol
rafbyraf: Topright
catacata92: hi mr !(!mentor)
foxubu: move yourself to the right side please
bebomethis: Bottom right
adietrichs: 3 difficulty levels, should do medium or hard
Klingenwetzer: LUL true
shimmer401: What are we doing today?
J3rwin: lmao
imaginenation: Geo you needa shave your beard
ProfessorMagikarp0: have u ever considered doing walkthroughs of vulnerable VMs like Ippsec does on YouTube for hackthebox?
tybutnowyoudie: LUL
jrrbls: Bottom Right
the_awoken1: hi buddy
sebiyy: what site is this ? leetcode ?
鼻史: HackerRank: am i a joke to u ???!
edoin21: move your cam
Klingenwetzer: fuckin' python forsenKek
foxubu: Buttom Right please
selcuktatar: selcuktatar subscribed at Tier 1.
clappersama: @sebiyy hackerrank
logi6000: this is basic
thv293: minecraft stream when
imaginenation: geo is orgasming to coding what
erichtp: LUL
alexlucas_: noob
RuhAdamTR: LUL
J3rwin: LULW
ImAventus: ImAventus subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 5 months, currently on a 1 month streak! lol
clappersama: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
thirteenn: SO BAD LULW
foxubu: Buttom Right please!
codsane: LUL
Kookook21: LUL
ForsakenReborn: F
supplydemand88: Nooooo booooooooom
supplydemand88: AhHahahaha
thirteenn: nymnSMALD MALDIN
imaginenation: you need to friggin post on your instagram dude you aint gonna get 1m2019
selcuktatar: :)
鼻史: alright enough for today
Kjjj11223344: LUL
c252: could you make text a little bigger
lolfulloftrolls: @georgehotz always
Quev1337: NotLikeThis
imaginenation: inside job
Silloe: monkaS
codevisionary: geohotz, first ever to hack the iPhone gets the lowest HackerRank score
Johnnymamen: o O
imaginenation: I am subscribed
supplydemand88: 🤣drunk
thirteenn: ANELE
dorkmo: a2 b2=c2
mtl_andy: 9/11 lol
imaginenation: ghive me big text
BugraEskiciiiiiiiiiiii: 9/11
J3rwin: Hopefully no advice buddies in chat today
edoin21: 9/11 lul
RuhAdamTR: 9/11 monkaS
machinelearningbot: monkaS 9 /11
imaginenation: MONKAS
c252: sorry
ProfessorMagikarp0: ProfessorMagikarp0 subscribed at Tier 1.
foxubu: Move yourself to the bottom right
Merwanedr: I finally got the notification I've been waiting for this moment for so long
phermy: phermy subscribed at Tier 1.
serhejenos: big text would be nice
sebiyy: i dont want the biggest company on the planed to be even bigger kappa
tybutnowyoudie: is it just a 3x3 matrix?
madebyollin: george please relocate to bottom right in obs
lyricballoon80: The array is 2d but you don't know the array dimensions @georgehotz
imaginenation: he doesnt even firgging have alerts on
thirteenn: he doesnt know nymnKek
erikjoelalexander: Ain'tt gooing to subscribe
davidsit_site: @lyricballoon80 !!
c252: simuleVI
logi6000: what is this warm up for
lolfulloftrolls: scarraPOGGERS scarraPOGGERS
thirteenn: OH NO NO NO nymnKek
sebiyy: does a thank you mean so much for you subs ?
dorkmo: c4r3l355
imaginenation: this stream is going downhill
imaginenation: cmon dude
Merwanedr: I expected Vimporn that's why I'm here
tybutnowyoudie: move cam to the right
jrrbls: Go To Bottom Right pls
alluxua: Do leetcode, bro
jxeus: this guy yeets
SoudExxV: can you change camera pos to bottom right
RuhAdamTR: Clap
Hazor90: PogChamp
Fezzry: PepeLaugh
imaginenation: This isn't the content we signed up for
phermy: Pog
c252: or project euler
Silloe: PogChamp
thirteenn: HE DID IT nymnK
chiragjn: yeetcode
serhejenos: the Stream is ok
clappersama: hacker_sucks_at_hacker_rank_watch_1080p.avi
davidsit_site: This is fine.
lolfulloftrolls: @georgehotz no, bottom right
aintmeee: best strean
jrrbls: what kind of bottom is that
aintmeee: m
asthmaa: @georgehotz learn v vlang.io
anthraxvirus322: waddup ?
imaginenation: when is the next mninecraft stream
ivylions: anger learning is primo content
Merwanedr: Where's the Vimporn George?
narc0rl: narc0rl subscribed at Tier 1.
selcuktatar: hi
c_oliver: LUL
imaginenation: minecraft
J3rwin: @georgehotz you are doing fine. lets go
imaginenation: i love you geo
lefse: Jebaited
Panda1Express: Jebaited
narc0rl: morgen4Hai
phermy: we're back BABY
foxubu: Ban the haters :D
codevisionary: LUL
c252: simuleCOW
duzy: haters gonna hate
Smithlmao: Can mods just ban the haters
imaginenation: cmon geo develop a thick skin
aintmeee: E BACK
thirteenn: monkaS
J3rwin: Pogchamp
Alternativeplan: Alternativeplan subscribed with Twitch Prime.
the_awoken1: fuck da haters george ...
Merwanedr: watching geohot using Windows is like watching your child becoming a crackhead
soeim: did you have a good cry?
Silloe: ban em xqcS
anthraxvirus322: F
Kjjj11223344: Ban the haters
supplydemand88: You are the best
guitu0405: gaulesBruxo
c_oliver: this is why i hate people named george
IaMvAzU: mod me @georgehotz
Kjjj11223344: We love you george
logi6000: we're back
serhejenos: serhejenos subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 8 months!
narc0rl: *hating*
imaginenation: GEO I WILL GIVE U MORE MONEY
c252: everyone likes george
anthraxvirus322: pay respect with F
imaginenation: F
myasovlavashe: D:
shahi1024: It's my first live stream watching geo hotz come back!!!!!
phermy: get owned nerd
abk467: abk467 subscribed at Tier 1.
foxubu: :D
napkats: tired
鼻史: i think i'm ur ＭＯＤ
davidsit_site: lol
Silloe: LUL
DemoFreak: LUL
Smithlmao: PogChamp
asthmaa: @georgehotz learn v vlang.io
shissle:
Gaboik: monkaS
IaMvAzU: lol
thirteenn: monkaS you are the greates alive George
imaginenation: can we have some Fs in the chat boy
lolfulloftrolls: INFINITY
codevisionary: LUL
shahi1024: Helloooooo
IaMvAzU: HSWP HSWP HSWP HSWP
aintmeee: did u get any sleep ?
anthraxvirus322: F
anthonyk95: yo man how are you/
asthmaa: :D
Wolf_King_IV: Can you move your cam .002mm to the left Kappa
jrrbls: luv from argentina <3
kaanfsd0: Cam is lagging
the_awoken1: george, u da bestest!
machinelearningbot: ban me ;)
thirteenn: monkaS this stream is great monkaS
foxubu: foxubu subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 9 months, currently on a 1 month streak!
codevisionary: inception
ivylions: ivylions subscribed with Twitch Prime.
IaMvAzU: VIP ME
napkats: i DONT want to be banned
imaginenation: LOL
supplydemand88: I like your kitchen style
Hazor90: LUL
asthmaa: ahjahaha
bebomethis: Add a sub link in info for the mobile guys
Merwanedr: Just open vim and your subscribers will grow exponentially
j0has: i want to be modded
napkats: LUL
ivylions: gr8 now i can talk shit
duzy: lets get hacking
napkats: i want to be MOD
the_awoken1: U DA MAN GEORGE
napkats: :D
smurfd0: keep up the good work :)
reyy911: LUL
narc0rl: i want to be paid :)
IaMvAzU: PogChamp1 PogChamp1 PogChamp1 PogChamp1 PogChamp1 PogChamp1 PogChamp1
imaginenation: hell yeah
davidsit_site: I want to get lunch sometime with you
Silloe: LUL
clappersama: while 1 < 10 : open(newTab)
mackenziebezos: mackenziebezos subscribed at Tier 1.
IaMvAzU: really , what a fuck face
saurabhshri: what's the warm up for
thirteenn: forsenDED
Zeldorino: OpieOP
anthraxvirus322: @georgehotz could you please check Autonomous intelligent driving's work ?
shahi1024: Wohoooo
ProfessorMagikarp0: Pride100 have u ever considered doing walkthroughs of vulnerable VMs like Ippsec does for hackthebox? its helpful for noobs like me to learn PepeHands
sk84uhlivin: Hope you're well George ^_^
logi6000: make a iPhone jailbreak in scratch
sh4kesbeer: stream is stuck
the_awoken1: why talk shite if u can't code a 0.00000000001 of how well george can code? SMH
gmabreak: from 0 to Trump how much hate is tolerated on this channel ?
machinelearningbot: neg..?
clappersama: nice bit animation
imaginenation: Why does he use OBS and not streamlabs OBS
IaMvAzU: KAPOW KAPOW KAPOW
duzy: What keyboard?
shahi1024: CoolCat
clappersama: @georgehotz hey check your god damn stream labs somebody send 100 bits to you
thirteenn: PogChamp 1:12
Silloe: VisLaud
shahi1024: VoteYea
selcuktatar: what keyboard
ghostfrommarz: PogChamp
imaginenation: hell yeah
catacata92: hella good
codevisionary: streamlabs is a distraction
RuhAdamTR: PogChamp
shahi1024: LesbianPride
SuperTremoco420: Waruppppppppppp
azgret: хай гайз
anthraxvirus322: PogChamp
potimotti: monkaS
IaMvAzU: MEEEE
鼻史: keyboard sucks
supplydemand88: Boooooom
erichtp: SHARE IT
IaMvAzU: TY
aintmeee: aintmeee subscribed with Twitch Prime.
mackenziebezos: LUL
IaMvAzU: come on george
ragemaster999: what are you playing? @georgehotz
alternatemule10: hm
supplydemand88: Keyboard with topre
Gaboik: jeez George enjoys the ban hammer 4HeAD
the_awoken1: george, did u hear about the ddos attack on wikipedia??
clappersama: @ProfessorMagikarp0 refund
MickInHburg: can someone share the link to the shirts, I missed it
fimonlark: @azgret здаровчик
IaMvAzU: stupid
tybutnowyoudie: these are all "easy"
thirteenn: he doesnt know nymnKek
ProfessorMagikarp0: @clappersama i tried :)
davidsit_site: all stupid
erichtp: Difficult: Easy you need to be hard
Wolf_King_IV: Cheer1 I like this side of George
mackenziebezos: PepeLaugh
Silloe: LUL
logi6000: when does pixie tech come back Kappa
serhejenos: try codewars there are harder problems
IaMvAzU: bogaHacker bogaHacker bogaHacker bogaHacker
J3rwin: isn't this the practice section
clappersama: @the_awoken1 wikipedia banned in turkey I use wikiwand
alex18920: wrong vhar
SuperTremoco420: i ust woke up so its all chinese
Zeldorino: #
clappersama: LUL
ProfessorMagikarp0: LUL
aintmeee: LOL
imaginenation: i guess you gotta flush the stdout
IaMvAzU: bogaTree bogaTree bogaTree
ProfessorMagikarp0: scammed
the_awoken1: @clappersama thx buddy
codevisionary: LMFAO]
thirteenn: he doesnt know nymnKek
clappersama: When is the geohot vs 12 year old kiddo
Psyckolul: nmpKEK
J3rwin: #7
kyriulan: LUL
IaMvAzU: bogaShocked bogaShocked bogaShocked
clappersama: @the_awoken1 you2 dude
mackenziebezos: 🥒
SlayerX1: go to i
logicunit1: you have one empty line in the end
SlayerX1: not i 1
payapayagaming: extra line..
IaMvAzU: bogaH bogaH bogaShh bogaShh bogaShh bogaSir bogaSir bogaSir bogaSir
paradox109: your output 7 lines :)
logi6000: what mouse does geo use
aintmeee: what is this keyboard YUCK
alex18920: range(0, ...) !!!!
imaginenation: what the fuck is this
Hazor90: LUL
Silloe: xqcT
IaMvAzU: bogaDeal bogaDeal bogaDeal thesto16Mald thesto16Mald thesto16Mald
bebomethis: bebomethis subscribed at Tier 1.
git0ut: makes sense LUL
paradox109: ahaha
davidsit_site: for i in range(n): result = ' '*(n-i-1) ('#')*(i 1) print(result)
Elinbae: you are, that is clearly not the same
LayzZ3: kekw
ForsakenReborn: Pepega
RuhAdamTR: Jebaited LULW
NicowxD: It has to be right aligned
mackenziebezos: Pepega
imaginenation: sys.stdout.flush() try that
sharmajee: their space starts with space , yours start with #
hexadecimalinteger: Yours look fatter
codevisionary: George make me a mod so I can ban all the haters
mackenziebezos: WeirdChamp
alex18920: range(0, ...) !!!!
napkats: pepeD
Joemerlino: Did u run the new code?
ghostfrommarz: PogChamp
imaginenation: gg lmao
Hazor90: PogChamp
duzy: PogChamp
Zeldorino: VoteYea
imaginenation: Geo how do i give u more money
chaprio1: monkaS
eduardoadf1: monkaS
thirteenn: n..no nymnS
syska: Hater here
Silloe: :D
Tal_X_Tal: monkaS
mackenziebezos: monkaS dindu nuthin
potimotti: monkaS
Waldoqq: Waldoqq subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak! Perfect way to start my Saturday. Love the stream bud
ragemaster999: first class programming PogChamp
TheX3X: hater alert
aintmeee: we hatin
clappersama: That website is totally broken The truth is shaped according to the answers of George Hotz
namewasused: me :)
phermy: monkaS
foxubu: Get some Tea :)
lefse: I hate haters
ragemaster999: first semester programming PogChamp
jkpfeffer: donate subs @imaginenation
SuperTremoco420: break hem all
chaprio1: when are u starting uni? :)
bebomethis: Pogchamp
codevisionary: @lefse if you hate haters, is that recurrent? That means you hate yourself
logi6000: iefse you are hating because you hate the haters
codevisionary: or is it not a loop?
qujoga: yo, whats up, what do we do here
asthmaa: Kreygasm
potimotti: Kreygasm
blinter121: !uptime
dorkmo: python3
CaSpErTbH: You are a boss.. Love the openpilot stuff! You reckon it will support UK roads at some point?
ghostfrommarz: EZ
madebyollin: :( calling sum in the loop
lefse: @codevisionary Kappa
duzy: damn sonm
TylerWaldon: which language is this?
imaginenation: ez first try
ragemaster999: @georgehotz first semester programming PogChamp
Zeldorino: 🐍 3
imaginenation: geo my man
discipleyo: whaaaaaat
dorkmo: letss gooo
Terbau: formatting DansGame
EpicAsAlwayss: C please
thirteenn: @georgehotz can you do mediums or hard problems? :)
ghostfrommarz: @TylerWaldon Python
SmokeSomethin: whats the agenda today homie
鼻史: these challenge sucks
estilen: Old style string formatting monkaS
mackenziebezos: popeyes or chick fil a
IaMvAzU: hey @georgehotz which language do u like the most to program in?
abhinabacharya303: @codevisionary wait what? NotLikeThis
imaginenation: woah edgy much?
dorkmo: make a gay wedding cake plz
blinter121: @georgehotz why do u code in python ?
yrpsa: lol
Zeldorino: 🎂 🕯️
SmokeSomethin: whast on the agenda today homie
codevisionary: @abhinabacharya303 what
ghostfrommarz: I feel bad for not coding this fast tatKevinS
davidsit_site: hahahahahaha
Sznurek066: Swift > Python > Java, fight me Kappa
mackenziebezos: D:
logicunit1: pick hard
ghostfrommarz: LUL
robbsalm: what is up george, i am at the second year of computer science but i feel burned out by too much coding, do you have any suggestions? (sorry for my english I am italian)
imaginenation: too slow
ruben1124141: Do you guys know any sites for javascript challenges ?
TylerWaldon: do you enjoy coding? @georgehotz
J3rwin: if you see right top it says the Difficulty leveel
soeim: apparently they are hard enough
logicunit1: pick hard category
ForsakenReborn: pick the hard ones
clappersama: That website is totally broken The truth is shaped according to the answers of George Hotz
Smithlmao: lol
Infinitelym: I think you're only doing the practice problems, not the real ones
Smithlmao: lmfao
mackenziebezos: 400 viewers PogChamp
chaprio1: this is gonna be painfull
chaprio1: Kappa
yrpsa: Wtf
selcuktatar: see u my friend @georgehotz
Zeldorino: monkaS
thirteenn: fuck time conversion nymnA
imaginenation: whens the next cooking stream?
logi6000: you should do root-me
tomaakola: Hi
chiragjn: Use time module ?
Zeldorino: real hax FeelsGoodMan
ghostfrommarz: First time seeing a dev not using Stack Overflow
chaprio1: rekt
TylerWaldon: Which website is this?
serhejenos: male text size bigger plz
soad188: @TylerWaldon hackrank
alex18920: Remove AM!!!
TylerWaldon: @soad188 is it free?
caslecasle: !uptime
M03x: do some root-me challenges basic ones
CaSpErTbH: 1st warning xD limmyParty
caslecasle: how log has he been online?
soad188: @TylerWaldon yes i think
ghostfrommarz: !uptime
thirteenn: make a cirucular array Kappa
imaginenation: bigger text please?
Crypod: elif
clappersama: @georgehotz increase the font please
sendnudeees: @georgehotz favourite os?
clappersama: punto*
imaginenation: bigger text please?
caslecasle: @georgehotz decrease the font please
logi6000: elif
clappersama: @georgehotz bigger punto please
davidsit_site: Ahh. The font is too big
the_awoken1: no
Zeldorino: hackos haHAA
mackenziebezos: plz make it bigger i am deaf
corbmonsta: Could be 12:05:00
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Waldoqq: font size was fine people are just blind
clappersama: @davidsit_site that was missing
MaFiaUSAHacker: i am deaf
awesmm: You can test your own input if you need
logi6000: yeah make it bigger for mackenziebezos
Dwayne449: Is this a hack course like code academy ?
Agent_Random: modulo 24?
uniqueuserr: OMG IM A BIG ASS FAN HERE
mackenziebezos: @logi6000 :)
gusfrehse: mod 24 !!!!
awesmm: @uniqueuserr big fan of ass aswell
thirteenn: WOW PogChamp
clappersama: @georgehotz please bigget text I am blind
dorkmo: letzzz goo
Klingenwetzer: BIG FAN BlessRNG
Smithlmao: hacks PogChamp
the_awoken1: MrDestructoid
SmokeSomethin: im a bigger fan though
h3llofriend: 5Head?
jrrbls: wheres the tea
thirteenn: mod 24 Pepega
Klingenwetzer: modulo
EpicAsAlwayss: C dude
davidsit_site: $
syska: what is your keyboard?
NicowxD: u could just sum mod 24
imaginenation: 5Head
Klingenwetzer: ye
uniqueuserr: PYTHON jet brains
Smithlmao: yea
ghostfrommarz: GG
el_pirulote: OMEGALUL
clappersama: @georgehotz please bigger text I am blind
thirteenn: nymnKek
caslecasle: Smaller font jesus christ i cant see anything. its too big
lukcsgotv: what are your thoughts about haskell? @georgehotz
noctrnalmachine: MrDestructoid
imaginenation: this one uses mod
clappersama: @georgehotz please bigger text some blinds watching that stream
logi6000: bigger braile I am deaf and blind
Zeldorino: LUL caesar cipher
chiragjn: st ing
halo_krs: bramosOMPA
shavo7: LUL
estilen: from string import ascii_lowercase
robbsalm: *gives up
timbo7io: Lol
ghostfrommarz: try C
ProfessorMagikarp0: codewars >hackerrank
chiragjn: str.translate
timbo7io: Break time
ForsakenReborn: go to the hard section
clappersama: !uptime
Guscles: you missed 1 letter in that alphabet
clappersama: nice
awesmm: no char in python da f?
Klingenwetzer: then use the professional difficulty and not the student one LUL
clappersama: @georgehotz you missed ö
J3rwin: dem variable names
timbo7io: xor
alfyfav: i dont remember if it was in hackerrank but I found once some very hard problems
estilen: str.translate will do exactly what ye need
Klingenwetzer: forsenS
heyhou95: @clappersama found the german
caslecasle: Isn't hackerrank like codeforces for people who are scared of codeforces?
sharmajee: try CTFs if this seems too easy
timbo7io: Sorry no onsite for you
gunnaren: your my hero george
uniqueuserr: currently learning html but this makes me switch back to python
Klingenwetzer: DatSheffy cmonBruh @heyhou95 whatchu mean?
thirteenn: just go to hard problems these are so trash LUL
Adolfich: Dammm u do it so long omglmfaoelol
uniqueuserr: the bandwagon i hate it
MrBankster: You going in for some interviews soon? Kappa
lemonzhestt: yes
onu4r: yes ofc
TheLast7Samurai: This could be helpful for my computer security project lol
heyhou95: @Klingenwetzer found the second germän
Klingenwetzer: DatSheffy
オレンジ420: Pepega
clappersama: @heyhou95 what about Ç KappaPride
hexadecimalinteger: Practicing for that Elon interview
MrMarkFilaroski: @TheLast7Samurai Yo! funny seeing you here.
robbsalm: edge cases everywhere
GoTo3: lul
Klingenwetzer: SOCIAL MEDIA forsenHead
awesmm: Do something harder...
imaginenation: ask elon
thirteenn: PogChamp ask us
GoTo3: who has freinds in 2019
prafaeltsantos: !uptime
TheLast7Samurai: Are you Turkish ? @clappersama
Muratandjose: what website is this?
Dwayne449: HARDER
SuperTremoco420: ohhh hahahah
clappersama: @TheLast7Samurai congrulations*
timbo7io: You can do it
TheLast7Samurai: Hey man lol @mrmarkfilaroski
Dwayne449: That what she said
clubmate42: love how this is basically CTF code. if it works, it works, doesn't have to be elegant.
timbo7io: Coffee
goedel_gang: linear time lookup Pog
onu4r: @thelast7samurai Are you Turkish?
slaterusa: gofundme to get him some furniture?
Klingenwetzer: lamboEZ
abstractingagent: Yo George, what's good
TheLast7Samurai: Eyvallah :) @clappersama
dorkmo: letzzzz gooo
caslecasle: jesus
NMODE: PogChamp
TheLast7Samurai: Yes @onu4r
clappersama: @TheLast7Samurai makam odası mı ora
caslecasle: do the hard ones then
thirteenn: HARD PROBLEMS PogChamp
onu4r: @thelast7samurai selam :)
ghostfrommarz: PogChamp
clappersama: SA
clappersama: as
Klingenwetzer: use C rephtoSmile
MrBankster: george how can i get into comma ai? I know node
serhejenos: you are on easy
slaterusa: dare you to do some PHP :D
ghostfrommarz: Try AI
syska: Try Leet Code
Guscles: what site is this ?
caslecasle: nono
takroli3: iyi şeyler izleyen arkadaşlsr da varmış
caslecasle: euler
J3rwin: oh god
caslecasle: fuck no
clappersama: @georgehotz use binary
robbsalm: difficulty : medium
GoTo3: tea 3Head
MrBankster: nasm
thirteenn: tea time with byron FeelsGoodMan
notelex: oha türk var
ghostfrommarz: Tea in the morning DansGame
aefnor: adderall
Klingenwetzer: pls use assembly rephtoSmile
TheLast7Samurai: Selam turkler :)
noctrnalmachine: lmao
hexadecimalinteger: Is this the guy that solved the 42?
timbo7io: Coffee time woooooooo
slaterusa: @aefnor is that what he's on? :D
SuperTremoco420: time to use assembly
ixeden: lmao
clappersama: when I try to get back like geohot I am crashing to the wall
robbsalm: assembly code is the best
takroli3: hi bro
clappersama: SELAM
el_pirulote: difficulty medium gonedoD
gunnaren: peeing on autopilot
uniqueuserr: sublime text??
the_awoken1: there it goes
ajgorspl: lul
vtcN_: @robbsalm why
Kaijizon: as krşdm
nullbit64: lul
twitch7443: wasap
timbo7io: Thats a nice chair
Muratandjose: doin coke
robbsalm: you can show off your skillz
noctrnalmachine: lol
the_awoken1: 100%
robbsalm: rotfl
Klingenwetzer: forsenS
ggtom: god damn relax
clappersama: * fap time *
dorkmo: what happened to gamer chair?
uniqueuserr: yee
ggtom: your breaking the bridge
CaSpErTbH: Didnt wash his hands limmyJm2
ghostfrommarz: monkaW
LDestroier1: monkaS
hexadecimalinteger: Going for that Adderall boost
omgwtfcute: remember to wash your hands
ForsakenReborn: monkaW
Guscles: what site is this ?
gusfrehse: monkaW
drivewaycam: KEKW
slaterusa: @Guscles twitch.tv!
ggtom: didnt wash hands DansGame
xfallenchamp: xfallenchamp subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 6 months, currently on a 6 month streak! yes very good
noctrnalmachine: thats the new style of gaming chair LUL LUL
imaginenation: Do You Use NOOTROPIC?
RS_Ggs: @Guscles hackerrank its in the title
erichtp: EW DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame
gunnaren: george stands while peeing confirmed @georgehotz
yrpsa: Hackerrank
onu4r: @guscles hackerrank
King_A3GON: we can here you peeing bro.. LUL
drivewaycam: mrsruvSip
MrMarkFilaroski: BOOM CRASH BANG
kaanfsd0: DO YOU BLOCKİNG YOUR CAM ?
codevisionary: https://clips.twitch.tv/TransparentTangentialSkirretPipeHype
Guscles: @onu4r thanks
Klingenwetzer: FeelsAmazingMan
ggtom: clappersama before flushing DansGame
omgwtfcute: SHARE WITH YOUR FRIENDS ON SOCIAL MEDIA
thirteenn: @georgehotz subs are only $ 2.5 this month, remind people :0
dorkmo: dark mode!!!
nullbit64: bruh
nullbit64: use darkmode
EastTangent: face cam kinda laggy
Klingenwetzer: Dark mode BlessRNG pls
ixeden: Darkmode
caslecasle: Dont do project euler man
slaterusa: does georgey-boy really need the money? :D
davens: dark mode
wood24: hi george hope youre doing good!
ixeden: !darkmode
CaSpErTbH: limmyBeast Dark Mode Engage
dorkmo: ¡darkmode!
abstractingagent: abstractingagent subscribed at Tier 1.
javadragoniv: Yes we like this content lol keep up do more autonomous driving related stuff would be cool to see more on how u tackle these kind of problems (kind of like slam ?)
thirteenn: @georgehotz subs are only $ 2.5 this month, remind people :)
BratvaTV: No more mac ?
twitch7443: bigbrain time
codevisionary: yeah I miss your twitchslam
Klingenwetzer: lowIQ lambo200IQ forsenIQ
ggtom: partial derangement LUL
oMythra: Saw your interview with Lex Fridman good stuff
caslecasle: switch to https://codeforces.com/
twitch7443: do it in kotlin lool
ForsakenReborn: 5Head time
caslecasle: this is weak
nullbit64: do otw
Klingenwetzer: LUL GOOGLE
konradmadisback25: omg my idol online fk yeah
robbsalm: oh i hate permutations
davidsit_site: Later Geo. I'm moving
SuperTremoco420: oh no
Zeldorino: #MATH
nullbit64: f math
SuperTremoco420: the solution is Math
SuperTremoco420: xD
sonyie: like 1,2,3,4
Klingenwetzer: djorjxBrain djorjxBrain djorjxBrain djorjxBrain
thirteenn: no, this is medium :)
CaSpErTbH: Answer is too hard. Delegate it to one of your team
caslecasle: medium lol
smurfd0: prime number order = natural position?
Zeldorino: 200 IQ needed to solve
ForsakenReborn: 5Head :|
Klingenwetzer: is it though? looks like a normal exercise in 2nd semester
menchedanem: not hard medium
nullbit64: idk lookup eulers toitient func
hexadecimalinteger: This is not hard, it's medium clearly
codevisionary: haters
nullbit64: or something
timbo7io: This ones fun
corbmonsta: Just do project Euler hackerrank is trash
foxubu: modulo inverse
robbsalm: is P a relation? of a function
oMythra: Q as in QQ
Zeldorino: Difficulty Medium :)
RS_Ggs: rate the challenge a 1 star @georgehotz
prafaeltsantos: it´s not hard it´s Medium
saltystones: lmao
michael_laurent: LuL
SuperTremoco420: ahahhaha
Klingenwetzer: LUL
abstractingagent: LOL
caslecasle: y
speeddrawing101: LUL
Shahin8520: LUL
MrMarkFilaroski: ET phone home
altic: LUL
CaSpErTbH: limmyBh
Dwayne449: hey george, any tips for learning ethical hacking at home ? @georgehotz
BrandonTouchedMe: welcome to project euler lol. you need to know some real math stuff to do these problems
cromize: multiplicative inverse modulo
kanogger: lul
Shahin8520: can you look at the example please
Zeldorino: letters of the alphabet Kappa
Muratandjose: prime numbers?
thes1nbad: Q is some shit from math
nomad119: I think it's probablity
SuperTremoco420: any math teacher here
codevisionary: math teachers make it worse
BrandonTouchedMe: a/b = p/q = p q^-1
Yemtex: es ist ein bruch
nomad119: binomial distribution
thirteenn: @georgehotz problems like these are pretty trash imo
SuperTremoco420: they probably saw and solved in 0.1 seconds math teachers xD
menchedanem: please pass this shit
sandfresse: @yemtex, haha :D
kanogger: ja
Yemtex: jip its math
timbo7io: Hacker rank is shit
oMythra: Math teachers are there to discourage you
Quev1337: please pass this shit
alex18920: P is numer of primes
Yemtex: @sandfresse hahaha
Shahin8520: maybe Q is the quotient?
codevisionary: math teachers are good at solving, but not very good at teaching
thirteenn: @georgehotz skip this one :)
nullbit64: BibleThump
SuperTremoco420: i agree codevisionary
narc0rl: Q^-1 = 1/Q : P.Q^-1 = P/Q which is the same format as a/b right?
robbsalm: i guess
alfyfav: Noo
alfyfav: a and b are coprime
alfyfav: In math
Klingenwetzer: LUL
aPosterior: NotLikeThis
JLO_: p = probability of success, q = probability of failure = 1 - p ?
alfyfav: P and Q means primes
ForsakenReborn: from 0 to 100 real quick
foxubu: Chinese remainder theorem
capsimirhd: classic hackerrank
averagesizepens: wow such a rare event, georgie online
cromize: pow() should be able to deal with it
vickson12: i'm taking a network design and management graduate level class
LegalFever: Omg I havent seen you in a long damn time
SuperTremoco420: The proficy as began math arrived
Klingenwetzer: forsenPrime
thirteenn: VisLaud
Shahin8520: PogChamp
goedel_gang: that’s a funny way to say Fermat
averagesizepens: where is my AI girlfriend? @georgehotz
Klingenwetzer: Jebaited
Muratandjose: ok
Klingenwetzer: gg :)
bosapiutsa: h r
Klingenwetzer: dark mode but the rest of the site stays white Wowee
jay_al97: what u doing at this time ?
bosapiutsa: u r d best
SlothEmperor: koilHm hmm yes continue
Cluwe: 25 up to 100
Klingenwetzer: LUL
timbo7io: :S
eaterenrgy: Hello George and chat.
f1gz: where to do small problems like this? to practice
Klingenwetzer: because libs is cheating BrokeBack
Klingenwetzer: *are
timbo7io: Put some malicious code into the repl
f1gz: is it codescreens?
Shahin8520: LUL hahaha
timbo7io: 😛
legendarydarkstar: im excited that george will hack ps5
J3rwin: rofl
robbsalm: lol
trustME_SC2: sacNOYOU sacNOYOU sacNOYOU
quickfloor: Cooking Stream ?
kanogger: lmao
legendarydarkstar: hey george when you tapping into ps5?
Agent_Random: it was python 2 :)
Zeldorino: SourPls
jay_al97: @f1gz hacker rank
c19946: CHANGE IT TO VIM MODE.
yrpsa: Am i retarded if idk whats going on :(
Klingenwetzer: LUL
dontbeameme: Can someone explain how this game translates?
tundratortoise: python 3 iterators rule bro
Zeldorino: just bUrself
Klingenwetzer: typedefs in python the irony :3
madebyollin: printing extra stuff to stdout
madebyollin: ?
x_algorithm: x_algorithm subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months! hello everyone!
legendarydarkstar: george when we getting ps5 haxs?
twiggy_io: Theres a library for for some top down recursive prime in python 3
timbo7io: For all p there exists q such that
madebyollin: you're printing n, k, p but the answer is right?
averagesizepens: @yrpsa dont worry dude we are here to pretend, just write integer. before any word
mutrx: u should be trading some btc rn
c19946: CHANGE IT TO VIM MODE
Quev1337: CHANGE IT TO VIM MODE
timbo7io: 2 is prime right?
goedel_gang: != 0???
menchedanem: not sqrt(n) prob n/2
Zeldorino: CoolStoryBob Happy little partial derangements
quickfloor: Feels like projecteuler
punisher_2003: what are you drinking? is that tea?
szabi_zsoldos: It is made by indians, many of them are wrong
bulbaz0r: !problem
tundratortoise: seems like a project euler clone
imaginenation: The number of total derangements = n!/e
yrpsa: Ya its project euler
timbo7io: Nice tea 🍵🍵🍵🍵🍵🍵
mutrx: why don't u build a trading program
timbo7io: 10!
goedel_gang: dude why are you checking if the remainder is 1
quickfloor: George Only drinks Vodka when he's coding
gusfrehse: 10! -2
timbo7io: Ahhh this is poker probabilities!
Cluwe: Binomial coefficient gives the answer doesn't it?
mutrx: why doesn't this guy do some algorithmic trading wtf would be way richer than some driving AI
vincexviii: PogChamp L33t H7cK3rz
Zeldorino: PrimeMe
maddyakhil: hello , long time no see
goedel_gang: listen pal you need to fix the modulo check for equality to 0
quickfloor: just can u hack that and find the answer number ?
ForsakenReborn: @mutrx ur a moron
imaginenation: The number of total derangements = n!/e
IMLadyBoy: only on sundays
mutrx: @ForsakenReborn y
timbo7io: Derangement lol
inov8r: Some people just have different incentives. Driving AI might be more “fun”.
timbo7io: Idk what that even is
vincexviii: @ForsakenReborn D:
ZORROBEATS: has george personally tried to get into swift or
dontbeameme: @quickfloor I agree just hack the program
qujoga: Do you run commai archive youtube channel?
ZORROBEATS: i personally found it interesting
0xreself: on wich site he is trying to solve it ?
alex_sez: @georgehotz play pwnable.tw ? :D
quickfloor: HOW WAS GEORGE MATH IN SCHOOL AND COLLEGE ?
abstractingagent: The unfortunate consequence of the language for generalization
SpiritHNTR: @0xreself hackerrank
quickfloor: Just think about that
alex_sez: hahahahahah
Klingenwetzer: LUL
1nc1s1on: This is what I want to be seeing...thanks george
Kraytill: georgehotz: would you rather read a definition formalised in Coq or similar?
Klingenwetzer: Kappa
alex_sez: mannn
ggtom: Kappa
timbo7io: Ihahaha
mutrx: do algorithmic trading
tundratortoise: as a non-CS-ish SWE I feel the same. I think they're just interested in a different sort of goal
Sznurek066: Kappa
vtmr: Kappa
timbo7io: Unnatural baby
quickfloor: Kappa
ZORROBEATS: Kappa
vincexviii: Kapp
quickfloor: @vincexviii you suck
imaginenation: natural position is the starting positions of the disks
imaginenation: the correct initial order 1....n
dontbeameme: Exploite for the answer then
quelsarprime: that's the foolish part
goedel_gang: 11 % 3 != 1 so we conclude 11 is not prime
vincexviii: @quickfloor D: S WORD
mutrx: do some algorithmic trading
konradmadisback25: careful he can get into your bank account be nice pls
tundratortoise: @goedel_gang you mean 2, not 3?
quickfloor: WORK SMART NOT HARD . this is what george doing
c19946: geo change it to vim mode
ZORROBEATS: kappa
geohot_pls_fck_me: hey wassup
Kaijizon: PogChamp
ZORROBEATS: Kappa
Klingenwetzer: LUL
alfyfav: What's the thing you're warming up for?
imaginenation: yo dude we need some quantum compute to break the internet
timbo7io: Hahaha
unknown_elemen: hi
Quev1337: geo change it to vim mode
Mig1939: hey george what you working on?
gereltod00: BCWarrior
timbo7io: Goode, escher bach
tundratortoise: I think he's just trolling you
alex_sez: @georgehotz the first level will troll you att pwnable.tw, i promise
alex_sez: XD
alex_sez: but i feel u if u wnana solve this
alex_sez: wanna*
ZORROBEATS: おれわマンコが大輔ですか
bulbaz0r: take the coefficient of binomial distribution
bulbaz0r: same thing as what you want
goedel_gang: dude change line 8 to == 0 :)
yrpsa: PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Shahin8520: not != its == 0
bulbaz0r: n choose k is n! / (k!* n-k!)
yrpsa: FrankerZ
punisher_2003: SoBayed
bulbaz0r: (n-k)! *
Zeldorino: BegWan
criiscarpenter: Giveaway your keyboard
imaginenation: so you have 1...n in correct order than you select k disks which you will dearrange Forumula nC(n-k) x (k!/e)
imaginenation: the forumula for derangements is simply n!/e
imaginenation: rounded to the closest integer
jens472: !today
imaginenation: natural log
imaginenation: e
GoTo3: e is constant e
konradmadisback25: this would take like 150 lines in java
abstractingagent: LOL
c19946: he blow server
Predator09: hello
alex_sez: what do u guys think about the curly braces enforcement in golang
alex_sez: i hate it
averagesizepens: i hate it too, sounds bad
tundratortoise: the thing I really hate is semicolons in Rust
BrandonTouchedMe: dont forget those k disks are prime numbers as well
jens472: what is hackerrank
maddyakhil: love your work at comma.ai <3
Shahin8520: can you send us the link to the problem, i want you read it up :D thanks
imaginenation: yeah
alex_sez: @georgehotz love ur old rop videos btw
Shahin8520: thanks
alex_sez: or pwn videos
imaginenation: I looked it up right now on Numberphile
corbmonsta: Count number of ways at least one can be in correct position
corbmonsta: Then subtract from total
DrRobotvinnik: back on twitch Poggers
imaginenation: the forumla is there on wikipedia as well
timbo7io: Dont we all
DrRobotvinnik: you just made my weekend @georgehotz cbrahFeels
dontbeameme: Your not cheating your not trying
tundratortoise: is itertools.permutations cheating
yrpsa: What level of math do i need to understand this
timbo7io: lets do this thing baby!
corbmonsta: cn! * n
imaginenation: Combinatoricvs @yrpsa
timbo7io: yeah it is
timbo7io: algorithim design manual is a sick book
Blobiciously: which problem number is this again?
imaginenation: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
imaginenation: thats the problem
timbo7io: thanks
Cluwe: thank you
anasninja: hello George :)
gigafact: hello everyone. Nice to catch the stream for once.
alfyfav: Geo u know you can change to python2 right?
GenBurnside: just me or is the screen black?
gigafact: just you refresh
GenBurnside: gotcha
thirteenn: memoization PogChamp
GenBurnside: fixed
flitcho: Hi
gigafact: George that Lex talk was legendary
thirteenn: might have to do it for fact too
timbo7io: how is that windows?
abstractingagent: Gotta say, these Project Euler problem's are really giving me a run for its money
robotboy987: SeemsGood
timbo7io: i like to think more than type
timbo7io: so there more fun
jrrbls: what's a good website to learn the math concepts needed to solve this problem? i only know basic coding
flitcho: What website is this?
thirteenn: @georgehotz I find algortihms on hackerrank way more fun than these math contests
imaginenation: How much math did you take Geo?
timbo7io: lol i got c's in math
Klingenwetzer: yeah its all about practice in math LUL
Blobiciously: it's math degrees
jrrbls: hackerrank @ flitcho
Usisuvach0: hi
keepingtrckofthisacct: you're back!
flitcho: Thanks
abstractingagent: I think those who end up solving these types of things that easily are just more familiar with the frameworks of thought required - not that there is any real boundary that creates a difference between us and them
Blobiciously: I just don't understand what Q is in the question?
averagesizepens: !uptime
Blobiciously: I see
jrrbls: p/q=a/b confirmed
Klingenwetzer: nymnHmm
imaginenation: oh man i want money like geo
Blobiciously: then A = NA
timbo7io: i want your chair!
thirteenn: @georgehotz I find algortihms on hackerrank way more fun than these math contests
timbo7io: what kind is it?
SKPTCL: what kind of chair is it
jrrbls: @imaginenation just solve math problems on HR
timbo7io: my back hurts
timbo7io: BibleThump BibleThump
jrrbls: how do you train yourself on those fwks?
MrBankster: yeah man
criiscarpenter: SSSsss
Sparks1Cx: no
thirteenn: @georgehotz but can you learn frameworks like these at an older age?
Blobiciously: then you realize that Asian kids in an authoritarian culture are gonna take over the world
timbo7io: lol
imaginenation: nah i am sick and tired of competitive programming, i switched to building applications instead
timbo7io: lolol
imaginenation: because i sucked at math
reyy911: Chair giveaway!!! Lol
timbo7io: hah
MatiGoG: LULW
dontbeameme: I agree math is bad
Klingenwetzer: then write your own EleGiggle
punisher_2003: @georgehotz what are you drinking? Is it tea? Coke?
imaginenation: Geo thinking intensifiesx
timbo7io: i wonder if they data mine all our code
Quev1337: tea
chepe1228: Moonshine
abstractingagent: True, but my experience has always been that the more familiar someone is with something, the less their mind has to wander about doubting the basics and the more free they are to abstract and reason with patterns
CaSpErTbH: 25,3
Klingenwetzer: Its called practice @abstractingagent
N3RdR4Ge92: PogChamp
timbo7io: is it, prune search space?
N3RdR4Ge92: bogaHacker
imaginenation: if there are P primes less than N then P-k primes must remain in the same position
imaginenation: How about that Geo?
timbo7io: define the correct total
timbo7io: oh yeah haha
imaginenation: Actually it doesn
dorkmo: you guys ever seen that movie mercury rising?
Klingenwetzer: no :3
UzeezU: I think you can learn a tremendous amount. One thing that is hard about math though if for any given topic there are hundreds of books that are hundreds of pages and all at various lelels. I wish there were more consdensed versions of the materials where it focusing on just learning the core of the subject and the most transferable infromation. Just read these 50 pages and you know the core ideas and frequent uses of this branch of math would be ideal.
jrrbls: @Klingenwetzer it's practice for sure but you can have a certain inclination for doing that practice in the first place
imaginenation: actually it doesnt matter if those numbers are prime or not you just need the cardinality or the quantity of fixed things
0om4ar: !uptime
imaginenation: p-k = fixed things
abstractingagent: @UzeezU That's why geometric algebra is so exciting, it subsumes all the other fields of math under one notation and one framework
IsaacRamsay: 1hour 5 min @0om4ar
740ii: whats cracking George
dontbeameme: @dorkmo Yes
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @georgehotz <3
timbo7io: haha
criiscarpenter: Awww man
UzeezU: @abstractingagent What is a paper of book I could read quickly to get a taste of the field?
timbo7io: yeah
menchedanem: five years later
thatfunkykid: How you doin
timbo7io: i have wasted many days throwing myself at problems like these
maverick_twitch_: @georgehotz Hello nice to see you coding
UzeezU: @abstractingagent paper or* book
joker2k999: jay knows his ish..
maverick_twitch_: isnt programming just math puzzles
Mua_987410: 2.99 for subscribe !
maverick_twitch_: :D
Alexandridas: Holy shiet, not a vod this time reapin3Nugget
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: shoutouts to commaai archive
gluecks: what are you coding?
dontbeameme: Maybe someone on Reddit already solved this one
abstractingagent: @UzeezU http://www.geometricalgebra.net/
maverick_twitch_: comma ai works in Mars ?
maverick_twitch_: probably you wont even need onr
abstractingagent: @UzeezU that's a good place to start - if you want the book - I can send you the .pdf link i found for it
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Derangement
gelavizh_ahmadi: hi, I enjoy watching your live programming, keep up. :)
abstractingagent: @UzeezU https://epdf.pub/geometric-algebra-for-computer-science-an-object-oriented-approach-to-geometry.html
abstractingagent: ^ the book
Jeppelelle: !keyboard
fkndean: lol
maverick_twitch_: what website i am on phone
maverick_twitch_: share the link humans
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: it is hackerrank dot com
Cluwe: wait is this related to the hypergeometric distribution?
Klingenwetzer: ayy lmao
criiscarpenter: Keyboard name?
UzeezU: @abstractingagent Thanks!
Jeppelelle: no switches
maverick_twitch_: @i4cc8a9morw8kfrh thx
bulbaz0r: I think ncr / e earlier was using the approximation of e from a poisson dist
bulbaz0r: sum ( to inf of 1 / k!)
maverick_twitch_: what problem he is solving ?
timbo7io: is it?
timbo7io: haha i love guessing!
timbo7io: well, iterating in general
joker2k999: guessing isn't that bad...
Shocker023: What's the problem?
maverick_twitch_: i guess the girl next door likes me and i am always wrong :D
konradmadisback25: @georgehotz quick do you have to know or be good at coding to bd a good hacker or work in cybersecurity, but also if you are good at coding will it help you be better at hacking/cybersec ??
maverick_twitch_: hacking is coding@konradmadisback25
timbo7io: ahhh
timbo7io: yues
konradmadisback25: explain pls
timbo7io: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
robbsalm: ahhh
maverick_twitch_: ahh
robbsalm: is this a warm up? lul
Jeppelelle: In that Angelina Jolie hacking movie she just hit TAB and got access to a mainframe
Jeppelelle: Thats how easy hacking is konrad
timbo7io: this version is more clear imo
timbo7io: https://projecteuler.net/problem=239
Klingenwetzer: tab was bound to autocomplete and enter at the same time lamboCool
garam_chai94: what's the problem statement?
timbo7io: A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order. What is the probability that we have a partial derangement such that exactly 22 prime number discs are found away from their natural positions? (Any number of non-prime disks may also be found in or out of their natural positions.) Give your answer rounded to 12 places behind the decimal point in the form 0.abcdefghijkl.
bulbaz0r: are you looking for total number of partial derangements possible?
geohot_pls_fck_me: still warm up ?
Jeppelelle: lul that nick
timbo7io: i still need to look up what a derangements is hehe
Cluwe: the hypergeometric distribution describes the probability of k successes (random draws for which the object drawn has a specified feature) in n draws, without replacement, from a finite population of size N that contains exactly K objects with that feature, wherein each draw is either a success or a failure.
timbo7io: we need to substract
timbo7io: values that contain primes?
timbo7io: hahaha
Klingenwetzer: SUBSCRIBE!
balkibee: Pog
abstractingagent: We need more twitch prime subscriptions! xD
robbsalm: primes are a scam? oh noh
maverick_twitch_: how is that going to help us in real world ?
NilsIRL: You should add the Programming tag to you stream to get a better visibility
Klingenwetzer: forsenPrime
timbo7io: xor
norlagg: hachuAYAYA
balkibee: !uptime
timbo7io: full_set xor prime_num_set ?
timbo7io: idk
balkibee: How long stream up, anyone?
NilsIRL: @balkibee 1h20
sabreje: yo what's up dude
balkibee: @nilsirl Thanks
maverick_twitch_: i didnt even understood the problem
ffntdt: whats the problem? im late
imaginenation: Geo can you explain the problem to us and your thought process on it
timbo7io: how many primes are there between 1-100?
imaginenation: 25 primes i reckon
maverick_twitch_: google it
imaginenation: Geo take a second to explain the problem to us and let us in.
syska: x / log(x)
imaginenation: lol okay
timbo7io: lol
timbo7io: your hired
ffntdt: lol
jocke12345: How far is this in the hackerrank page?
balkibee: Anyone restate problem?
gt853_tv: i just got here
gt853_tv: what's the problem
TheJonesEffect: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
abstractingagent: I just gotta say, one of the things that I love so much about this stream is your authenticity and George deals with difficulty.
joker2k999: yea i guess got here..
abstractingagent: his*
J3rwin: @jocke12345 it's the first euler problem he opened if i'm not worng
abstractingagent: Its Problem Euler 239
maverick_twitch_: Euler was mesmerized by these stuffs
abstractingagent: or a variation of it
timbo7io: http://mathworld.wolfram.com/Derangement.html
sabreje: guys who knows what kind of keyboard he had on old streams?
fa_k: the fuck is a disk
timbo7io: haha
timbo7io: frisbee
yrpsa: Magic keyboard :)
TheJonesEffect: Yeah, it's a variation of Euler Problem #239 posted on HackerRank: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
timbo7io: coffee break?
imaginenation: he uses a Das keyboard
imaginenation: i think
joker2k999: happy hacker keyboard i believe...
robbsalm: @georgehotz what do you think about energy drinks?
Klingenwetzer: DasKeyboard are good ^^
fa_k: guys what do i google to understand this "disk"
SmokeSomethin: anyones twitch chat keep disconnecting?
Jeppelelle: Yeah, but what switches? Thats the important part
maverick_twitch_: @fa_k why
sabreje: 10й
MatiGoG: PepeLaugh
MaximustheGent: euler disk
StrickenDown: hhkb only uses topre
sabreje: 10q
StrickenDown: and das keebs are shit (now)
fa_k: A set of disks numbered throughare placed in a line in random order.What is the probability that we have a partial derangement such that exactlyprime number discs are found away from their natural positions? (Any number of non-prime disks may also be found in or out of their natural positions.)
yrpsa: Rainbow switches
Jeppelelle: topre has more than one versions though
fa_k: what is disk??????????????/
maverick_twitch_: just google everything you dont understand
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @SmokeSomethin are you using firefox
Klingenwetzer: mx cherry switches probably @Jeppelelle you can figure out what by just hearing LUL
imaginenation: i just bought a mech keyboard today
imaginenation: G413
SmokeSomethin: @i4cc8a9morw8kfrh nope chrome, and twitch app has been doing the same thing for me as well
norlagg: just find the solution on stack overflow 4Head
StrickenDown: @imaginenation waste of money
maverick_twitch_: cool
syska: what keyboard is that guys ?
alexlucas_: HHKB
GoOnAli: logitech mech keyboard pepeLaugh
MatiGoG: hhk
imaginenation: Thanks @StrickenDown
joker2k999: matlab it bro. i gotta see what my functions are doing...
duzy: its Topre switches
maverick_twitch_: stack overflow
sabreje: hhkb type-s
imaginenation: hell yeah dude, It
imaginenation: its fire
joker2k999: i just told you, happy hacker keyboard.
imaginenation: Thast is not how people do math
imaginenation: they have a pen and a paper
perfectjustlikeme: What is the problem he is doing?
imaginenation: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
imaginenation: There ya gho
Shasan_: Who need math when you got google
maverick_twitch_: @perfectjustlikeme he is finding a number by guessing
fa_k: im afucking brainlet
imaginenation: This is making my brain hurted
itsawizzard: Is there any discord server
imaginenation: for what
maverick_twitch_: yes
averagesizepens: my brain is in a comma allready :d
km_404: in programming it's not the math exactly it's all about the logical thinking people
imaginenation: memes?
itsawizzard: I guess
maverick_twitch_: programming == maths
gigafact: it's amazing that at almost 500 viewers chat is so civilized
Sparks1Cx: lol
gt853_tv: what is a disk
imaginenation: Lol
GoOnAli: true @maverick_twitch_
robbsalm: LOL
imaginenation: that is because geo is banning people
imaginenation: who aren
imaginenation: t subbed
imaginenation: and are mongoloids
maverick_twitch_: lol
averagesizepens: 20 my dude
코케인: hacking math LUL
joker2k999: lol
imaginenation: this is some next level shit boys
maverick_twitch_: yeah
abstractingagent: @imaginenation ikr
Sparks1Cx: i dont think it works like that
duzy: 10 10 :)
jocke12345: Jesus christ this is medium? What in gods name are the expert ones like and how long do those take to "crack"?
Marshall3: ^^
imaginenation: you literally need to smoke crack i think
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @km_404 yea i agree with you
abstractingagent: Shit is crazzyyyy
maverick_twitch_: how to use a computer please help
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: i dont Kappa
timbo7io: lol
Klingenwetzer: don't do drugs rephtoSmile
timbo7io: tenderloin?
robbsalm: i drink energy drinks lol
PanicPoint: meth is where it's at
imaginenation: Geo are you having fun?
abstractingagent: We need us a dozen joints to get through this one
GoOnAli: yall noobs dont even somke crack
imaginenation: if you aint smokin crack what are you even doing with your life
MatiGoG: do you have probability in high school in us?
Wansie: what is hacker ranks
Wansie: ?
imaginenation: probability to smoke crackl?
yrpsa: Bruh a 8ball is all i need to get through expert questions
imaginenation: hell ya a 420%
maverick_twitch_: GOOGLE WHAT YOU DONT KNOW
imaginenation: LOL
Jeppelelle: Wansie https://www.hackerrank.com
imaginenation: hackerrank is so mainstream
trueDEJV: 4*2*0 is correct
averagesizepens: crack helped me get my life together
Wansie: yuck
maverick_twitch_: OR YOU CAN USE DUCKDUCKGO
fa_k: JUST SOLVE THE PROBLEM 4Head
NilsIRL: @georgehotz you should add the Programming tag to your stream for better visibility
Wansie: chat you're all boring LUL
maverick_twitch_: 0 memes
imaginenation: well geo is already suboptimal when it comes to SEO, i think he doesn
imaginenation: t care
HanDerreLinni: Heyo George, CommaAI for Hyundai NEXO?
maverick_twitch_: no
imaginenation: nope
dineshro: hi George
Sparks1Cx: D:
gigafact: @NilsIRL Category: Basic Programming
MatiGoG: or change category to science and technology
GoOnAli: m0xy5Head
fa_k: D:
imaginenation: LOL
Klingenwetzer: cool LUL
Sparks1Cx: lol
Klingenwetzer: riPepperonis
menchedanem: ten thousand years later
ffntdt: D:
robbsalm: well, better than nothing
fa_k: LULW
Klingenwetzer: lamboDeaD
gusfrehse: OMEGALUL
J3rwin: he lost it
NilsIRL: @gigafact yeah but no one uses that Category
yrpsa: Wtf
imaginenation: He is going to smoke
joker2k999: damn.. lol
IMLadyBoy: Still have m hardcoded I think
asaalgk: whats the task
maverick_twitch_: PixelBob
imaginenation: wait till he comes back
josergdev: F
robbsalm: lol
PhearTheCeal: what is P and Q in the problem description?
duzy: CiGrip boys
Klingenwetzer: 37/38 LUL
imaginenation: OO
GoOnAli: STREAMER GONE TriHard
gigafact: 1 passed Good Job
averagesizepens: LUL
imaginenation: toilet noises
fa_k: TriHard
suteki1: TriHard
Sparks1Cx: TriHard no mods
Wansie: George will never get hired LUL Kappa
Jeppelelle: Thats a quick shit
play_papst: ho clean your hand
Smithlmao: Didn't wash hands
imaginenation: he took a O(1) Shit
captn_marvl: what is site name?
Klingenwetzer: at least you got one right OpieOP
suteki1: no moderators in current chat room TriHard
imaginenation: Geo wash your hands
robbsalm: costant time pee?
Shasan_: Great job
IMLadyBoy: @georgehotz is m still hardcoded?
aoezalp: Is george getting ready to build self driving cars?
joker2k999: not sure about all that.
GoOnAli: Kappa
duzy: Kappa
fa_k: Kappa
suteki1: Kappa
maverick_twitch_: NEVER GIVE UP
spanilith: BASIC basic?
PhearTheCeal: what is P and Q in the problem description?
imaginenation: Keepo
nanodanger7: when did the stream start?
duzy: !uptime
dontbeameme: So if you just copy him will you move up in hacker rank ?
spanilith: gorilla.bas
joker2k999: about 2 hrs.. or so ago.
imaginenation: Kappa
maverick_twitch_: @dontbeameme lol
Klingenwetzer: LUL
chepe1228: MaxLOL
timbo7io: nice
Klingenwetzer: It just works rephtoSmile
timbo7io: man
HanDerreLinni: Is this basic programming?????
Sparks1Cx: PogCh
fa_k: PogChamp
imaginenation: exactly we can just copy him and have an awesomer hackerrank profile to interview at comma
jocke12345: How long have you been coding/hacking stuff?
fa_k: some right PogChamp
Sparks1Cx: PogChamp
timbo7io: your persistence is refreshing
gigafact: how many times you can run tests?
bosapiutsa: it's good enough
timbo7io: can we fuzz test this bitch?
imaginenation: I would have given up and started Minecraft by now
imaginenation: lol
timbo7io: lol
niimdaa: niimdaa subscribed with Twitch Prime.
timbo7io: money maker
imaginenation: Pog
timbo7io: pay day
abhb09: Which website is that?
timbo7io: hey ohhh
Sparks1Cx: maybe the computer is wrong
Wansie: go to easier problems, this is obviously to hard for you Keepo
Yemtex: do you have a 4k display ?
Yemtex: looks so small
spanilith: i took basic in community college and got yelled at for using a GOTO
imaginenation: he has 6k display
timbo7io: yeah he has a dishwasher too
imaginenation: yikes
fa_k: @spanilith i would yell at you as well
spanilith: it worked tho
KrakkenTM: what it do babyyyy
foxubu: what is he eating? Cellogs? :D
Jeppelelle: ice
balkibee: LUL
foxubu: whaaat
abhinavneelam: what is this problem about?
imaginenation: lol i really like the way he is thinking about math, very non rigorous and sloppy
jocke12345: seems like he is drinking pickle juice
Yemtex: @imaginenation ufff
foxubu: how can he chew ice? 😨
imaginenation: yo dude i need to chew ice if i wanna get a job at comma
PhearTheCeal: robot teeth
duzy: hes got platinum teeth
Klingenwetzer: same LUL
timbo7io: lol
Klingenwetzer: Its the best
timbo7io: veneers
joker2k999: thats how u git gud bro
jmc516: Ayy I finally caught you live and not on an archive video
Klingenwetzer: yea just chew ice Keepo
imaginenation: I am sure there is a more elegant way of doing this
perfectjustlikeme: Hurts my teeth
Klingenwetzer: then you're doing it wrong :3
Yemtex: !uptime
GoOnAli: m0xy5Head simple math really
gigafact: @imaginenation there is always better ways to do it...
GoOnAli: m0xy5Head quite straightforward
MatiGoG: 5Head primary
Dodo131296: Can anyone please bring me up to speed? what's he doing?
fa_k: 5Head ah yes quite the elementary
ForsakenReborn: 5Head ah yes
Jeppelelle: Dodo: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
imaginenation: hes solving a problem on hackerrank
Yemtex: @georgehotz do you use a laptop or a desktop pc
ezii_tm_registerred: did you already do all project euler challenges?
gigafact: it's a razer laptop
PhearTheCeal: @Yemtex he is using a jail-broken iPhone
th3_maj0r: yoo guys
RobMonstaFlex: tea?
robbsalm: oh gosh
Yemtex: @PhearTheCeal wonderful
th3_maj0r: yoo George
Yemtex: @PhearTheCeal what a performance :) Can it run minecraft ?
Shasan_: I can’t answer this an I went to college
fa_k: jannies PogChamp
gt853_tv: can you go through line by line and explain
averagesizepens: you are chewing crystals my dude
robbsalm: that isnt a warm up
Yemtex: @Shasan_ then college was worth it LUL
PhearTheCeal: the math actually turns out to be quite simple as explained in this video https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9iUvuaChDEg
duzy: monkaS
robbsalm: yes
gigafact: rip
jshieldss: so
jmc516: U changed the 2
Klingenwetzer: u broke it LuL
jmc516: It was 1 before
Shasan_: @yemtex LUL college wasn’t work it
abstractingagent: rip
jshieldss: @georgehotz i can not figure out how to learn how to code
imaginenation: btw literally try the formula for derangements, its fact(N) / e rounded to closest integer.
jshieldss: do you have any suggestions
imaginenation: so it covers all the cases i feel like
Klingenwetzer: all failed now 👀
trashtofu: SSSsss Any Minecrafters in the chat?
imaginenation: here dude
averagesizepens: nop
Klingenwetzer: >memoisation
Yemtex: @Chat what problem is he solving ?
Shasan_: I failed data structures
MatiGoG: @jshieldss just code to-do app 4Head
gigafact: George do not forget after stream pastebin the code
Jeppelelle: Yemtex: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
TheCoolKidsTable: you added those brackets
riaddo: doctorWARCRY
ecksdeelul: DansGame
imaginenation: Geo how about give the formula for derangements a shot might be the silver bullet
fa_k: CRA 💿 IDDO
Sparks1Cx: Ctrl Z quick monkaS
yrpsa: Ure dereferencing a null pointer!
Klingenwetzer: brute force BlessRNG
imaginenation: I am a youtube Normie can someone link me to a guide for become a twitch pro?
joker2k999: i thought thats what he was doing..
GoOnAli: 4Head just dont be a normie @imaginenation
gigafact: what kind of programming language is this?
timbo7io: break time
robbsalm: python 3
dineshro: python
timbo7io: my adhd got me going... hey ohhhh
joker2k999: ipython i believe.
ecksdeelul: Kappa
Klingenwetzer: python 3
spanilith: javacrip, coffee gangster
MatiGoG: @imaginenation if you watch anime you can call yourself a week LUL
imaginenation: did he crash?
MatiGoG: weeb
JanTSV: hiiii
averagesizepens: think harder
sub_g_hammond: geo does it worth it sellling to the man NotLikeThis
gigafact: I would love to see Elon doing this kind of streams lol
riaddo: WORK HARDER COMRADE doctorLOGO1 doctorLOGO2
dennjs: hi hi
KingKewpa: wen elon co stream?
gigafact: we at least have George doing it
oyAli: hiya Georgie
maverick_twitch_: Elon is tweeting
timbo7io: hahaha
fa_k: 5Head AH YES
Klingenwetzer: LUL rookie mistake
imaginenation: LOL
maverick_twitch_: he is super busy guy
SlayerX1: LUL
abstractingagent: LOL
ecksdeelul: LUL
timbo7io: stupid math ppl
yrpsa: Elon codes with his brain waves
timbo7io: haha
speeddrawing101: @riaddo stfu
bhad: elon doesnt code, he has people do it for him
timbo7io: oh shit
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink
timbo7io: python...
dennjs: elon lmao, yall ever heard of geohotz?
timbo7io: run time boo hoo
fa_k: OPTIMIZATION PROBLEM OH NONONONONO
timbo7io: im a slow interperted language
Jeppelelle: ddosed the compiler with all the submits
RobMonstaFlex: LUL
thirteenn: george is maldin nymnSMALD
SlayerX1: math people LUL
GoOnAli: you asked m0xy5Head
averagesizepens: math people LUL
timbo7io: whoa
Alucardofbelmont: you also got that in manual try. with 100 i believe?
riaddo: doctorJAWLINE Math People are stupid
maverick_twitch_: meth people
timbo7io: sammm son
timbo7io: damm*
NilsIRL: Math has a lot to learn from computer science
Klingenwetzer: LUL lamboGG
joker2k999: math people... How DaRe You sir
fa_k: PogChamp
Vorkoz: partial derangement sounds like a fun thing to do on a weekend
trashtofu: rajjHAA
imaginenation: damn the wrongs
robbsalm: definitly less wrong
ecksdeelul: PogChamp
th3_maj0r: "less wrong" sound so ok
giorgostheo97: Heyo
timbo7io: can i see the start of your script?
itsmuriuki: meth people
x_algorithm: to be able to do math you have to be a mathgician
thirteenn: not timeouts, different icons if its a timeout iirc
sub_g_hammond: geo what do you think abou selling to the man Mau5
imaginenation: could the runtime error be due to the modulo thing
timbo7io: great artists steal
timbo7io: cheap away
oyAli: true^
timbo7io: cheat*
maverick_twitch_: avg artist ?
Klingenwetzer: pow shouldn't be the problem
oyAli: i think a better word than steal is innovate
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink
sub_g_hammond: geo what do you think abou selling to the man Mau5
timbo7io: simple
oyAli: hehe
Klingenwetzer: LUL
timbo7io: cha
maverick_twitch_: tell that to copyright guys
Klingenwetzer: NotLikeThis
space_monkeyk1: BlessRNG
oyAli: lmao right ^
fa_k: 8 is right tho
fa_k: were 8 right?
bhad: no
shwakersam: if i watch thsi dose it make me smart ?
maverick_twitch_: no
space_monkeyk1: yes
maverick_twitch_: na
Klingenwetzer: wonder what 8 is LUL probably something trivial
giorgostheo97: Wanna start from scratch ?
gigafact: if you subscribe you will get smarter Kappa
Klingenwetzer: or a corner case
sub_g_hammond: geo what do you think abou selling to the man Mau5
imaginenation: can you tell us how did you get the derangements forumla
imaginenation: it looks wrong to me
maverick_twitch_: hmm
McNabL: What’s the program about ?
maverick_twitch_: he isnt google
joker2k999: full rand permutation i think..
imaginenation: Geo tell us where did you get the derangements formula
Zanfr1980: what answer is it expect? just hardcode it Kappa
sub_g_hammond: guys what are the best machine learning resources to learn from
imaginenation: google you mogoloid
Klingenwetzer: the tests are hidden @Zanfr1980
imaginenation: the derangement formula is wrong because !n is not n! on wolfram they mean two different things
JanTSV: @sub_g_hammond the internet
imaginenation: that is wrong geo
Zanfr1980: are you off by 1 perhaps?
thirteenn: wrong nymnKek
imaginenation: the !n is differnt from n! dude
timbo7io: http://mathworld.wolfram.com/Derangement.html
imaginenation: found your error
imaginenation: !n != n!
robbsalm: yep
timbo7io: lol
Tal_X_Tal: thirteenn 😡
Klingenwetzer: LULW
imaginenation: HAHAAHAH
thirteenn: LUL
Klingenwetzer: forsenHead
imaginenation: told you
gigafact: haha
robbsalm: lol
imaginenation: n! / e
Zanfr1980: LUL
jmc516: rip
imaginenation: GOTEEE
giorgostheo97: Dummy
prvk3: LUL
ruselec: Did you solve self-driving bus problem?https://www.hackerrank.com/challenges/self-driving-bus/problem
fa_k: lulw
Yemtex: @imaginenation nice one
imaginenation: can i get a job at comma now
Klingenwetzer: didn't even knew that LUL
imaginenation: lmao0
balkibee: rduLULUL
joker2k999: can't say i've ever used a sub-factorial. lol
thirteenn: @imaginenation PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: thx I guess :3
JanTSV: SeemsGood SeemsGood
Raiwo: PepeLaugh
sub_g_hammond: i got free burpsuite licenses contact me
joker2k999: lol
averagesizepens: trump WROOOng
imaginenation: AHAHAHAH
robbsalm: ahahahah
thirteenn: LUL
RobMonstaFlex: rip
Rydberggg: xD
timbo7io: is this it?
Klingenwetzer: LUL exclemation mark ❗
timbo7io: http://mathworld.wolfram.com/Subfactorial.html
fa_k: 4Head
imaginenation: can someone clip this
Jeppelelle: do it yourself freak
dorkmo: Subway100 bonus10
Rydberggg: you correct a genius, so you are a genius @imaginenation
gigafact: it's going to be on commaaiarchive
sub_g_hammond: khabib vs porier ??
Yemtex: @imaginenation for your future job ?
dorkmo: 5 dollar footlong
ProfessorMagikarp0: he is coding live he made an error what is the big deal?
SnakeOneMLG: !uptime
averagesizepens: wash hands please
robbsalm: can he work at facebook now?
timbo7io: lol
joker2k999: !nobot. 2:35
timbo7io: ocd ppl
Klingenwetzer: LUL Chat
giorgostheo97: Lol did ya wash ?
imaginenation: https://clips.twitch.tv/TubularExquisiteApeYouDontSay
averagesizepens: LUL
sub_g_hammond: khabib vs porier ANELE
timbo7io: https://clips.twitch.tv/ExquisiteOriginalTapirThisIsSparta
sophisticatedgaming291a11: mikkiPog
Dorgesh: what you doing today chief
Yemtex: @Dorgesh solving problems on a website in python
fa_k: https://clips.twitch.tv/FurryCuteSwallowTF2John
marfinatorhx: WHERE IS MINECRAFT
imshafay: Yooooooooooooo Gerogeeee Big fan here
joker2k999: subfactorial bro.... sound like a smoking stream...
thirteenn: https://clips.twitch.tv/PhilanthropicBombasticGarageBrainSlug
Klingenwetzer: NaM
kitelong: can u tell me when did u start learning to coding and techs?
fa_k: ZULUL
imaginenation: geo you need to trust your twitchies a lil more
imaginenation: copy pasta
Klingenwetzer: Keepo sure @imaginenation
imaginenation: love you too bro
imshafay: LEGEND
marfinatorhx: are you aware that you are genius @georgehotz?
joker2k999: lol,
sub_g_hammond: khabib vs porier guys UFC 2 hours left !
timbo7io: haha yea
robbsalm: damn
timbo7io: what is it in english
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: NaM
timbo7io: nested primes?
akbang47: @sub_g_hammond thanks for reminding me :P
dineshro: Will this video be uploaded to youtube?
gigafact: yes
Alucardofbelmont: use cache decorator of python please for recursion
imaginenation: Geo should also become a part time react andy
imshafay: I think the video gets autouploaded on youtube in like 12 hours or 2 hours
averagesizepens: bc they are subbed to factorials
thirteenn: @sub_g_hammond is khabib in 2 hours or does the whole event start in 2 hours
imaginenation: the text is too small for us to see geo
dineshro: ok that is good. I like to see George while doing programming.
sub_g_hammond: @akbang47 i'm here for you bro
akbang47: @sub_g_hammond <3
fa_k: JUST DIVIDE BY E 4Head
joker2k999: big ones are bros
Klingenwetzer: LUL
imaginenation: no i think subfacts should be smaller
Zanfr1980: just divide by 0 Kappa
imaginenation: strictly
sub_g_hammond: the hole event i'm in UAE now google your time zone
エワルパー: what site is this? can't see even on source
maxminos: this is painful
imaginenation: CLOSE ENOUGH
twiggy_io: @エワルパー hackerank
Hankete34: hackerrank
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink trial and error the best kind of coding LUL
エワルパー: @twiggy_io thx
Klingenwetzer: FeelsGoodMan
averagesizepens: LUL
imshafay: -1 is the mistake
akbang47: Pepega
imaginenation: LOL
fa_k: Kappa 1 2 3
ascential138: LUL
maxminos: maybe
averagesizepens: nice
KingKewpa: is this how you do math?
imaginenation: geo gives me hope tbh
gigafact: keep trying and you will win
SnakeOneMLG: nah but like he isnt thinking he is just doing random changes to the code
Seanyang0813: just htrow things at it 4Head
imaginenation: if he can do math weird like this, i should do it too
sub_g_hammond: Geo do you even UFC bro cmonBruh
shwakersam: subway is good forget about subfact
maxminos: wait he hasnt solved it yet
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz The man, the myth, the legend back at it again
imaginenation: Geo who do you pick Khabib or Porier?
Klingenwetzer: rephtoSmile
akbang47: LUL
imaginenation: LOL
averagesizepens: dana gonna win
jmc516: lul
jedieconomy: LUL
Abbadon1334: i think the answer is 42.
yrpsa: Khabib!
Klingenwetzer: rephtoSHOCK
sub_g_hammond: Khabib for daaays
st47ik: 42 has been cracked!
Zanfr1980: could you... bruteforce it by shoving random outputs?
playnich8: Boys. The nate and jorge fight coming up now tho
Rydberggg: khabib gonna win as always
Klingenwetzer: no @Zanfr1980
Yemtex: @KingKewpa I guess, he is doing it like that the last 45 minutes
imaginenation: lets focus on the problem boys UFC can come later
x_algorithm: @imaginenation wrong postcast, that something you should ask joe rogan :)
montecarlo: link to problem?
エワルパー: khabib is today?
averagesizepens: cannot focus sir, im a dog
Yemtex: !problem
imaginenation: subfact is a different beast
Yemtex: german here ?
Klingenwetzer: I see forsen1
Dodo131296: Could you please explain a bit of what you are trying to do?
twiggy_io: PEMDOS
shwakersam: i say subway is the best
sub_g_hammond: Andrew ng vs andrew yang
montecarlo: euler239 from url
エワルパー: holy shit what resolution is this? he can see everything?
montecarlo: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/submissions
marfinatorhx: Just play MINECRAFT @georgehotz
capsimirhd: lol how is this medium
maxminos: solve it in skript
sub_g_hammond: you need to post more on Your IG bro MingLee
st47ik: dark theme pls my eyes WutFace
Dodo131296: Could you please recap what you did until now?
ChimiFckingChanga: which hogwarts house is he from?
gigafact: what happens if you pass this exam?
Klingenwetzer: this fuckin' chat forsenHead
imaginenation: your P is P(n)-K in the derangements formula ?
JanTSV: @chimifckingchanga hufflepuff
maxminos: would help rn but ceebs
sub_g_hammond: Geo your IG game sucks post more
imaginenation: yeah Geo
st47ik: please if possible change the theme to dark my eyes hurt
averagesizepens: correct
imaginenation: No dude you're on the right path
Klingenwetzer: LUL brute force
imshafay: Actually I believe we are missing just one thing
timbo7io: hell yeah
gigafact: lol
extr3mity: ok
ggwpl2p: brute force smash SMOrc
extr3mity: whats the problem?
Klingenwetzer: only when I'm made
joker2k999: brute force is better. and more fun
imshafay: we need to rethink from the stat
Klingenwetzer: *mad
extr3mity: someone link me
timbo7io: spin up those cpus
imshafay: start
imaginenation: This is like the sunday church
imaginenation: but better
timbo7io: brute force in the house
imshafay: WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace
st47ik: SMOrc
Klingenwetzer: SMOrc
sub_g_hammond: i got material that can get you higher then a school girl knee sucks who's in
jotye: :) that makes me happy to hear
HousedHorse: can anyone explain what P and Q are in the problem statement? I joined late
st47ik: we can solve it all SMOrc
imshafay: n-c-k 1 <- have you tried this
st47ik: by sheer bruteforce
Dodo131296: Could you please recap what you did until now?
maxminos: have you tried turning it off and on again
extr3mity: WHAT'S THE QUESTION SIR
bedo9898: can somebody link this problem ? thanks
joker2k999: off by 20
montecarlo: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/submissions
f00z: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
Zanfr1980: of course its our fault
Klingenwetzer: the formulation of the excercise alone is already out for you to confuse you. LUL
bedo9898: thanks chat
Klingenwetzer: typical uni exercise
extr3mity: if subfactorials are a function of factorials, then just forget about them
extr3mity: seems convoluted
averagesizepens: love youselfes boys programming can brake you
st47ik: <3
andrestogas: warming up? LUL
st47ik: tough warm up Kappa
imaginenation: [derangements(k, n-P(n)) * nCr(P(n), P(n)-k)]/n!
893gdjw: yoo it's geohot. getting sued by sony :)
imaginenation: I think I might be wrong
dorkmo: that Subway sandwich bit emoji made me so hungry
MrSlick1015: damn thats a nice house
imaginenation: i really want him to become a minecraft streamer
giorgostheo97: Anyone attending any interesting conferences rn?
imaginenation: guys when comes back tell him to wash hands
imaginenation: LOL
Ipkstef: what are we working on todya?
extr3mity: HAHAHAHAHHAHAHAHA
Klingenwetzer: programming can make me stay awake till 8am and still hook me on
extr3mity: I LOVE THIS CHANNEL
snbk97: power piss
JanTSV: ha
st47ik: DansGame
imaginenation: GEO WASH Your hands buddy
trashtofu: wash hands?
KingKewpa: thats a powerful mic
eddysohealthy: wash hands
Zanfr1980: real coders piss in bottles
marfinatorhx: you piss like a horse
JanTSV: wash
averagesizepens: wash hands please
Triphasic: yo what's up Hotz
maxminos: how did you wash your hands without getting water in your sleeve
fa_k: wash hands DansGame
Klingenwetzer: LUL
sub_g_hammond: take a shower bro
giorgostheo97: WASH YO HANDS MONKEY
CallMeShockZz: hi geo
capsimirhd: LOL
imaginenation: wash your hands
Fr0zenOfficial: hey, clean hands = clean brain, refreshed xD
Klingenwetzer: Relax CHAT forsenW
st47ik: ResidentSleeper
sub_g_hammond: Shower bro
extr3mity: lets me honest, who washes their hands all the time?
extr3mity: lets be*
maxminos: me
extr3mity: after pissing
snbk97: me
fa_k: me :)
893gdjw: me
marfinatorhx: me
Zanfr1980: people with OCD
st47ik: me :)
CallMeShockZz: hello everyone :D
trashtofu: me
extr3mity: LOL OK OK
giorgostheo97: ME
massivly: washing ur hands after pissing? LUL
Klingenwetzer: not me :)
CallMeShockZz: how r u guys today?
yrpsa: Bleach my hands
andrestogas: Just google the answer Kappa
st47ik: bruh if u touch the toilet it's already nasty
Zanfr1980: burn my hands after touching anything
Zanfr1980: only way to be sure
CallMeShockZz: HE'S TOUCHING HIS MOUTH AOIWDJOIAWJD
imaginenation: i did some math geo and heres a forumla i could be wrong: [derangements(k, n-P(n)) * nCr(P(n), P(n)-k)]/n!
T_boltsniper : What is the problem?
T_boltsniper : can someone link me
imaginenation: nah dude too lazy
st47ik: UV sanitizing my hands every time Kappa
imshafay: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
T_boltsniper : ty
st47ik: Hepatitis incoming
marfinatorhx: im washing hands after pissing but not after pupping, am i disgusting
Zanfr1980: alcohol hand sanitizer is good enough most of the time
GoOnAli: DansGame
st47ik: DansGame
Zanfr1980: but forget your skin if you do it too often
fa_k: what is it really about 8*7*6
imaginenation: anyone knows geos skin care routine?
sub_g_hammond: do you even math guys
fa_k: i fuck bitches for living
averagesizepens: you should wash hands before pissing
Zanfr1980: for face? hands?
fa_k: how would i know math bro
Klingenwetzer: this is some good ASMR coding stream forsenThink
Serbius: sup haker daddy
st47ik: he washes his hands with skin oil from typing too much
marfinatorhx: whats math for in coding lul
trashtofu: hhkb clack clack
imaginenation: I don
swagettiyolonaise69: how is this basic
xlionel775: delete everything and start again
Zanfr1980: yes theoritically it makes sense to wash hands before... but if you are at home your hands already have your own germs
Klingenwetzer: lmfao @st47ik
imaginenation: if bruteforce isn't working then definitely there is error in logic
Nuroki: i dont get it he has expected output as the last string in his answer wtf?
st47ik: logic vs bruteforce SMOrc
Zanfr1980: if outside, wash after touching any surface that isn't you
Zanfr1980: just bruteforce it dude
bhad: Just skip the question LUL
sub_g_hammond: i'm addicted to peanut butter SeriousSloth
Klingenwetzer: just combine logic with bruteforce SMOrc 🤝 djorjxBrain
trashtofu: Touching the air rajjHAA
GoOnAli: just make it work 4Head
Zanfr1980: @Klingenwetzer you summarize bitcoin mining
capsimirhd: maybe ill wake up tomorrow to george still doing the problem
Klingenwetzer: rephtoSmile np @Zanfr1980
prometheus_k: Yeah. Its night here too. 12 Am. Gotta sleep now.
st47ik: he gonna jailbreak it don't worry chat
prometheus_k: Goodnight weebs.
KAZERKE: finally caught a livestream moon2POGGYWOGGY
gigafact: did anyone see that 1B bitcoin transaction?
Zanfr1980: just code tensor cores to solve it for you?
imaginenation: by the way number of derangements is approx n!/e you just need to find the cardinality of the P(n)-k I think
giorgostheo97: @zanfr1980 yeah true... the other surface thing
Klingenwetzer: 8pm for me :3
prometheus_k: :) XoXo
imaginenation: and then derange those
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz maybe this help you https://pastebin.com/448gbF88
averagesizepens: submit code even if wrong answer
st47ik: oh no :o
maxminos: pastebin virus
gigafact: it's safe
maxminos: thats what i viral person would say
imaginenation: I dont even know what are his P c and n
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Klingenwetzer: HAHAHA
imshafay: WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
abstractingagent: Excellent, we've made some progress - time to spark one up
timbo7io: hahahahaha
Quecks_: if it isnt easy it isnt worth it
maxminos: see he knows
CaptainAshtar: which website is that
st47ik: LUL
joker2k999: LUL
bhad: what are you learning tho
Serbius: whats the problem?
fa_k: LUL
timbo7io: thats great
gigafact: George doing it the hard way
imaginenation: Dude can you tell us what your P,n and c are ?
KingKewpa: "so close" - george 5 hours ago
sub_g_hammond: nikola tesla is gay SmoocherZ
somewhere_rains: !topic
somewhere_rains: !uptime
averagesizepens: go back to adding 20 be result oriented
Klingenwetzer: relax take your time ^^
CaptainAshtar: @sub_g_hammond why you are saying that?
xlionel775: start again
MobsterSquirrel: you know a legend is coding when you look a the numbers... totally not 'cause the motherf*cker is like Elon Musk
giorgostheo97: Why the pigeon was male ???? Kappa
fa_k: @MobsterSquirrel why do you talk like the 13%
st47ik: uptime is around 2h 30min maybe
bhad: watch a khan academy video
KyoshiDeath: What is the stream about today ?
CaptainAshtar: can you tell us the website with this tasks
sub_g_hammond: @captainashtar he was evil af i studied him
snbk97: I can't even solve easy ones, it's very depressing for me to solve comp questions :c
st47ik: @georgehotz hydrate bro DrinkPurple
CaptainAshtar: @sub_g_hammond you are wrong he was going to give the world something amazing but nobody cares because of the money
maxminos: oof
fa_k: chat Jebaited
spanilith: spanilith subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak!
GoOnAli: I am from the future 3 weeks to be exact, George still hasn't made any progress :(
kratosboii: Hey george @georgehotz
KingKewpa: tesla wasn't gay, he was in love with a pigeon
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG
PhearTheCeal: a MALE pigeon
jkpfeffer: do it with recursion
gigafact: George you need to add stream notifications
maxminos: that will deplete the time it takes for him to solve
CaptainAshtar: do somebody know the website he is in right now to take tasks for practice?
maxminos: hackerrank
giorgostheo97: Leave nikola and his death Rays alone
sub_g_hammond: hackerrank
CaptainAshtar: @maxminos thank you
xlionel775: dude this is a long warm up lol
murkythunder: jesus what res is his monitor
maxminos: you're welcome
imaginenation: was his subfactorial function description correct?
maxminos: no clue
maxminos: we dont know math
th3_maj0r: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
imaginenation: aah
imaginenation: i dont know math either
imaginenation: i just google
maxminos: he should copyand paste an existing subfact function
averagesizepens: 20
PhearTheCeal: @th3_maj0r what is P and Q in the problem description?
giorgostheo97: Po ta to , ma ths
Blobiciously: p and q means a and b
imaginenation: you see subfactorial is basically the number of derangements which is approximately factorial(n) divided by constant e rounded to nearest integer
maxminos: vectorization of a and b
maxminos: okay
averagesizepens: WRONG
maxminos: what are derangements
Blobiciously: google them
imshafay: Mathematical function, suitable for both symbolic and numerical manipulation. For noninteger n, the numerical value of Subfactorial[n] is given by Gamma[n 1,-1]/E. Subfactorial can be evaluated to arbitrary numerical precision. A permutation in which no object appears in its natural place is called a derangement. Subfactorial automatically threads over lists. Subfactorial[0] gives 1
maxminos: tldr
kektobiologist: LUL
menchedanem: all f***n days
imaginenation: derangemetns are basically how many different ways can you arrange things such that none of them are in their original positions
averagesizepens: derangements are numbers that would commit mass murdering in a school
imaginenation: you see subfactorial is basically the number of derangements which is approximately factorial(n) divided by constant e rounded to nearest integer
kektobiologist: where can we see the qeustion?
ganeshvjy: Yes
maxminos: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
sub_g_hammond: guys i created a terminal version of BinDiff
maxminos: geohot hates euler confirmed
murkythunder: why did they put english punctuations in math
imaginenation: we will be waiting al lnight then i suppose
buraknml: Is this hackerRank? Cant really see the site name
imaginenation: ya dude
imaginenation: euler is mainstream
ganeshvjy: Printf 356
maxminos: ZOOM
Klingenwetzer: yes it is
maxminos: looks like brute forece
kratosboii: lol
imaginenation: press x to doubt
maxminos: x
imaginenation: x
averagesizepens: x
giorgostheo97: Do permutations?.?.
MeSaber: y
ganeshvjy: X
extr3mity: GEO WHATS THE NAME OF THE CHALLENGE? I'm on hackerrank
yrpsa: Bro just plug this in machine learning and let it solve itself
maxminos: good idea
maxminos: i approve
gigafact: trying too hard to to brute force
ForsakenReborn: @yrpsa you don't really get the point of these challenges do you
imaginenation: lets train a nueral net fo compute subfactorial bro
maxminos: probably dont even need that many layers
yrpsa: Lmao
maxminos: we're watching it rn dude
kratosboii: this is mr robot irl
giorgostheo97: @sub_g_hammond it’s out?.?
imaginenation: when in doubt use a Neural Net bro, isn
imshafay: You can try the NEAREST INTEGER FUNCTION
ganeshvjy: I am gonna go man.. Good luck solving
averagesizepens: is mr robot inspired after george hotz Kappa
Rezzmeze: can we just do the math then implement :D
imaginenation: isn't that what he said the output of his perception system is? a 1024 dimensional feature vector
Rezzmeze: it is math question not coding :D
scumtoots: it's my favourite influencer, george hotz!
imaginenation: LOL
maxminos: ,
KAZERKE: monkaS
extr3mity: what's the name of the challenge though?
KAZERKE: monkaS 👉 .
imaginenation: @imshafay he isn't using the e shit
r0bru: What are your PC specs?
andrestogas: LUL
imshafay: Got it
gigafact: razer laptop
imshafay: I am actually trying here
kektobiologist: , 👈 monkaS
imaginenation: he has a razer blade
ggwpl2p: any e-shitters
drawingdead_: can i get link to the problem plx?
maxminos: a year later: it really does need the e shit
imaginenation: i need an e-girlfriend
imshafay: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
ForsakenReborn: !runtime
dorkmo: I'm reading the wiki page for Euler, pretty wild dude
timbo7io: hahahaha
timbo7io: hell yeah
drawingdead_: ty
timbo7io: this is fun
averagesizepens: LUL
maxminos: this challenge is giving him partial derangement rn
timbo7io: thanks george, wfh life is isolating
imaginenation: i told ya
bulbaz0r: the e shit is coming from an approximation that e = sum(1/k!)
KAZERKE: FrankerZ
gigafact: need to defrag the brain a bit
bulbaz0r: so isn't exact I'm pretty sure
drawingdead_: at least its a challenge that causes pain and not just life
imaginenation: i remember the inclusion exclusion principle too
maxminos: it's a limit
maxminos: i dont
imaginenation: include exclusion include exclusion include exclusion
maxminos: is it just sets
timbo7io: is that the pigeon hole principle?
imaginenation: just do it till you die
kektobiologist: whats going on why not just implemeent it verbatim
payapayagaming: PIE principle PogChamp
imshafay: A permutation with no fixed point
grootdoloot: FightPepper
imaginenation: whats the lesson for today kids? math is hard
KAZERKE: virus in chat WutFace
timbo7io: hahahah
imaginenation: bernoulli solved it while smoking pot
timbo7io: an decade
joker2k999: about 6 seconds
imaginenation: in a day
st47ik: bernoulli took his longass time
averagesizepens: like 10 min
ggwpl2p: atleast three fiddy
imaginenation: why is fiddy so funny dude
imaginenation: always cracks me
drawingdead_: this is crazy hard, i dont even know what its trying to ask
maxminos: because it reminds us of 50 cent
imaginenation: all i remember is that inc exc is really hard
maxminos: it's a math problem
maxminos: the language of the gods
imaginenation: I am going to watch some minecraft to chill this is very stressful
drawingdead_: how old is george/
imaginenation: stress is bad
st47ik: the language of world simulators*
imaginenation: george is 29
Rezzmeze: Can you show what is the problem
averagesizepens: old is just a number
drawingdead_: i bet he never smoked weed before
joker2k999: LUL
saulgd: leetcode > hackerrank
yrpsa: A UB? That was something i herd in math class
maxminos: ew
ggwpl2p: pretty sure I had this in my discrete maths class but I dont remember
imaginenation: does anyone know when george is going to do a minecraft sream
imaginenation: stream
drawingdead_: i dont know if i was always stupid or if weed made me stupid
maxminos: right after he solves this problem
saulgd: what kind of spongy ass keyboard is he using
joker2k999: prolly next time he lights up a bowl
maxminos: the latter, just to make you feel better
averagesizepens: weed didnt help forsure
gordovolador: or both
imaginenation: if you smoked weed before 25 which is the age for full brain development then defenitely that is what made you stupid
kratosboii: true
imaginenation: definitely*
drawingdead_: i started smoking at 17
RonDune: wait I thought the subfactorial generating function already follows the inclusion/exclusion principle?
imaginenation: youre brain dead not drawingdead then
ggwpl2p: typing on a keyboard that is not mechanical is anti-ASMR
Goatwow: !uptime
drawingdead_: brain dead is fair
drawingdead_: i hear it often
fwef64: Why is he using Windows?
drawingdead_: must be true
imaginenation: LOL he just added 6
izikatoshka: those keys resist like 300g force
imaginenation: AHAHHA what a scam
eynalhurts: Cause Windows is the superior OS
drawingdead_: well good luck guys, this channel is too far above me
fwef64: @eynalhurts come on now
averagesizepens: it'scalled hacking
drawingdead_: peace
imaginenation: Explain to us whats going on in your brain
IMLadyBoy: nope
averagesizepens: nope
maxminos: nothing
spanilith: i hate not having a numpad
timbo7io: hahahaha
maxminos: oof
averagesizepens: georgie thinks we are hard wired to his brain, he lives in the future
imaginenation: i love you
timbo7io: rabbit hole
Klingenwetzer: LUL
gigafact: damn
timbo7io: ya?
KAZERKE: LUL
imaginenation: does that make the ice thicker?
kratosboii: monkaS
imshafay: Can i get 1% of your brain mate?
gigafact: that is how you moderate your chat
KAZERKE: monkaS 👉 ,
smurfd0: add parantheses?
Ziv0: he likes chewing thin ice monkaS
gigafact: scare tactics
averagesizepens: you forgot * 5 5 i guess
weedlord666: piccolo bean cannon pose
asaalgk: have you played zachtronics programming games like tis100, shenzen i/o and exapunks
Goatwow: @georgehotz huge fan <3 keep up the good work!
maxminos: * 1
drawingdead_: if i spent a lot of time doing hackerrank problems and stuff would there be a reasonable chance of finding employment? 32yr neet that never had a job or girl, i suppose no hope right?
smurfd0: (8*7*6) (8*7) - (7*6) 6
maxminos: pemdas man
maxminos: learn it
kratosboii: @drawingdead_ apply to google mate
drawingdead_: my resume is just what they looking for
drawingdead_: never been fired
KAZERKE: go to google yea
st47ik: lmao
kratosboii: YOu don't even need a resume
imaginenation: geo wash your hands please this time
izikatoshka: mad professor
blueskycata: What’s the leaderboard rank based on?
extr3mity: HAHAHAAHA AGAIN?!!
st47ik: peeing too much??
KAZERKE: Kreygasm
eddysohealthy: why does he piss so often
st47ik: caffeine maybe
imaginenation: soo much pee
averagesizepens: he is too hydrated
spanilith: spindrift
FargioFarmani: wash your hands bro
maxminos: the subfactorial truly is the derangement number
joker2k999: caffeine makes me go like that
imaginenation: peeing to often can be a symptom of diabetes
izikatoshka: what makes more sound, piss or keyboard?
st47ik: drink 4 coffees a day and you'll pee 4!
ggwpl2p: didnt wash hands
KAZERKE: monkaS
andrestogas: WutFace
joker2k999: LUL
imaginenation: I LOVE YOU GEO I CARE FOR YOU i dont want you to get diabetes
timbo7io: hell yeah
imaginenation: xD
st47ik: green tea caffeine so good Kreygasm
timbo7io: pee is life
Yemtex: !time
drawingdead_: is this a futuristic furniture style?
drawingdead_: wheres the couch
weedlord666: no ice maker
KAZERKE: put ice with his unwashed hand WutFace
timbo7io: lolol
timbo7io: hahaha
joker2k999: been up for about 3:30
st47ik: kitchenware
timbo7io: fuck hacker rank
maxminos: switch to vim
dorkmo: @ imagination https://doihaveprediabetes.org/take-the-risk-test/
andrestogas: warming up btw
Cluwe: math is surprisingly hard to brute force
Yemtex: @georgehotz why do you take so much time to solve this ?
Klingenwetzer: LUL
ggwpl2p: its the e-shit bro
joker2k999: LUL
st47ik: E
averagesizepens: will he discover e?
drawingdead_: has anyone here solved this?
drawingdead_: does anyone understand what its asking?
drawingdead_: is the like an eli5?
maxminos: no idont understand all this sub and co stuff
RonDune: the simplest possible incl/excl formula is ∣a∣ ∣b∣−∣a∩b∣ I think
maxminos: that's union
drawingdead_: im gonna go watch the ufc prelims, i understand getting punched in the face
averagesizepens: LUL
drawingdead_: i was bullied all my life
ObscureCloud: it's obviously 1337
ggwpl2p: i thought the answer to everything was 42?
KAZERKE: drawingdead_ moon2PH
TerminatDiem: ∩ is intersect
jrrbls: @ggwpl2p it was
jrrbls: not anymore
Klingenwetzer: LUL
timbo7io: lol
gigafact: lol
maxminos: YES
maxminos: thats what we been saying
timbo7io: well use it as a math guy
imaginenation: lets use a GAN
Klingenwetzer: USE machine learning on everything BrokeBack
timbo7io: hey professor, err i mean ml
KingKewpa: machine learning PogChamp
imshafay: I vote for Mathematics and formulae understnading
andrestogas: Machine Learning DansGame
imaginenation: i am down for ML
Cluwe: i think i got a formula for the probability but i have no idea how to get a and b now
Yemtex: is this nasa shit
ggwpl2p: no this is e-shit
revolutionist123: What is he doing?
Crying_Potato: pawsU is he hacking the internet
Shasan_: I failed precalulus but passed calculus 2 education system LUL
ObscureCloud: any link to this problem?
maxminos: hes taking a break
x_algorithm: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
Cluwe: this is the warm up for the hard problems
drawingdead_: this problem is the same as a project euler problem
Dorgesh: warm up 4Head
Yemtex: @Cluwe how hard are the hard problems
Yemtex: uffff
maxminos: why would it be called project euler if it doesnt need e :c
Shasan_: A good warm up problem is print your name
T_boltsniper : This is the warmup? wow
MatiGoG: n-k!*n! ?
maxminos: how do you print your name
gigafact: printf("geo")
maxminos: no no
maxminos: YOUR name
averagesizepens: we re getting close boys
MatiGoG: @yourname
Yemtex: print("my name")
imshafay: subfact(n) - subfact(n-1) subfact(n-2)
imshafay: Hey try this
Shasan_: @maxminos @gigafact print your name
imshafay: subfact(n) - subfact(n-1) subfact(n-2)
Shasan_: Print your name using functions
maxminos: my brain does not function
imshafay: subtract
asaalgk: whats the task mates
asaalgk: url too tiny
drawingdead_: it doesnt matter if its prime or not
JUST_5HEAD: @asaalgk Project Euler #239: Twenty-two Foolish Primes
asaalgk: ooh okay
spanilith: speedrun gorilla .bas
JUST_5HEAD: @asaalgk on hackerrank
ObscureCloud: @x_algorithm Thanks. It's part of project euler i see https://pbs.twimg.com/media/D-Oo62fWwAAyX0x.png
maxminos: the way to solve the problem is to go backwards
maxminos: <3
st47ik: crowd-sourced problem solving <3
robbsalm: i dont do open source
drawingdead_: i admire you guys, this shit is hard man
maxminos: it was a ready player one reference so it must be true
jessicak4: safe
dorkmo: subfact(n-subfact(-1 n subact(n-2)))
maxminos: thats some intense recursion
Cluwe: @georgehotz can you explain again what you have figured out by now and what the question is right now in a bit more detail?
Shasan_: Geo is so smart I love it
jessicak4: lol
maxminos: passive aggressive messages are starting
ViktorTV: @dorkmo what's the question
ParanoiaSystem: man what is it? hacker rank?
maxminos: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
Causevd: think think think think
Occamm: danHmm
ProfessorMagikarp0: PrideWingL nickiThink PrideWingR
Klingenwetzer: nymnHmm
Thomasbrah: i want to make something, but i don't know what, anybody else like this ? MingLee
Shasan_: Once we solve this let solve it in php
higgsas: oh yes m0xy5Head
KingKewpa: u have to be deranged to solve math is what im understanding here
ObscureCloud: C is best for these type of problems
maxminos: lets solve it in pseudocode
yrpsa: @obscurecloud can you explain why
Causevd: he just googled that, thats why yrpsa Keepo
MisterKappa: lmao
Yemtex: pseudocode: think .. death
IMLadyBoy: nope
murkythunder: of course
averagesizepens: nah
timbo7io: lol
timbo7io: brute force
maxminos: what is the ncr function again
timbo7io: you remind me of myself
timbo7io: hehe
IMLadyBoy: @georgehotz do you understand why? lol
ggwpl2p: Jebaited
murkythunder: the world will never know how much time went into that two lined for loop
joker2k999: there on to us..
JUST_5HEAD: just add 4 4Head
averagesizepens: -4
ObscureCloud: @yrpsa Doing competitive programming and dealing with similar issues moroever if you notice all the top 10 solvers of all project euler problems used c which is also the main language used during IOI and ICPC
imshafay: N 1
imshafay: forgot the loop last
timbo7io: i know
timbo7io: you have the brain torque
timbo7io: i have the wine
timbo7io: hahaha
murkythunder: what do you think of the colon in python
maxminos: did he do it
timbo7io: basically
maxminos: if he did it pogs
gigafact: nice
averagesizepens: 50%
andrestogas: Kappa
Causevd: EZ
robbsalm: "medium" difficulty
timbo7io: lol
gigafact: progress
timbo7io: ya hacker rank
timbo7io: smh
Venald: lru_cache from functools
Scott_w_c: im learning python and cannot understand the def() function plz explain
ph4tal_: what was that
robbsalm: whats this sound
ggwpl2p: :o
timbo7io: DEGENERATE VS DERANGEMENT lol
maxminos: thats what math has come to
davens: chat, is he still on the same problem from 2h ago ?
mattdougherty0: will this be on youtube later?
maxminos: mhm
Halixness: when it says not in the time limits: I guess the algorithmic cost is too high
Klingenwetzer: LUL
timbo7io: intresting
ph4tal_: what's a bit leak
timbo7io: yeah
gigafact: @mattdougherty0 will be uploaded
bhad: thats the most green you've ever seen in your life
Lefer_: Is this my favourite instagrammer streaming again? PogChamp
robbsalm: lol
Klingenwetzer: getting information about the solution through not knowing the solution
murkythunder: my favorite ig THOT Kreygasm
Causevd: LUL
Akash_44: LUL
ggwpl2p: major bruhmoment
JUST_5HEAD: lmfao
KingKewpa: thot leader
imaginenation: you need to post more in IG
maxminos: oof
sendnudeees: @georgehotz favourite os?
ObscureCloud: ironically enough this would be the last stream to find thots in
joker2k999: deep
robbsalm: @georgehotz what do you think about energy drinks?
ObscureCloud: although the first one i'd go to if twitch asked me where neets hang
bhad: hey thats cheating!
shlver: SeemsGood
imaginenation: damn
sebiyy: i didnt poop for 5 days should i go to a doctor ?
yrpsa: :3
Venald: Why didn't you use lru_cache from functools for the cache optimization?
samtheprogram: how long been streaming
xternl: !uptime
Causevd: he's been streaming for 24 hours
ggwpl2p: @sebiyy yeah mate what the fuck :)
samtheprogram: !uptime
murkythunder: overflowing in python LUL
gigafact: no
Lefer_: @sebiyy drink some coffee bro
tanoshiizo: 3:04 h
shlver: @sebiyy yeah dude go to the doctor
timtimlkl: @sebiyy get some banana
imaginenation: you know if its overflowing just mod every number
Moskon: !uptime
sebiyy: i dont eat alot
shlver: yeah just normalize with mod
sebiyy: i drink coffe every morning :)
trashtofu: There has to be a simpler solution than this right?
ggwpl2p: run to the doctor buddy
sendnudeees: @georgehotz favourite os?
sebiyy: can i die lol ?
samtheprogram: !uptime
samtheprogram: nvm
sebiyy: i feel normal but i know its weird
maxminos: what is runtime error
kanogger: what is python
shlver: I actually have no idea what problem he's trying to solve
maxminos: we dont either
ggwpl2p: @kanogger big snek
maxminos: its just about disks
oreid52: Project Euler 239 on Hacker rank I think
averagesizepens: same
weedlord666: i dont know what a derangement is lol
solomonspeare: LUL
Hamled: doesn't python have automatic upgrade to bignum
ObscureCloud: https://oeis.org/A000166
K0enich: rabin miller test?
sebiyy: how often do you ppo @georgehotz
sebiyy: poop
yrpsa: How do i gitgud in programming
shlver: He doesn't poop, like Kim Jong un
IMLadyBoy: where are you using that?
weedlord666: wow absolutley savage ice chewing
JUST_5HEAD: Kappa
murkythunder: good enough :)
trashtofu: Kappa
andrestogas: Kappa
davens: lmao, fair enuff
the12eaz: Kappa Kappa
ggwpl2p: you dont eat ice you absolute madlad
samtheprogram: memoize all the functions
Causevd: ice chewing gives you 35 intelligence and it's a problem solver Keepo
ggwpl2p: bro dont eat the ice maaaan
shlver: he's rage chewing
sebiyy: programming is so ez you just need 140IQ and time to sit on a fucking chair for 9hours
kanogger: today is not my birthday
trashtofu: Pagophagia is real
McBainTS: Can't you use modulus in your factorial function?
guccibruf: eating ice helps you to keep your head cool
McBainTS: That would help alot
feggis: If you were able to break iOS/PS3, this will be a piece of cake.
solomonspeare: @georgehotz why doesn't it say what kind of runtime error ?
Hamled: run it in something locally which will give you better error output?
JUST_5HEAD: @solomonspeare too much information
Causevd: NomNom NomNom
sebiyy: what is this drink of gods ?
kanogger: wieso
gigafact: it's a challenge
ggwpl2p: cant watch this man treat ice like this
ObscureCloud: what we all learned today keep ice nearby when solving a hot problem
trashtofu: Eating ice DansGame
averagesizepens: stop eating crystals dog
solomonspeare: @JUST_5HEAD well but like isn't that information vital in debugging? what's the point of "disallowing" debugging ?
timbo7io: haha
Klingenwetzer: LUL
imaginenation: LOL
gigafact: lol
ggwpl2p: any e-shitters
timbo7io: ya
imaginenation: TOLD YA
kanogger: eee
Causevd: oh god LUL
sebiyy: fucking math lOL
imaginenation: nah man
timbo7io: exponentioalll
imaginenation: we aint doing e
joker2k999: damn
shlver: math WutFace
imaginenation: lets do it rigorously
sebiyy: what did he study ?
averagesizepens: e discovered e PogChamp
imaginenation: Geo we aint doing e shit
kanogger: @sebiyy gender studies
haircutjimmy: Hi everyone.
sebiyy: no wonder his head is so big
sebiyy: 5Head
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: 5Head 🍷
JUST_5HEAD: @solomonspeare you are not in this challenge to debug your code, you are here because you are supposed to know what you do.. thats how i see it, i see your point though and i somewhat agree
feggis: @sebiyy BHe jailbroke the iPhone as 17 if I remember correctly, this means that his studies is pretty irrelevant at this stage.
ggwpl2p: all i see is this insane guy chewing ice
feggis: @sebiyy Studies != skills
shlver: PogChamp
tanoshiizo: Pog ?
imaginenation: close enough
sebiyy: still nobody learns high maths in home
tanoshiizo: NotLikeThis
bhad: as if jailbreaking was hard back then? feggis , before apple hired masterminds
Goatwow: good shit!!
Annex_Greenland: Is he jail breaking the new iPhone
Klingenwetzer: Probably LUL
samtheprogram: memoize everything
averagesizepens: not even 50%
sebiyy: is this coke with coke ?
solomonspeare: @JUST_5HEAD lol I see :D
Klingenwetzer: memoize BlessRNG
st47ik: E
feggis: @bhad Nah, wont say it was so good. I succeeded bypassing pincodes to extract data by myself on iOS4.
smakatak: chat what website is that ?
dorkmo: I haven't peed once since we started
Lol_for_lol5: didn't he unlock the iphone?
FargioFarmani: wash your hands bro @georgehotz
yrpsa: How do i get to the skill level to solve euler problema
averagesizepens: that doesnt count as washing hands
ViolaAlpina: LUL
KingKewpa: all this braining makes you pee a lot it seems
Klingenwetzer: same @dorkmo
Klingenwetzer: LUL
sebiyy: all programmers look the same
JUST_5HEAD: @solomonspeare im just guessing right, i dont know if what i said is actually true. but thats what i see
imaginenation: press E to do the E-shit
timbo7io: oh its comming
imaginenation: E
timbo7io: yeee haaaa
averagesizepens: E
th3_maj0r: I think he use hairs to "wash" his hands
feggis: @bhad And i wasn't skilled at all at tje time, so yeah. Having the right mindset is key, plus a bit of knowledge about how things works.
JUST_5HEAD: you can optimize this for loop
sebiyy: how tall is he ?
Klingenwetzer: cmonBruh @sebiyy
imshafay: E
Klingenwetzer: forsenE ❓
imaginenation: E PoG
solomonspeare: forsenE Clap
JUST_5HEAD: forsen subs everywhere lmao
Klingenwetzer: forsenBoys
sebiyy: too large thats what she said
Klingenwetzer: big fan FeelsGoodMan
sebiyy: and gave me back my money
ascential138: how many questions has he solved so far?
samtheprogram: memoize?
solomonspeare: @georgehotz in my computer math.factorial(1000000) has been running for 10 mins now
samtheprogram: probably not actually
shirafx: yoooooooooooooooooo
boxofninjas: generators
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Klingenwetzer: -1
Crwth: what is the question
dorkmo: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
Klingenwetzer: OpieOP
dorkmo: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leonhard_Euler
averagesizepens: try 3
blackhoneygames: lol
swftdev: job interview prep not going well :d
BTM_Ole: BTM_Ole subscribed at Tier 1.
dorkmo: Party1
st47ik: PogChamp
solomonspeare: LUL
blackhoneygames: i grind leetcode for jobsearch right now and wanna blow my brains out, cant imagine someone doing this shit for fun
spitza: can you code when your stoned?
swftdev: also math lib has build in factorial
Klingenwetzer: LUL @blackhoneygames
4_realzies: Why are there different test cases?
hashcoder: George, tell if it is real to write text rewriter (helper service for copywriters) using AI?
ImNotTrolling: @4_realzies so you are actually solving the problem instead of one case
swftdev: lru cache and build in fact function
TylerWaldon: how to become a data scientist
Klingenwetzer: THX SUB!~
4_realzies: @ImNotTrolling gotcha, ty
feggis: @spitza Me and my friend had a weekend coding and drinking. On sunday morning we were pretty amazed of what type of shit we made. And most amazed about that the code was in fact running properly.
samtheprogram: I couldn't pass google foobar because of timeouts, now i don't feel so bad
feggis: @spitza Cant say anything about being stoned tho.
JUST_5HEAD: try it to see if its the subfact fun
Infinitelym: what level did you get to in foobar?
MonkaSupreme: MonkaSupreme subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak! damn
Infinitelym: @samtheprogram
samtheprogram: only 2nd
samtheprogram: it was either a prime number or factorial problem I got stuck on, ran out of time executing
Infinitelym: my friend is on 3rd right now and he is scared to go forward lol
samtheprogram: you will be "straight scrubbing toilets" all weekend
samtheprogram: lol you have to complete it within 48 hours right? so there's nothing to do but go forward
samtheprogram: unless they changed it
Infinitelym: the timer starts once you accept the problem. my friends hasnt accepted it yet haha
spitza: @feggis sounds fun, yeah i think i'd do better on alcohol tbh, coding while high is sooo hard for me lol
samtheprogram: true. I haven't done it in 3 years but I have another invite and I'm scared to try again
shirafx: any tips not to get distracted while programming
shirafx: ?
shirafx: today I just stared at the monitor, hating my life
Siandemm: dont distract
KingKewpa: listen to classical music
sebiyy: the answer is 32 bro
Infinitelym: how did you find foobar?
kanogger: @shirafx ADDERAL
Klingenwetzer: THX SUB!~
samtheprogram: google foobar
hashcoder: George, tell if it is real to write text rewriter (helper service for copywriters) using AI?
solomonspeare: @georgehotz I don't think there is "overflowing" in python3, those runtime errors must be smth else
samtheprogram: I was on Google Maps documentation constantly for months because of my job and I got the invite through that
serhejenos: Version control with a notepad.
McBainTS: Can you use numpy?
mister_manager_: How's the church coming along?
Infinitelym: lol nice, my friend found it while researching something for his college class
yrpsa: How to get inv for foobar
therealspitonyourmama: @georgehotz what are u making?
sebiyy: i hack the russians on a daily basis
dorkmo: is it worth converting all the prime numbers to decimals in order of occurance 1,2,3,4,5,6...
selcuktatar: Im feelin bad
MonkaSupreme: whats this page_
MonkaSupreme: ?
selcuktatar: Idk
solomonspeare: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
MonkaSupreme: ah
Ax1SGodz1lla: KonCha
swftdev: c^a del
JUST_5HEAD: can you put custom input and get a timeout ?
voxelfox0125: Would be funny if geo did an online interview with a google engineer at https://interviewing.io
sebiyy: how can i learn to code by sleeping ?
sebiyy: i want to dream how i code
minmaxy: i mean, he WAS a google engineer...
timbo7io: lol
solomonspeare: Pog
imshafay: that would be company called CARNIVAL
imshafay: I believe.
swftdev: blacklisted Kappa
my_curiosity: 10% in Algorithms category?
myaocat: hype
murkythunder: he was a project zero, not a google swe/university intern
FadezzHD: @georgehotz Hello Geo, first time watching the stream
i4t_: i4t_ subscribed at Tier 1.
dorkmo: Party1
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG
FadezzHD: !uptime
swftdev: w
kanogger: N
cjocol2201: F
kanogger: C
cjocol2201: D
selcuktatar: What’s keyboard 🙄?
dorkmo: MacBook pro
Klingenwetzer: LUL
swftdev: hhkb, pro 2
swftdev: silenced im assumming
gigafact: https://www.hhkeyboard.com/
selcuktatar: 🙏 thanks
plsgetmeout: is it really basic programming :)
KingKewpa: do i become a hacker with that keyboard?
Klingenwetzer: 1. make it work 2. make it faster
Siandemm: u lose money with it if u ask that question
selcuktatar: Yep snsjs
yrpsa: It comes prebuilt w hack key
swftdev: rule 1 nest loops
solomonspeare: “Premature optimization is the root of all evil” monkaS
my_curiosity: you also need the mouse to be a true hacker
Klingenwetzer: mouse LUL
gigafact: uninstall mouse drivers
selcuktatar: @my_curiosity definitely
7Locrian7: monkaHmm
swftdev: lru cache math.factorial()
Klingenwetzer: FeelsBadMan
myaocat: assembly will make it faster
swftdev: zzzz
samtheprogram: rm -f /dev/input/mice
kanogger: BASIC PROGRAMMING Kappa
imaginenation: lol i got 4 test cases right
selcuktatar: TheIlluminati
samtheprogram: is there any other programming category on twitch now?
Klingenwetzer: ^
fe26tr: i don't think so
7Locrian7: moon2T
JUST_5HEAD: just bit shift 4Head
solomonspeare: Pog
imaginenation: :(
Albinkj91: Thought the Science and Technology was the standard one
Woozi_: most programming streams are in the science and technology section
samtheprogram: there's just Basic Programming and Science and Technology
sebiyy: how tall is geo ?
imshafay: How can I become a lead hacker?
samtheprogram: I think Basic Programming is new, I used to stream in Science and Technology
yrpsa: 7foot
sebiyy: height = coding skills
imaginenation: that is my solution
imshafay: I am 6 ft 1 inch
teta_musha: wow, I'm glad I found this Basic Programming stream
imaginenation: https://pastebin.com/raw/RtbRZMMc
JUST_5HEAD: just bit shift 4Head @georgehotz
solomonspeare: Pog ? Pog ? Pog ?
imaginenation: damn
imshafay: I don't have that much ideal hacking skills
yrpsa: How tall is elon?🤔
kratosboii: PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG
imaginenation: hes gonna get it
dorkmo: Squid1 Squid2 Squid2 Squid2 Squid3 Squid2 Squid2 Squid2 Squid2 Squid4
zbrfey: good
sophisticatedgaming291a11: BlessRNG
MrYasser2194: Hello people!
gigafact: good work
imaginenation: real champ
murkythunder: <3
Klingenwetzer: morning? LUL
myaocat: Pog
sebiyy: what pills do you guys take modafinil ?
JUST_5HEAD: Kappa
FargioFarmani: yes sir
Klingenwetzer: We believe BlessRNG
solomonspeare: I BELIEVE PogChamp I BELIEVE PogChamp
ImNotTrolling: i dont
imaginenation: i used to take modafinil
dorkmo: TransgenderPride
imaginenation: but meh
andrestogas: Kappa Sure
JUST_5HEAD: I BELIEVE Kappa
imaginenation: now i just stick to nootropics
dorkmo: HolidaySanta
WEBCRAFT: Too much headache from mo
Mephisto_Mods: diazepram
imaginenation: yea modaf is too strong
imaginenation: for my taste
my_curiosity: It looks like a beautiful dancing area behind the chair.
dorkmo: MercyWing1 HolidaySanta MercyWing2
bsx1123: never give up, never surrender
FargioFarmani: don't forget to wash your hands bro @georgehotz
andrestogas: Basic programming LUL
Klingenwetzer: LUL We believe :)
Klingenwetzer: in you
chickenNwaffles723: 50mg is more than enough imo
sebiyy: his pee pee isnt dirty so he doesnt need to wash it
thirteenn: @georgehotz wait are you stil on the same problem?
imaginenation: I think the final hack would be approximating the subfacts
imaginenation: he said the exact thing
JUST_5HEAD: i think subfact is the problem
imaginenation: hack dem subfactsss
myaocat: maybe the sum
imaginenation: guys whats the next strream going to be like
yrpsa: Have you tried throwing money at the computer?
myaocat: because of line 49?
dorkmo: PowerUpL HolidaySanta PowerUpR
Klingenwetzer: water is the best
Lethly: what chair is that?
sebiyy: are you fucking hyperactive ?
saulgd: this tap water pleb LUL
imaginenation: sieve of eratos
thirteenn: @georgehotz what kind of tea do you drink?
imaginenation: try sieve
Klingenwetzer: LUL
7Locrian7: there's a leetcode question for that PogChamp
gigafact: math is hard
chickenNwaffles723: number theory oh no no no
saulgd: is that how americans pronounce sieve or is he just retarded LUL
MonkaSupreme: can you do network requests out of hackerrank? LUL
KingKewpa: is this what a job at google looks like
imaginenation: bro try tweaking them subfacts
zeroeagle1: back in Uni I had this assigment in asseembly
murkythunder: memoe Pepega
Lethly: what chair is hotz sitting in?
Klingenwetzer: memoization BibleThump
sebiyy: @KingKewpa no they just eat and drink check youtube life as a coder kappa
th3_maj0r: @georgehotz Didn't u work with primes years ago? I remmeber u wrote that u bought a pc with 64GB of RAM to work on the problem
imaginenation: sieve is log(log(n)) if i remember correctly
Saprykinkostja: chat, what task is this?
kanogger: small pp
imaginenation: lol he said pp
solomonspeare: @Saprykinkostja https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
yrpsa: Pp XD
Saprykinkostja: thanks
dorkmo: SSSsss SSSsss SSSsss SSSsss HolidaySanta SSSsss SSSsss SSSsss SSSsss
Causevd: I can solve this problem, hold my beer Keepo
murkythunder: I hate hackerrank/leetcde difficulty ratings :)
myaocat: what about this? https://www.hackerrank.com/challenges/leonardo-and-prime/forum/comments/207138
Cluwe: Euler's totient function here go
sebiyy: drinks the beer*
imaginenation: yo geo try hacking them subfacts you can make it constant time, since you have precached the facts
haircutjimmy: pep8
Klingenwetzer: does it make you feel bad? @murkythunder
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
imaginenation: ooo
JUST_5HEAD: that was fast
imaginenation: drumroll
Klingenwetzer: NotLikeThis
solomonspeare: @georgehotz hack the site so it gives all right Pog
sulozor: Pog
Lethly: what chair is @georgehotz sitting in?
gigafact: so close
myaocat: https://stackoverflow.com/questions/4643647/fast-prime-factorization-module
haircutjimmy: no vim?
JUST_5HEAD: its not the sieve
imaginenation: the last think is the subfacts with the EEEE
imaginenation: thing
yrpsa: Code.fastest
willgreen98: When did George start?
myaocat: https://www.hackerrank.com/challenges/leonardo-and-prime/forum/comments/207138 https://stackoverflow.com/questions/36522167/checking-primality-of-very-large-numbers-in-python
yrpsa: Fasterer
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
kniightt: idea PogChamp
7Locrian7: PogChamp ?
imaginenation: i know
murkythunder: ml
solomonspeare: PogChamp ASSEMBLY PogChamp ASSEMBLY
myaocat: GCD
imaginenation: POT
ForsakenReborn: PogU
Marshall3: PogChamp
dorkmo: boiiiiiiis
imaginenation: SMOKE
imaginenation: CRACK
FargioFarmani: a second latte
averagesizepens: me me
swftdev: c^w
SHB111: no
teta_musha: I do
Lethly: i know
imaginenation: lol
imshafay: leave the problem
Klingenwetzer: some sick design pattern forsenThink
umps: tree
Enmare: turn off stream?
sulozor: Code on VIM for speed PogChamp
myaocat: GCD........
umps: graph
abstractingagent: roll a fat joint and keep going
DrRobotvinnik: call Uber eats? @georgehotz
JUST_5HEAD: multitasking
imaginenation: E
solomonspeare: PogChamp ASSEMBLY
meridiansis: ADDERAL
imaginenation: EEE
Klingenwetzer: LUL
ArfArf: machine learning?
ForsakenReborn: i do :)
kniightt: POP PILLS
FargioFarmani: a second latte @georgehotz
haircutjimmy: bubble tea?
KingKewpa: fap?
Lethly: we're gonna rewrite it in rust
imaginenation: we are doing machine learning?
joker2k999: LUL
seacult: fap
cjocol2201: r u on drugs?
imaginenation: EEEE
samtheprogram: adrafinil
andrestogas: LUL
myaocat: Miller-Rabin's Primality test.
imaginenation: EE?
abstractingagent: LOL
myaocat: Miller-Rabin's Primality test. Miller-Rabin's Primality test. Miller-Rabin's Primality test. Miller-Rabin's Primality test.
swftdev: c !!!@#!@#!
7Locrian7: c PogChamp
ChimiFckingChanga: we are going to play rust
haircutjimmy: c!!!
ImNotTrolling: ECSTASY
imaginenation: ..........................
tanoshiizo: PogChamp
7Locrian7: oh FeelsBadMan
samtheprogram: EWWWWWW
KAZERKE: PogChamp
WEBCRAFT: Pog
ForsakenReborn: monkaS
asaalgk: Pog
dorkmo: Cccccccccccc
averagesizepens: damn
JUST_5HEAD: fuck
imshafay: Rewriting it in C
gigafact: cccc
kniightt: Groovy PogChamp
tanoshiizo: Real coding hours
CaptainAshtar: rewrite it in go
Klingenwetzer: IN C ! That was my idea from the beginning :( @georgehotz
imaginenation: why not write it in cython
andrestogas: Just ditch Python LUL
samtheprogram: NotLikeThis
WEBCRAFT: Use bitwise operators
meridiansis: those tabs...
solomonspeare: WHY NOT ASSEMBLY WHILE AT IT lol
Cluwe: import fractions def phi(n): amount = 0 for k in range(1, n 1): if fractions.gcd(n, k) == 1: amount = 1 return amount
imshafay: because of computational efficency
bsx1123: c
imshafay: Oh ma gazzz
ObscureCloud: what did i say about c earlier
ForsakenReborn: C monkaS
faxity: ithedaYAYA
trashtofu: This is gonna be fun ResidentSleeper
happens_: do rust, do rust PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: C 14 LUL
zbrfey: sievw of atkin?
myaocat: Just copy paste this: https://www.hackerrank.com/challenges/leonardo-and-prime/forum/comments/207138
myaocat: Just copy paste this: https://www.hackerrank.com/challenges/leonardo-and-prime/forum/comments/207138Just copy paste this: https://www.hackerrank.com/challenges/leonardo-and-prime/forum/comments/207138
zeroeagle1: zeroeagle1 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
voxelfox0125: Because C is Fast AF
KingKewpa: what language were you writing in?
sulozor: Copy pasting is boring man...
7Locrian7: ye
dorkmo: letsss goooooooo
imaginenation: that is write
imaginenation: right
CaptainAshtar: @myaocat why you are spoiling the fun?
imaginenation: LOL
dorkmo: Party1
imaginenation: monkaS
7Locrian7: no, that's read*
JUST_5HEAD: LMFAO
myaocat: std?
ForsakenReborn: C monkaS
tanoshiizo: his language doesn't have types LUL
averagesizepens: does english count as programming language?
imaginenation: you know I have a feeling that this is still not going to work
murkythunder: I spent years in uni and never figured out how to get length of array in c
spicydamsgaard420: Hey just came. whats going on?
imaginenation: LOL
josergdev: cya python magic
imaginenation: you just ask the array nicely
samtheprogram: aren't they just going to have different time limits for C ??
myaocat: @murkythunder strlen(arr) Kappa
swftdev: CoDeChEf StAtUs OwO
7Locrian7: @samtheprogram probably lol
JUST_5HEAD: @samtheprogram i think no
teta_musha: but doesn't slower languages have more time to execute the test cases?
Badges_OW: normally its same limit for all languages sam
sulozor: is it me or the camera sometimes drops FPS ?
meridiansis: use dark theme plz
trashtofu: int i tho
7Locrian7: oh, interesting
serhejenos: isnt there a golang option, May be try it?
solomonspeare: GOLANG Pog
myaocat: golang is slow
imaginenation: you know by the end of this geo would have proven P = NP
ViktorTV: math dot sqrf
kjanofficial: There are different time limits for different languages. You might be wasting your time. See https://www.hackerrank.com/environment
myaocat: why not c#?
voxelfox0125: Wait he knows C , python and ASM
samtheprogram: @Badges_OW innnnnteresting tyty
대리인: the lack of spaces is killing me
Klingenwetzer: gimme pure C BlessRNG
imaginenation: he knows that for sure
imaginenation: but sometimes C just works
JUST_5HEAD: just go for assembly bro Kappa
gigafact: There are different time limits for different languages. You might be wasting your time. See https://www.hackerrank.com/environment
solomonspeare: @georgehotz timeouts change from language to language https://www.hackerrank.com/environment
Klingenwetzer: u forgot semicolon at 17 @georgehotz
swftdev: yea, python3 usually gets a 5X limit in code challenges
jagger_rsw: not sure what n is but probably not big, just include all primes up to, say 1000000
imaginenation: I used to be a c fanboi
imaginenation: but meh
smurfd0: 'long' for big numbers
ObscureCloud: @imaginenation haha no since this is an NP complete problem
myaocat: that wont compile
JUST_5HEAD: @georgehotz read chat
samtheprogram: @swftdev 1 i would guess the same
imaginenation: this is a P problem bruh
kniightt: but now we're crack heads @imaginenation
7Locrian7: according to my googling, it seems diff languages have diff time limits
imshafay: semicolon ;
imshafay: ;
solomonspeare: @georgehotz timeouts change from language to language https://www.hackerrank.com/environment monkaS
imaginenation: well of course different langauges have diff time limits
MonkaSupreme: init with false
imaginenation: thats why i believe this isnt going to work
teta_musha: @georgehotz timeouts change from language to language https://www.hackerrank.com/environment
myaocat: why not store them as array? https://www.infoplease.com/math-science/mathematics/numbers-formulas/prime-numbers-between-1-and-1000
imaginenation: he is just trying his luck
myaocat: hack the system
smurfd0: http://www.cplusplus.com/reference/cmath/
imaginenation: was his subfacts still doing the recursion thinggy
swftdev: dynamic problems in python are rough, i agree c is the play
Siim135: @georgehotz j =i not j
solomonspeare: 1
Cluwe: there are other ways to write the prime counter! Google Euler's totient function
vmarkushin: sum from i =2?
Lethly: what level are you in classic @georgehotz ?
vmarkushin: =2*
imaginenation: classic minecraft?
Klingenwetzer: he probably means WoW
imaginenation: what a normie
Klingenwetzer: true
solomonspeare: lol
7Locrian7: no classic maplestoruy
imaginenation: LOL
myaocat: LUL
imaginenation: AHAHAH
solomonspeare: LULW
JUST_5HEAD: LMFAO
tanoshiizo: LUL
imaginenation: Kappa
swftdev: wow is all fun and games, till you want a mount
ForsakenReborn: BRUH
andrestogas: LUL
Adolfich: hahah lul
JUST_5HEAD: XAXAXAXAXA
myaocat: BUFFER OVERFLOW!
Klingenwetzer: LUL
CondomsWontFit: PogChamp
joker2k999: LUL
myaocat: HACK THE BUFFER
Cjiq: LULW
teta_musha: use long long unsigned ints
joker2k999: gdb bro
Klingenwetzer: LMFAO here we go python boys
imaginenation: LOL
cjocol2201: F
gigafact: c is hard
imaginenation: his stack is too big
chickenNwaffles723: doesn't hr have a vim mode?
7Locrian7: C syntax lole
Adolfich: noob
Misiaakoo: define size of array
Lethly: what chair are you using @georgehotz ?
solomonspeare: at least python had bignums PepeHands
Klingenwetzer: size of array
ForsakenReborn: compilation error :(
swftdev: "Ask you friends for help:"
Klingenwetzer: yea LUL
myaocat: maybe because of pp[] ?
Misiaakoo: int pp[size];
Klingenwetzer: arrays size are static :3
MonkaSupreme: your syntax is weak bro
yrpsa: Ask elon for help
7Locrian7: pp Kappa
Adolfich: pipi
Klingenwetzer: Clap
zeroeagle1: *
gigafact: lol yes ask on twitter for help
FargioFarmani: what is P and what is Q ?
myaocat: LUL
Klingenwetzer: LUL
JUST_5HEAD: LULW
imaginenation: i also forgot c since is started programming in python
myaocat: now in assembly!
MonkaSupreme: already timeout LUL
joehartshorn: first time ive caught one of these twitches, whats up!
swftdev: c 20 is soon
KyoshiDeath: maybe using std::for_each or transform could make thr code quicker
cmcintosh1981: morning
sulozor: I want to see some vim speed coding FeelsBadMan :(
imaginenation: isn
gouzzz: why the 123?
solomonspeare: CPP in 2K19 LUL
cmcintosh1981: man im going to have start code streaming :/
imaginenation: isn't his subfact doing some recursion thingy as well
cmcintosh1981: 600 folks
myaocat: why not store them as array? https://www.infoplease.com/math-science/mathematics/numbers-formulas/prime-numbers-between-1-and-1000
Klingenwetzer: C lowVe
zeroeagle1: zeroeagle1 converted from a Twitch Prime sub to a Tier 1 sub!
Agent_Random: @gouzzz because prime
gigafact: I wish Linus was here... He would optimize this too the moon
MonkaSupreme: gouzzz its in the question https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
imaginenation: guys am i wrong, is his subfact doing recursion or not
Lethly: what chair are you using @georgehotz ?
myaocat: @imaginenation it is
gouzzz: thx, i'll check it
Klingenwetzer: it is @imaginenation
swftdev: na linus would start a mail thread about him not doing charity
solomonspeare: @imaginenation it is calling itself lol so yeah
Klingenwetzer: with memoization
myaocat: we told you but you dont read chat
myaocat: import ai
andrestogas: Jebaited
solomonspeare: @myaocat lol
KyoshiDeath: use stl algorithms maybe ?
imaginenation: dude geo can you show us your subfact function
Badges_OW: is heap allocation faster than stack allocation?
KyoshiDeath: no
Meapzor: no
Klingenwetzer: semicolons NotLikeThis
Hamled: I suppose GMP is not available @georgehotz ?
sulozor: linting monkaS
Infinitelym: it's on the screen @imaginenation
Badges_OW: so he shouldnt be using new then right?
Lethly: what chair are you using @georgehotz ?
selcuktatar: CoolStoryBob
Cluwe: semicolons;;;;!!!!!
JUST_5HEAD: ;
imaginenation: dude
Meapzor: @Badges_OW it doesn't matter in applications like this
Misiaakoo: subfact[0] and semicons
gigafact: ;
jotembruv: anyone have a link to this? doubt i would solve it i just wanna see what it is
Cluwe: ;
Klingenwetzer: Triggering my OCD LUL
Klingenwetzer: ;-;
imaginenation: sorry i am blind
solomonspeare: @jotembruv https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
jotembruv: @solomonspeare thanks man
myaocat: look for the solution
ObscureCloud: cout << "He needs to chew more ice" << endl;
JUST_5HEAD: ;
7Locrian7: doesn't it also have to do with variable length arrays being only dynamic
radino321: hi im a noob ,whats he doing rn? hacking ? coding?
7Locrian7: hencenew
revolutionist123: Can someone expain to me what Q^-1 and P are in the problem?
imaginenation: dude subfact(n) = closest int ( fact(n) / e ) and since you already cached your fact
imaginenation: that should be const time
joehartshorn: 1 also noob wtf is going on rn
myaocat: ^ tht sounds smart
solomonspeare: @radino321 he's tryna solve this https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
solomonspeare: but it keeps givin timeout errors so
myaocat: c p
Klingenwetzer: coding = hacking @radino321
alaouiib: hey geohot.. first time i catch u online
Lethly: what chair are you using @georgehotz ?
voxelfox0125: Geo what way of learning applies to you. Jumping in head first and coming across problems, then researching and teaching yourself. Or learn as much as you can then tackle the problem?
imaginenation: yeah i am sure he hates e but i really dont see any harm in ttrying it out
timbo7io: you gotta rewrite it all in c
timbo7io: ;)
CaptainAshtar: python is good he will do it
Klingenwetzer: he is doing that atm
imaginenation: nah i am pretty sure the language isnt the problem here
pawerr: !keyboard
Lethly: !chair
imaginenation: he uses a das keyboard
imaginenation: all black keys
myaocat: is this faster algorithm? https://rosettacode.org/wiki/Miller–Rabin_primality_test#Python
KyoshiDeath: calculating factorials with recursive templates could be faster ?
pawerr: imaginenation do you know what switches?
imaginenation: rabin karp is a stochastic algoorithm
myaocat: https://rosettacode.org/wiki/Miller–Rabin_primality_test#C
KyoshiDeath: since everything is done compile time
imaginenation: its approximate
imaginenation: not exact
imaginenation: so i dont know if rabin karp would work
myaocat: he didnt try he is cconverting the python to c
shaniquaratchet: What nootropics do you use? @georgehotz
imaginenation: i dont think he would reveal that
imaginenation: but i am sure he uses some
sulozor: microdosing LSD PogChamp
imaginenation: LOL
ObscureCloud: sony nootropics
Usisuvach0: nootropics LUL @shaniquaratchet he is using weed
zeroeagle1: typedef ll unsigned long long
imaginenation: inootropics
SnakeOneMLG: @sulozor 🤔
Klingenwetzer: ull
imaginenation: !nootropics
Klingenwetzer: FeelsGoodMan
sulozor: @SnakeOneMLG monkaS you know me monkaS
324B2l: fameOkay
r3mote: Hello :)
ParkerBarwick: ParkerBarwick subscribed at Tier 1.
sulozor: do you think AI is getting back into the winter season? @georgehotz
CaptainAshtar: they keyboard is so ASMR
ObscureCloud: @revolutionist123 Those are partition functions P and Q of n
Klingenwetzer: THX SUB!~
dorkmo: Party1
marfinatorhx: im m
Lethly: what chair are you using @georgehotz ?
Sznurek066: Wait AI winter is coming FeelsBadMan
imaginenation: you see the only thing i believe that is left to optimize is the subfacts function with the use of E making it const time
marfinatorhx: i am netwatch, AI is fucking trash
imaginenation: i dont know anything else
myaocat: @Lethly pls subscribe and he will tell you
imaginenation: n = 1000000123
joehartshorn: ddos ai with meatspin link and ai spring will spring
solomonspeare: monkaS
imaginenation: segfault is the best
edargorter: Hey George, first time on stream from South Africa. Huge inspiration down south - keep it up!
Phott0n: nymnDab
swftdev: nervous without pdb
Klingenwetzer: segfault forsenHappy
imaginenation: yo dude try the subfacts hack with the exponent fam, no harm in trying it buddy
Klingenwetzer: forsen1
unctarheelss: can you do edit distance
myaocat: http://blog.softwx.net/2013/05/miller-rabin-primality-test-in-c.html
MonkaSupreme: use machine learning to give correct answers on the tests SeemsGood
imaginenation: i hate dynamic programming
Klingenwetzer: D:
imaginenation: that shit made me quit competitive programming
josergdev: c has type inference O.o?
myaocat: how do you know which code makes bottleneck ?
Klingenwetzer: dynamic programming lowVe
Cluwe: c error are the best Kappa
imaginenation: use a lot of comments @myaocat
ObscureCloud: Just get one of these geo https://tinyurl.com/yawnthisbadboy
unctarheelss: i have an onsite soon and i still dont know dp :(
CaptainAshtar: for pro hackers there is no pitstops
myaocat: @imaginenation what do you mean?
voxelfox0125: What happened to the CTF streams?
imaginenation: lol comment a lot of shits out and use custom inputs
Klingenwetzer: dynamic programming is 2nd semester stuff ResidentSleeper
zeroeagle1: n-k 1?
imaginenation: I have switched to machine learning world and i can testify that I am way happier than before my skin is clearer the air is fresher
myaocat: @imaginenation i mean how do you know which code fail the time test?
CaptainAshtar: killing it i'm doing right now ROS dynamic programing with C
dorkmo: MercyWing1 TheIlluminati MercyWing2
KingKewpa: wen hack complete?
Klingenwetzer: LUL @imaginenation that might be true though
ObscureCloud: C nibbas in the chat do 1
sulozor: its colder as well no? @imaginenation
imaginenation: it is true
imaginenation: machine learning is way easier than this competitive programming shit
solomonspeare: @myaocat I think he just commented out it in parts and see if it still gave a timeout
sulozor: well if you have 2 2080Ti sure LUL
joehartshorn: which CS course/ resource is best for a noob? i heard cs50 was good
imaginenation: I have a v100 dude
lithiumx4900: Just tuned in. Is he doing 4 at once?
imaginenation: and 4 x p100s
Klingenwetzer: makes you lose less hair @imaginenation LUL
sulozor: .............
imaginenation: i am still loosing hair though'
imaginenation: gotta fix that
ggwpl2p: malding?
WEBCRAFT: No just one challenge, trying in Python and C
imaginenation: balding
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink might be the genes or age
dorkmo: MercyWing1 HolidayTree MercyWing2
some_kind_of_speedrun: @joehartshorn MIT courses from edX
Klingenwetzer: forsenMald nymnSMALD
averagesizepens: malding programmer
myaocat: @solomonspeare yep so he assume the part of time consuming is finding prime number
imaginenation: can machine learning help me grow my hair back?
ObscureCloud: too many python ML betas around rn
joehartshorn: bless u @some_kind_of_speedrun
imaginenation: bro pytorch family here
imaginenation: that shit makes u alpha
sulozor: pytorch family here too
guccibruf: pytorch gang rise up
dorkmo: MercyWing1 BibleThump MercyWing2
imaginenation: OneHand
zeroeagle1: tf > pytorch
imaginenation: nah fuck tensorflow
ObscureCloud: python so gay even your go to distro is named anaconda
ObscureCloud: think about it
imaginenation: made by google shills
myaocat: i see the pain moving from python to c : no semi colons, types. Kappa
dorkmo: GayPride
Klingenwetzer: when I tilt when coding. I getting a hang to start brute forcing stuff via trial and error LUL
imaginenation: HAHAHA
imaginenation: he finally agreed
CaptainAshtar: :D
myaocat: in python you imagine you have infinte memory so you can write how you want
jotembruv: LUL
drparse: some people, when confronted with a problem think "I know, I'll use C ". now they have two problems
dorkmo: PowerUpL BibleThump PowerUpR
lithiumx4900: @WEBCRAFT thx
imaginenation: whn we have AGI, i would just ask it to solve(x)
CaptainAshtar: c sucks
WEBCRAFT: np
ggwpl2p: talk shit post fit
imaginenation: import AGI AGI.solve(x)
Klingenwetzer: it the other way around for me with python LUL always typing those semicolons
imaginenation: x = cancer
myaocat: that looks interesting problem!
sulozor: actually AGI is not far... we just need a good environment and use model based RL like world models and woops, done
myaocat: what is AGI?
sulozor: Artificial General Intelligence
imaginenation: artificial general intelligence
dorkmo: PowerUpL SabaPing PowerUpR
CaptainAshtar: wtf ...
imaginenation: its just that we dont have a use for quantum computers for AI yet
WEBCRAFT: It's about algorithm time efficiency not memory
myaocat: thx
gigafact: AGI = humans gone
imaginenation: nah dude once we have quantum neural networks its all over we can solve np hard problems in polynomial time
whichtom: that kind of statement stunts progress
CaptainAshtar: skynet terminator takes over
myaocat: np = p ?
ObscureCloud: Easier to go from c to python than reverse one of the reasons why we have so many shitty python coders around they're not passionate about CS
Klingenwetzer: compensating memory for time is what he is doing
myaocat: NP=P!??!!!!!!!!!!!!
Infinitelym: i've been reading chat and i forgot george is streaming lol
KingKewpa: is elon right about ai destroying us
whichtom: no
imaginenation: i really think that this was a bad judgement call on geos behalf
sulozor: computation isnt really a bottleneck for AGI atm @image
imaginenation: c aint gonna cut it
yrpsa: Elons on crack
zeroeagle1: maby AGI will simply sucuide itself since no point of existing?
myaocat: elon makes more money from selling hat then selling cars Kappa
Klingenwetzer: @ObscureCloud true LUL
voxelfox0125: Did anyone here learn C at this website? https://www.learncpp.com/
edargorter: np = p if and only if n = 1 or p = 0
JUST_5HEAD: elon LUL
whichtom: elon isn't an ai expert
Usisuvach0: elon tusk xD
imaginenation: LOL
dorkmo: MercyWing1 PunchTrees MercyWing2
imaginenation: i hope the AGI gets depressed
myaocat: @Usisuvach0 LUL
imaginenation: hell yeah
CaptainAshtar: the elon crazy elephant musk
joehartshorn: who do we trust about AI? Sama?
ObscureCloud: did you guys see elon and the alibaba chinese guy interview?
Usisuvach0: elon open ai dota
EkkoTheUnforgiven: whats the problem he's solving?
imaginenation: man i srsly wished he did the e trick
solomonspeare: @EkkoTheUnforgiven https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
CaptainAshtar: elon is spending money where he wants to shine most
myaocat: e trick?
gigafact: that china elon interview was hilarious
Klingenwetzer: np geo
sulozor: LUL I joined the ship halfway, I was lost instantly
imaginenation: yo geo can you upload your solution
myaocat: imagine he will make the chat to subs only Kappa
edargorter: @EkkoTheUnforgiven Agreed, what is he solving?
joehartshorn: it was fuckin so bad, jack ma is a tool lol
imaginenation: dude you can make your subfacts faster
yrpsa: Jack ma got pwned
imaginenation: GEEEEEEEEEO
imaginenation: jack ma i9s a dumbass
ObscureCloud: @voxelfox0125 if you're a noob start here https://isocpp.org/get-started http://www.learncpp.com/ http://www.cplusplus.com/doc/tutorial/
JUST_5HEAD: n&1 ?
solomonspeare: @imaginenation is that the problem tho?
dorkmo: BrokeBack FBCatch DoritosChip
Deathbladein: Do you prefer programming on Mac, Linux, or Windows?
imaginenation: it was actually painful to hear jack ma talk
sulozor: programming on windows pepeLaugh
ancientchineseelder: hey geo can you solve this in scratch please
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink he is coding at win10 atm
WEBCRAFT: I use window terminal with ubuntu
WEBCRAFT: not half bad
gigafact: he is coding on chrome atm
Jeppelelle: Went away for 8 hours so whats up? Is he still on prob 239?
JUST_5HEAD: knew it
Klingenwetzer: LUL
ObscureCloud: Jack ma is like the non tech manager asking you to get it done by monday
imshafay: VIMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMM
KannaKim: OMEGALUL
myaocat: we have updated your system, this computer needs to restart! we will restart your computer in 10 sec makes sure you close everything LUL
some_kind_of_speedrun: he is coding at virtual env
imaginenation: LOL
Klingenwetzer: nice naming FeelsGoodMan
KannaKim: k well :(
dorkmo: PowerUpL PanicVis PowerUpR
imaginenation: can we have some F's in chat boys
gigafact: grounding issue?
imshafay: <3
rkxbz: hi, im first time on the stream
JUST_5HEAD: PowerUpL TheIlluminati PowerUpR
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink
joehartshorn: yeah no wonder they never gave jack ma that job at KFC, id short alibaba if the chinese govt didnt back him lol
Usisuvach0: ask your friend to help @georgehotz :)
KannaKim: Pog
myaocat: Pog
whichtom: oh shit
JustAnotherSillyBot: PogU
Klingenwetzer: Jebaited
gigafact: swowow
some_kind_of_speedrun: PogChamp
imaginenation: lmao
Phott0n: PogChamp
balkibee: Pog
Klingenwetzer: Jebaited LUL
imaginenation: nah
myaocat: Now assembly? Or Rust?
KannaKim: few more way to go
gigafact: damn skills
Klingenwetzer: OH NO NO NO forsenKek
KannaKim: monkaW
imaginenation: this aint gonna work
dorkmo: lettttsssss goooooooOOooo
dunehazard: C Pog
324B2l: fameHyperS
kiikoh: TOO SLOW
sulozor: Rust PogChamp
imaginenation: its still slow
hashcoder: PeoplesChamp
fear_ep: assembly lol
JustAnotherSillyBot: HahA
imaginenation: its not hte language
ancientchineseelder: piss asmr
rkxbz: what is he doing&
Infinitelym: the ones that are wrong here are the exact same ones that were wrong using python
rkxbz: ?
KingKewpa: pissing
joehartshorn: you can piss in the cloud, amazing
tanoshiizo: Kreygasm
dunehazard: lmao
voxelfox0125: @ObscureCloud thanks i am learning at learncpp currently im on chapter 3 (debugging) but i did read a book called "Learning c through Game programming" . Thanks for the other 2 sites.
Klingenwetzer: @imaginenation believe in the power of C
imaginenation: LKOL
hashcoder: найс ссыт чел)
EkkoTheUnforgiven: ITS DP TIME
radino321: nice mic can hear everything
myaocat: @rkxbz https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
guccibruf: washed hands PogChamp
yrpsa: This is exciting
myaocat: Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly Assembly
geochill1: geochill1 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
imaginenation: SUBFACT can be optimized
unctarheelss: DP DP DP
EkkoTheUnforgiven: DYNAMIC PROGRAMMING
dorkmo: Party1
rkxbz: @myaocat thanks
ObscureCloud: it's actually strange to me how jack ma achieved his position given his IQ he must have been surrounded by morally ethical friends that were engineers not interested about the business social side of operation
KannaKim: monkaW
Klingenwetzer: can you use some openMP in this problem? forsenThink Keepo jk just joking
Klingenwetzer: not gonna work
Cluwe: @georgehotz if you solve this you will get my twitch prime subscription
Klingenwetzer: or can you forsenThink
Michael31415926535: wow I've actually caught you live LUL
imaginenation: subfact(n) = round( fact(n) /e )
imaginenation: try that fam
timbo7io: HeyGuys BibleThump WutFace WutFace
edargorter: Ma at least recognises the distinction between the human creative drive and emulation
rkxbz: anyone watching ufc242?
Klingenwetzer: #pragma omp parallel for BlessRNG
imaginenation: link
josergdev: "Ok, let's dp it in assembly"
imaginenation: please
unctarheelss: DP
myaocat: someone recommend any youtube channels that teach this or articles series?
rkxbz: russian is okay?
imaginenation: subfact(n) = round( fact(n) /e )
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Klingenwetzer: probably not
EkkoTheUnforgiven: fun fact there is a bitshift formula for calculating primes
myaocat: can you try that? https://www.hackerrank.com/challenges/leonardo-and-prime/forum/comments/207138
ivylions: always prefer articles, can do at your own speed, videos are hit or miss
joehartshorn: whos a trustworthy person to listen to about AGI? Sam A?
zeroeagle1: import multiprocessing as mp mp.cpu_count()
sulozor: Nick Bolstrom not too bad
Klingenwetzer: LUL
whichtom: LUL
sulozor: LUL
zbrfey: J. Carmack and Demis Hassabis
joehartshorn: looool not sam then
sulozor: Open AI Charter PogChamp
sulozor: Kapp
Infinitelym: HE GOT CASE 26
timbo7io: gotta google that
joehartshorn: noted, thanks hotz
Klingenwetzer: yeah
quezod: god to know hotz, thanks
quezod: yeah you're right
EkkoTheUnforgiven: LETS CREATE A LOOKUP ARRAY Kapp
timbo7io: hahaha
timbo7io: true that
ObscureCloud: Rather hang with assholes
quezod: trying not to be one is hard sometimes
zbrfey: need better AI Index (performace metrics).. EFF has only "attempt" i have found
Klingenwetzer: they are just milking the "open" notation
imaginenation: im an asshole
geochill1: Pround EON #5352 owner here
dorkmo: MercyWing1 DxCat MercyWing2
myaocat: you can create a self driving car in month but solving a time problem you cant.
critical_section: maybe bitshifting ?
imaginenation: subfact(n) = round( fact(n) /e ) try it for the memes
nicetool: You ever use Go at all? Use cases for it?
Michael31415926535: what language is this?
tooinsaneee: big fan love watching you code 😇😂
andrestogas: Just solve it 4Head
myaocat: @Michael31415926535 c
bulbaz0r: Can you post your code? I missed the last couple hours
balkibee: yagutSmart
Klingenwetzer: Google DeepMind BlessRNG
imshafay: I think its HYPE as well
JustAnotherSillyBot: @georgehotz make it recursive SeemsGodd
Klingenwetzer: now they use StarCraft 2
ObscureCloud: get your employment coats it's AI winter
McBainTS: @georgehotz Have you tried using deep learning for this problem to make it faster?
edargorter: @georgehotz you should check out the game "Tak" and then train an ann to play it...
Cluwe: one somehow has to work with the modulus earlier
KyoshiDeath: hardcode these factorials :p
Klingenwetzer: LUL
JUST_5HEAD: LMAO
joehartshorn: lol
xidarul: @georgehotz what you think about the future of web development technologies?
Klingenwetzer: hard code the primes
Klingenwetzer: Keepo
FargioFarmani: best idea yet
EkkoTheUnforgiven: FACTORIAL WITH BITSHIFTING
unctarheelss: use dp
sulozor: I truly believe we have the algorithms for AGI... It's just that we don't have the environment in order to train one (except real life, but too costly LUL)
critical_section: @georgehotz bitshifting i thinks the way. games do it
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink
myaocat: https://discuss.codechef.com/t/algorithm-to-find-inverse-modulo-m/344/3 ?
7Locrian7: PogChamp ?
quezod: @sulozor sims too weak?
Klingenwetzer: LUL
EkkoTheUnforgiven: YOINK TriHard my code now
mikey9988: copy code EZ
Klingenwetzer: delting old code NotLikeThis
unctarheelss: rEaL engIneER
geochill1: To chat at you about comma, do we only do that on youtube live videos? Don't want to crash this party
ggtom: sulozor what agi bro
Klingenwetzer: NOO NotLikeThis
EkkoTheUnforgiven: CTRL Z TIME
JustAnotherSillyBot: @EkkoTheUnforgiven not in a browser lul
Klingenwetzer: can you in that browser though?
gigafact: @geochill1 yes
sulozor: well if you want to reproduce "human intelligence" you have to be able to simulate the world it was developed in, aka real life @quezod which is way too expensive atm
Klingenwetzer: or on that site I should say
voxelfox0125: Copy it into a C compiler to see the compile times.
geochill1: Thanks gigafact
Deathbladein: What is your preferred operating system for programming?
dorkmo: MercyWing1 TPFufun MercyWing2
EkkoTheUnforgiven: @JustAnotherSillyBot it can be overidden to work :)
zeroeagle1: why the N-2?
myaocat: https://stackoverflow.com/questions/43605542/how-to-find-modular-multiplicative-inverse-in-c
dorkmo: PowerUpL HolidaySanta FBtouchdown PowerUpR
benjaminr42: int,
fear_ep: overflow
benjaminr42: vs unsigned long long
ObscureCloud: https://pst.klgrth.io/paste/xhddxe6498p8t6k99o97jz4n if our n was < 100
edargorter: You guys seen this? https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fast_inverse_square_root
JUST_5HEAD: ll
thenomadplayer: YO YO YO BRO
myaocat: @ObscureCloud ip logger?
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
gigafact: this stream is getting long already 6GB... it's going to take a while to upload and process on youtube :/
Klingenwetzer: Click it forsenO
bulbaz0r: what is ll?
ObscureCloud: @myaocat if i wanted toip log you i'd say geo hot girlfriend leaked on twitter
Klingenwetzer: NotLikeThis
Klingenwetzer: almost 5 hours on this
sulozor: 1 timeout probably
JUST_5HEAD: @bulbaz0r unsigned long long, type definition
bulbaz0r: @JUST_5HEAD gotchya thanks
joehartshorn: geohot girlfriend is AI and hes not sharing cuz AGI got a booty
chexmixz: Blizzard NA servers getting ddos plz send help
gigafact: wiki got ddosed so stupid
gigafact: who would ddos wiki?
dunehazard: The problem is the color scheme
Klingenwetzer: LUL
ancientchineseelder: wow classic gettin ddosed today too
murkythunder: buy more time with a premium subscription
unctarheelss: time AI
xidarul: ddos in 2019 LUL
gigafact: ddos = brute force
JUST_5HEAD: do some custom test inputs with weird shit too see if you timeout
ObscureCloud: geohot signing up to remedial math classesafter this
averagesizepens: is he malding yet?
edargorter: Using recursive NCr?
Phott0n: @averagesizepens nymnSMALD nymnSMALD
Klingenwetzer: LUL forsenMald
myaocat: open issue!
Klingenwetzer: nice I'm watching somebody code instead of coding myself LUL killing any productivity out of myself rn
Cluwe: use the modulus in the ncr
timbo7io: lol
Cluwe: and in the factorial use the modulus
myaocat: use inline assembly
geochill1: Chill out man
timbo7io: you got this
smurfd0: you have some recursive thing there, not sure if thats faster or slower... https://rosettacode.org/wiki/Modular_inverse#C.2B.2B
myaocat: it will make it faster
samtheprogram: memoize
timbo7io: i believeeeeeeeeeee
Klingenwetzer: LUL myaocat
JUST_5HEAD: go bitshift LUL
ObscureCloud: @Klingenwetzer as if you wouldn't be looking at memes on twitter if geohot wasn't streaming
geochill1: jchillin
Misiaakoo: nested for LUL
myaocat: inline assembly will make it faster! LETS GO HYPE
Deathbladein: Next problem
KyoshiDeath: does the website compile with -O3 ?
edargorter: insert a bunch of gotos?
JUST_5HEAD: LMFAO
ggtom: LULW
lucas9o: LUL
dunehazard: LMAO
some_kind_of_speedrun: PogChamp
myaocat: hype
geochill1: #Operation GeoChill
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink @ObscureCloud looking at twitter for memes. also only if I'm super bored 👀
Klingenwetzer: forsenS
myaocat: maybe the headers makes it slower? types slow? so convert from long to int?
andrestogas: LUL
ObscureCloud: TheIlluminati
imaginenation: yeah check the loeaderboard dude
zeroeagle1: is it possible long long takes more instructions to load into cpu?
Klingenwetzer: forsenS he is getting insane
catacata92: you can check who solved it
FargioFarmani: let's call it a day @georgehotz
ObscureCloud: aaron chen did
f00z: it only has 9 100.0 scores
subzik_: KEKW
Andemannen: do you have a job? @georgehotz
KyoshiDeath: simd instructions ftw
Klingenwetzer: @ObscureCloud you followed pokimane WutFace
Crameleon_: Hi @takizz
Crameleon_: :)
JUST_5HEAD: oh shit
Klingenwetzer: forsenX WutFace
f00z: you're rank 11 on this problem @georgehotz on the Leaderboard tab
Crameleon_: xqcDab
th3_maj0r: @f00z full time influncer on instagram
gigafact: link to learderboard
StrippyDrippY: lirikHMM
samtheprogram: so only 9 people have solved it?
andrestogas: BabyRage unfair
imaginenation: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/leaderboard
teta_musha: can't you precache the values once and use for every test case?
f00z: yep @samtheprogram
UniversalGeneve: would vectorizing help anywhere?
gigafact: geohotjunk haha
ggtom: UniversalGeneve i dont think ur allowed to use vector libraries
gigafact: best name lolđ
imaginenation: am i insane for suggesting the e solution for subfacts
Crameleon_: Hi @georgehotz :)
UniversalGeneve: ah i see.
Misiaakoo: do you srly need so much for loops?
Klingenwetzer: HEH the chinese is on rank 1 forsenS
myaocat: LUL
ggtom: LULW
ObscureCloud: @Klingenwetzer never watched her stream i think someone linked it on discord made a meme about it
dunehazard: LUL
ssh4422: lol
EkkoTheUnforgiven: LOL
JUST_5HEAD: lol
Crypod: monkaS
Klingenwetzer: LUL @ObscureCloud okay
FadezzHD: saved
7Locrian7: just look at vod for restoration :)
timbo7io: Haha
tacorising3: LUL
asaalgk: code it in assembly
josergdev: LUL
andrestogas: Saved
Klingenwetzer: LMAO
timbo7io: I love c
Crameleon_: Code it in binary :)
ObscureCloud: i heard her StarCraft 2 streams are great wink wonk
imaginenation: WELL
Klingenwetzer: use c rephtoSmile
geochill1: Make typing chill
imaginenation: i dont really think its about the language
Klingenwetzer: I like C rephtoSmile
UNOlover68: use fortran 4head
korede360: Any real reason you switched to Windows?
imaginenation: and you know it geo
timbo7io: They dont even show you the cases man
Klingenwetzer: FORTRAN forsenKek
Lethly: rewrite in rust
Klingenwetzer: here we go
mikey9988: LUL
Fat_Fart_9000: C is fine
trashtofu: gonna do C in uni soon rajjHAA
timbo7io: Do it in julia
Phott0n: I only use machine code :)
imaginenation: wait why doesnt he precache the subfacts as well
timbo7io: Or mathmatica
timbo7io: PrimeUWot
SublimeOtal: i can handle this easy
Klingenwetzer: use fancy keywords for the compiler :3
imaginenation: oh he has
myaocat: would you really need to learn this for job interview? is it really relevant for nowadays with all the libraries?
Andemannen: pp big pepelaugh
Cluwe: you already use the modulus 10^9 123 in the ncr and factorial right?
Klingenwetzer: forsenH
J3rwin: @myaocat no
Klingenwetzer: #define LUL
trashtofu: @myaocat This problem is a bit extreme for an interview environment LUL
0xBADBADBAD: the plus plus is already in the name comeon!
serhejenos: pp big
Misiaakoo: merge some of for loops
Phott0n: Python is faster Kappa
Lethly: rewrite in rust
JUST_5HEAD: lol
myaocat: python is slowerr
myaocat: use inline assembly
myaocat: pls
imaginenation: i feel bad that no one has my back with the subfacts : BibleThump :
MachoBeet: faster or slower depends on the purpose
crisofilaxx: it shouldnt matter which language you use. hacker rank does testcases do its solvable ib each language
JUST_5HEAD: @imaginenation i do
revolutionist123: @georgehotz can u explain the problem's solution?
asaalgk: whats the point of doing project euler problems on another site
imaginenation: thanks man you the real G @JUST_5HEAD
Infinitelym: @imaginenation I don't understand the problem enough to have your back :/
imaginenation: lol
Cluwe: eulers totient algorithm give a faster P i think
gigafact: it's raining here
imaginenation: he is using recursion for subfacts what i am suggesting is using an approximation
7Locrian7: those newlines take up too much time to process
7Locrian7: :)
imaginenation: which is a really good approx
myaocat: @asaalgk this website checks how long it takes for the code execute but in euler you just know if you solve it or not
EkkoTheUnforgiven: GOD
timbo7io: i know
timbo7io: maybe
smurfd0: cmight be a liiitle faster, but you might get screwed on how to solve the big numbers? is u long long there?
imaginenation: nah prime sieve is pretty fast
joehartshorn: whoever recommended me that MIT course on Edx, thank you, I was thinking of learning python once i got some cs grounding
trashtofu: this is rocket science, I would give up in like 20 mins trying to solve this
Misiaakoo: merge for loops
ObscureCloud: https://twitter.com/WasntMeBuddy/status/1167878041889984517 geohot after this hot problem
amaramee1: c
imaginenation: you can't really go faster than eratosthenes sieve
timbo7io: did you try to cache it? pre computed results?
Klingenwetzer: approximation?
EkkoTheUnforgiven: U CALCULATE SQRT EVERY ITERATION 2ND INNER FOR
timbo7io: memozation
asaalgk: you just need to be a nerd and know the tricks
dorkmo: how many primes are there to 10mil?
myaocat: @EkkoTheUnforgiven noice
imaginenation: pp
timbo7io: ya
Lethly: rust
imaginenation: if pp == bitg
Phott0n: my pp hard
imaginenation: big
teta_musha: pipi
Klingenwetzer: forsenL
JUST_5HEAD: stop recalculate shit and save them just once @georgehotz
myaocat: HYPE
teta_musha: then break!
drparse: LUL
myaocat: 1 minute break
trashtofu: Capital p Kreygasm
timbo7io: ya hashset check before compute
gigafact: oh no
Klingenwetzer: LUL
timbo7io: idk
timbo7io: haha
Infinitelym: read chat for 1 minute george
7Locrian7: FeelsBadMan
asaalgk: run an ad
imaginenation: geo really hates me right
myaocat: everyone follow geohot instagram
7Locrian7: hi
EkkoTheUnforgiven: 2nd inner for you make sqrt calculation every itteration
Infinitelym: yep @imaginenation
imaginenation: figured
gusfrehse: oh god you're still in the same problem
bosapiutsa: have sex
JUST_5HEAD: well..
myaocat: 1 minute ads your instagram page!
FargioFarmani: show us your crin
Cluwe: google eulers totient function for the algorithm
gigafact: check https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/leaderboard
FargioFarmani: *crib
Klingenwetzer: COMPILER PLS SAVE US BlessRNG
joehartshorn: george your infinity pool instagram influencer shit is legendary, thank you for that
Misiaakoo: 41-46 can be one loop
imaginenation: nah dude
Klingenwetzer: Ignore chat LUL
Lethly: rewrite in rust while you wait
Phott0n: Jebaited
7Locrian7: KappaPride
imaginenation: LOL
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
0xBADBADBAD: Kappa
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
imaginenation: he is reading the wrong parts
Fat_Fart_9000: LUL
oMythra: POG
Phott0n: PogChamp
7Locrian7: PogChamp
StrippyDrippY: LUL
tanoshiizo: PogChamp
Phott0n: nymnPog
Fat_Fart_9000: Pog
UNOlover68: Pog
EkkoTheUnforgiven: CALLED IT
ProfessorMagikarp0: PogChamp
Jewishrambo: Lol
imaginenation: damn
revolutionist123: PogChamp
myaocat: @imaginenation whats wrong?
Misiaakoo: PogChamp
KingKewpa: wow pp=big worked?
Klingenwetzer: @imaginenation sure Kappa
trashtofu: PogU
the12eaz: LUL LUL
Phott0n: if pp = hard
FadezzHD: PogChamp
some_kind_of_speedrun: PogChamp
imaginenation: no i meant wrong parts of what i typed here in the chat before
imaginenation: dude
dorkmo: dorkmo gifted a Tier 1 sub to EkkoTheUnforgiven! This is their first Gift Sub in the channel!
oMythra: C the GOAT lang!
imaginenation: that was a joke LOL
CHENLOLA: PogChamp
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
Klingenwetzer: can't we give the compiler some flags? :C
0xBADBADBAD: LUL
sulozor: LUL
trashtofu: Kappa
gusfrehse: LULW
UNOlover68: LUL
imaginenation: ....
StrippyDrippY: give imaginenation a medal
EkkoTheUnforgiven: thank you boi <3
Klingenwetzer: bro :)
andrestogas: LUL
sulozor: just type it again @imaginenation
joehartshorn: lmao
imaginenation: sigh
myaocat: @imaginenation do you mean rewrite algorithms?
imaginenation: no i meant
myaocat: @imaginenation :(
imaginenation: the subfactorials
piece_drake_azur: pp haha so funnay 4Head
imaginenation: try changing the subfactorials, he is doing recursion there
sulozor: precache sqrt(n) PogChamp
ObscureCloud: https://pastebin.com/kdm76FPW similar problem
imaginenation: he can try using the approximation formula there
myaocat: is this website better than leetcode?
cjocol2201: say sike right now
trashtofu: So you rewrote it in C so it would execute faster?
Infinitelym: @imaginenation u r trying so hard lul
A_McQueen: change i to i makes is also a little faster
Klingenwetzer: approximation !
ObscureCloud: @georgehotz https://pastebin.com/kdm76FPW
dontbeameme: Holy shit he is still going ____👃🏽
UniversalGeneve: sorry a bit late on the stream, what is george trying to accomplish with the code?
Moe_Bradberry: what is he coding? i have no knowlege of this btw
mondeverest: !uptime
Klingenwetzer: just Pastebins LUL everywhere
Misiaakoo: 41-46 can be one loop, calculate condition of loop before entering
imaginenation: Geo try changing the subfactorial computation
gigafact: George attracts great people
sM4rT3r: A french guy solved it with python
gorgai: Just joined, what's the problem you are facing?
ObscureCloud: a russian did with c
imaginenation: subfact(n)= round(fact(n)/e)
dontbeameme: French are super smart
trashtofu: Only the real ones are in the chat Kappa
oMythra: Russian dudes snappin
dontbeameme: Russians super smart too
joehartshorn: only geohotz twitchies have long dicks
cjocol2201: F
Lazylion2: im real MrDestructoid
ObscureCloud: @dontbeameme merci beaucoup
myaocat: french accent is super funny
Klingenwetzer: use disassembler and optimize the assembly code Kappa
KingKewpa: solve it george, make us americans proud
piece_drake_azur: KKona
Klingenwetzer: MURICAN KKona
joehartshorn: lmao
Phott0n: KKona
dotmops: KKona
Cluwe: why exactly do you have to use infact?
sulozor: and oil ofc
revolutionist123: KKona
imaginenation: and Iraq wars
asaalgk: based
Xandoo: LUL LUL
trashtofu: KKona
mikey9988: KKona
TheZombieKillerWhale: KKona
Klingenwetzer: BIG MAC HELL YEAH KKona
woogio: AND C KKona
gusfrehse: KKona
oMythra: Do it for Murica George
dontbeameme: America 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸
andrestogas: KKonLUL
McBainTS: Does it count compile time in the time limit?
nanodanger7: @georgehotz wow tomorrow will be my 16th month sub anniversary :D
myaocat: america getting best by removing the encryption and doing surveillance on the citizens like china :(
Klingenwetzer: We germans use assembly DatSheffy
UniversalGeneve: UniversalGeneve is gifting 2 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 2 in the channel!
UniversalGeneve: UniversalGeneve gifted a Tier 1 sub to Rtc_ti5!
UniversalGeneve: UniversalGeneve gifted a Tier 1 sub to eynalhurts!
imaginenation: POG
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
myaocat: POG
Klingenwetzer: Never lucky BibleThump
Klingenwetzer: FeelsBadMan
spitza: can anyone llink the hackerrank page for this problem?
MatiGoG: dodge EZ
ObscureCloud: America CS going down with new immigration laws
piece_drake_azur: got one Pog
JUST_5HEAD: EZ DODGE
gusfrehse: dodged
eynalhurts: @UniversalGeneve Thanks for the gift sub!
dotmops: KKona french usually give up midway 🏳️
ObscureCloud: all your american "german russian chinese etc" guys leaving
serhejenos: POG
dontbeameme: @dotmops lolol
myaocat: @Klingenwetzer and soaps
sulozor: :rage: @dotmops
imaginenation: subfact(n)= round(fact(n)/e) you already have facts precached right?
piece_drake_azur: just make it faster 4Head
imaginenation: man geoooo
imaginenation: ...
Klingenwetzer: JUST 4Head
imaginenation: imm KMS
JUST_5HEAD: @imaginenation he is not gonna read it ever bro LOL
imaginenation: i feel that
MatiGoG: just rewrite it to rust 4HEad
Klingenwetzer: LUL relax imaginenation
eynalhurts: @imaginenation He saw your name and turned around
imaginenation: LOL
Klingenwetzer: Fame BlessRNG
imaginenation: okay then
joehartshorn: that chair is a herman miller for that dude who was asking a million times
timbo7io: we love you
catacata92: "medium" problem
dontbeameme: Break something geo it’s so frustrating 😡
imaginenation: onnit
piece_drake_azur: PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: optimize the loop (:
gigafact: remember guys this is warm up
JUST_5HEAD: slam the desk 😡
andrestogas: Just make it faster 4Head
ObscureCloud: warm up "basic programming"
timbo7io: i want your chair
timbo7io: memozation
ObscureCloud: can't wait for the actual game
sulozor: what is after the warm up btw?
janchomath: write inline ll power()
kornflexx: Donate them money for better CPUs Kappa
gt853_tv: power(x, y, p) does what exactly?
Klingenwetzer: LUL
smurfd0: change the while to a forloop?
Chocho1984: Hello from France
IndoPridePinoy: chat figured it out. buy a better computer
joehartshorn: https://www.hermanmiller.com/en_gb/products/seating/office-chairs/sayl-chairs/ @timbo7io
UNOlover68: compiler is biased to europeans
dinomdanom: hi george
Klingenwetzer: branch misspredicts LUL
markovchain21: can you stop the time the loop takes? just to get an idea of what we are talking here? @georgehotz
piece_drake_azur: give up now BibleThump
ObscureCloud: int pp [BIG}
smth68: try restarting the router or the pc it would work
janchomath: write inline ll power(){}
Shibby834: just close some of those chrome tabs and It will run faster Kappa
Cluwe: why exactly do we need infact?
Hooterrr: hi, what we doing?
Klingenwetzer: he chuckeled PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: We did it guys
ObscureCloud: @Shibby834 chrome legit crypto mining us
ObscureCloud: lmao
Klingenwetzer: nymnOkay
Klingenwetzer: thats why I don't use chrome rephtoSmile
jagger_rsw: maybe you can use some __builtin_<findfirstbitset>() to speed up your power
CaptainAshtar: @Shibby834 the compiler is not on his computer so it doesn't matter if he is using chrome or not
MrPapillon_: Put return everywhere and it will run faster.
UNOlover68: too much whitespace => sloww
UNOlover68: Kappa
zgamer0123: Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa
myaocat: array size?
ISD_Schogol: o7
Klingenwetzer: @CaptainAshtar wait really? :) would have never thought
piece_drake_azur: golden Kappa check
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Klingenwetzer: golden Kappa check
sulozor: you can assign x and y inside the while ?
janchomath: write inline power(ll x,ll t,ll p)
joehartshorn: just write code on one line for speed and ease
joehartshorn: lmao
dorkmo: MercyWing1 PanicVis MercyWing2
samtheprogram: inline might help
CaptainAshtar: @Klingenwetzer what do you mean
myaocat: rip
dontbeameme: Clip it
janchomath: you can use some pragmas too
cjocol2201: F
ISD_Schogol: Have you guys seen the new PowerToys tool from microsoft? you can create your own zones where and how apps can/should dock <3
dontbeameme: N/m
myaocat: LUL
Klingenwetzer: LUL
some_kind_of_speedrun: TriHard
dennjs: geo getting swated
TonyShart: hi geo i saw u on lex. good stuff.
piece_drake_azur: try c 23 PogChamp
jirikmarik: run monkaS
foxubu: lol
dorkmo: cops cops cops
whichtom: wtf is happening outside
TheZombieKillerWhale: monkaS
alphasweetpea: Someones having a bad day outside ur place
UniversalGeneve: PoPo
cjocol2201: BibleThump
joehartshorn: NO COPS IN THE CLOUD
Quev1337: OhMyDog
Klingenwetzer: try the #pragma omp thing for funzies LUL
kornflexx: I mean 14 is bigger than 0...
dontbeameme: 🔴🔵🔴🔵🔴🔵🔴🔵
josergdev: c 14 maybe has more limit time
FadezzHD: PoPo is coming
smth68: monkaS run barry
revolutionist123: monkaS
myaocat: sirens make people freak out!
cjocol2201: are u in the cloud?
piece_drake_azur: 🔫 TriHard
Chocho1984: stop george! cops are coming for u
dorkmo: shutting down some street racing
Klingenwetzer: G OMEGALUL
DelayedSwagger: geo can you recommend a beginner any books?
gt853_tv: write it in R
zeroeagle1: c 14 was going too fast
ObscureCloud: who can run faster geohot'sloop or the guy outside chased by cops
DelayedSwagger: or ayone
gt853_tv: R would be easy
woogio: G LUL
Lethly: rewrite it in rust
janchomath: write some inlines and
ottizy: no optimizer flags? monkaS
mehi9h: nah go is slower
gt853_tv: python and R get 10 seconds
murkythunder: peole who use go have a lil brain delay so they give extra time
dorkmo: Google paying to host hackersite
Misiaakoo: make it multi threaded LUL
KingKewpa: i think the problem is you need another piss break
Klingenwetzer: #pragma omp parallel for rephtoSmile
Klingenwetzer: Kappa
myaocat: conclusion, writing the same code in c didn't help FailFish
subzik_: i mean, ya know ...
JUST_5HEAD: thats it
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Misiaakoo: finally
myaocat: geohot logic: adding code reduce time
janchomath: for(int j= i * i; j<=n; j =i)p[[i] = 0;
MrPapillon_: No SSE?
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp
janchomath: if(pp[i] == 1) for(int j= i * i; j<=n; j =i)p[[i] = 0;
piece_drake_azur: PogChamp
gigafact: wow close
Phott0n: PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
LordDaniel09: really lol
timbo7io: fuck you so close
revolutionist123: PogChamp
jemoetahh: pp Kappa
zeroeagle1: save that code
spanilith: 2.05 seconds
dontbeameme: Nice
MaamPlsMarryMe: based
gt853_tv: see if you can combine other loops as well
janchomath: write fuckin i*i instead of 2*i
ObscureCloud: we're close boys edging this problemto the end
dontbeameme: Let’s get it
cjocol2201: Go george go!
MrPapillon_: I guess SSE is forbidden, because the code looks ike it could be good for SSE.
Klingenwetzer: edging 👀
JUST_5HEAD: bitmask
janchomath: its really easy
cjocol2201: is this going to be on youtube?
ObscureCloud: @Klingenwetzer uh oh Kappa
LaytonioSantos: move sqrt out of loop
KyoshiDeath: improve cache locality by storing subfact and fact in one array where subfact[i] is next to fact[i]
gigafact: @cjocol2201 going to upload it later...
FadezzHD: How many languages do you know? Asking for a friend :)
sulozor: @georgehotz do what @KyoshiDeath says !
janchomath: inline i * i instead of 2 * I will AC
Klingenwetzer: In C LUL
samtheprogram: why not go
Shahin8520: hahahaha LUL
CaptainAshtar: :D
piece_drake_azur: oh god
murkythunder: WE MUST GO EVEN DEEPER
timbo7io: hahah
ObscureCloud: LMAO
Phott0n: go op
KingKewpa: BRILLIANT
JUST_5HEAD: oh shit, im done
timbo7io: epic
ssh4422: haha
cjocol2201: @gigafact thanks!
CondomsWontFit: we have to reach assembly
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG
Cjiq: Do it in BASH Pog
revolutionist123: 2 hours letter "i will write it in assebly"
piece_drake_azur: he fell for the meme PepeLaugh
josergdev: r u using the dynamic algorith of calculate factorial?
Aixyn0: do it in brainf**k
revolutionist123: later*
gt853_tv: 10 seconds in python
kevin__cs: !keyboard
Klingenwetzer: python forsenKek
FadezzHD: Is ther any proof that challenge can be finished in all languages
Lethly: unlocked i/o for that last push
dontbeameme: Such angry keyboard
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG
kevin__cs: keitiAYAYA
Klingenwetzer: Worse BibleThump
tanoshiizo: NotLikeThis
joehartshorn: this is going really well with the shanghai symphony orchestra at the proms
ObscureCloud: i have an idea we'll go from python to c *2 hours later* oh i have an idea we'll rewrite it in C *a day later* let's just try Go guys! Google backing us we're bound to solve it
dorkmo: Subway10 bonus1
tanoshiizo: GO time?
ISD_Schogol: Are you coding on a laptop?
sulozor: store precompute in one array instead of 3 ?
dontbeameme: ralliedCrack
Lethly: unlocked i/o for last push
sulozor: well you gain allocation time
jagger_rsw: try randomly throwing static inline
gigafact: razer blade laptop
amaramee1: register
PartyAnime: I just joined what's he doing ?
josergdev: r u calculating factorials with dynamic algorithm?
A_McQueen: change i to i
janchomath: wriiiiiite fuckin i * i in eratosthenes
timbo7io: o(cats)
LaytonioSantos: move sqrt out of loop
Klingenwetzer: LUL
dontbeameme: @partyanime Creating A.I
jagger_rsw: if you don't use static inline then functions are by default exported and are called through call and not inlined
Lethly: unlocked i/o for that last nanosecond save
Misiaakoo: you just made it slower
Phott0n: R?
Klingenwetzer: in R LUL
unctarheelss: use circuits for maximum speed
janchomath: i*i
gt853_tv: write it in R 10 seconds
janchomath: in eratosthenes
swftdev: 5 hours if you write it in R
KyoshiDeath: couldn't you actually solve the whole thing at compile time with templates and constexpr in c :thinking:
UNOlover68: Pog
Klingenwetzer: LUL
THX1342: why use anything other than python, ever? KevinTurtle
Meapzor: mb try sql?
dorkmo: the video stream title does sayyyy "GO"
kevin__cs: rewrite it in haskell Kappa
tybutnowyoudie: LUL
Klingenwetzer: hey C compiler loves its keywords PunOko
7Locrian7: PogChamp
gigafact: wow
joehartshorn: oooooo so close
myaocat: almost
JUST_5HEAD: revert that invfact bro
CondomsWontFit: LUL
FadezzHD: PogChamp
some_kind_of_speedrun: PogChamp
janchomath: write i*i in eratosthenes
dontbeameme: Just do it the hard way and get it over with
tanoshiizo: PogChamp
LordDaniel09: wow...
Lethly: @georgehotz unlocked i/o and you're there
revolutionist123: PogChamp
zeroeagle1: what that's weird... xD
umps: cmonBruh
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG ALMOST
samtheprogram: and those are 2 different ones failing
joker2k999: nice
UNOlover68: more inlines Kappa
janchomath: write i*i maaan
dontbeameme: Clip it
sulozor: inline the while loop @georgehotz
LaytonioSantos: @georgehotz are they compiling without optimization
joehartshorn: edge of my seat
unctarheelss: sieve of eroticsynthesis
janchomath: it was my idea :d
dontbeameme: Let’s goooooo🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥
Pilo290: move the invfact back into the loop above
Klingenwetzer: inline it all OpieOP
samtheprogram: inline the things
shemyor: 2?
revolutionist123: inline for loops PogChamp
kevin__cs: rewrite it in HolyC
JUST_5HEAD: keep invfact calc in one loop
FadezzHD: Today we learned that C is faster than C 14
jagger_rsw: __attribute__(("always inline")) static :)
joehartshorn: edge of my herman miller sayl chair
UNOlover68: inlines is abbreviations of roller skates
dontbeameme: 🖕hacker rank
unctarheelss: INLINES
tacorising3: are they compiling with -O3?
janchomath: write i*i instead of 2*i
janchomath: its not fast
ottizy: No optimizing apparently LUL
Lethly: @georgehotz unlocked i/o
kornflexx: Put subfact back into the loop
KyoshiDeath: probably not tacorising
dorkmo: can you take sqrt out of for?
jagger_rsw: __builtin_predict
dontbeameme: !uptime
Klingenwetzer: c loves its keywords BlessRNG
unctarheelss: !keyboard
myaocat: @dorkmo and then what?
Klingenwetzer: LUL
sulozor: nooooo but subfact inside the for loop @georgehotz
myaocat: why are you doing sqrt?
Klingenwetzer: here we go
piece_drake_azur: ..
FadezzHD: Python NotLikeThis
kornflexx: @georgehotz put subfact back into the loop. It was faster
umps: isn't that nested loop O(n^2)
Klingenwetzer: interpreter chill guys
THX1342: see... Python always solves the problem...
tacorising3: @KyoshiDeath yeah, that's what I thought after the inline change
Lethly: @georgehotz getchar_unlocked
Klingenwetzer: he is just printing some numbers LUL
tybutnowyoudie: python 3 LUL
myaocat: https://www.techiedelight.com/measure-elapsed-time-program-chrono-library/
Klingenwetzer: Nice loop OpieOP
Shahin8520: hahahaha nice
dalant979: hardcode woo
Klingenwetzer: just precaculate the solution FeelsGoodMan
kornflexx: Noooo put the subfact back into the loop first!!
Klingenwetzer: to save time
Lethly: @georgehotz getchar_unlocked
7Locrian7: me :) /
Klingenwetzer: ME PogChamp
Pilo290: soo dirty
janchomath: write i * i in eratosthenes
balkibee: i am ready :)
Shahin8520: me :D
joehartshorn: lesgeddit
Klingenwetzer: DAD!!!! I'M READY PogChamp
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
gigafact: hahaha
joker2k999: my body is ready.
foxubu: Backup your code
dontbeameme: PopCorn PopCorn PopCorn PopCorn
tanoshiizo: LUL
josergdev: WTF
FadezzHD: LUL
andrestogas: LUL
Crypod: oh no u didn't
tacorising3: LUL
JUST_5HEAD: wtf
gt853_tv: LUL
Klingenwetzer: Its not python LUL
MaamPlsMarryMe: oh, this is epic
revolutionist123: LUL
gt853_tv: PepeLaugh
tanoshiizo: cheater BabyRage
TheZombieKillerWhale: yup
tybutnowyoudie: cheating
Klingenwetzer: yes :)
covac123: elegant solution :)
JUST_5HEAD: i wish i didnt
gt853_tv: yeah you're hardcoding it
smurfd0: lol really down to the nitty gritty
LordDaniel09: this looks... like cheating...
zeroeagle1: thats elegent
myaocat: HYPE
FadezzHD: You piece of crap, cheater
timbo7io: no
jagger_rsw: use Linux predicticton macros :) : #define likely(x) __builtin_expect((x),1) #define unlikely(x) __builtin_expect((x),0)
catacata92: CHEATER xd
unctarheelss: beautiful code
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG
timbo7io: i missed it
dorkmo: this what the French guy must have done
Klingenwetzer: OMEGALUL
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
myaocat: FUCK
Siim135: @georgehotz sieve should start with i*i
Klingenwetzer: forsenHead
dalant979: F
leon042: why he's not streaming in Science & Technology category?
Shahin8520: LUL
gigafact: lol
tybutnowyoudie: one more failed
Klingenwetzer: Jebaited
timbo7io: hahahaha
Shahin8520: hahahahhaa
sM4rT3r: F
tanoshiizo: LUL
EkkoTheUnforgiven: F
covac123: slower LUL
gt853_tv: even worse OMEGALUL
gn110: LUL
Srkinko: F
joker2k999: LUL
smakatak: LUL
timbo7io: coffee break
Klingenwetzer: HAHAHA
mmr_matt: F
coProof: POGGERS
FadezzHD: Even more errors LUL
dunehazard: OMEGALUL
balkibee: that's impossible NotLikeThis
fear_ep: hahahha
UNOlover68: F
takkeo: LUL
MonkaSupreme: LUL
andrestogas: Jebaited
joker2k999: damn e shit.
myaocat: :(
samtheprogram: is faster for some but not others
joehartshorn: ooooohhhhh not ideal
mmr_matt: LUL
Ziv0: how is that failing more LUL
revolutionist123: LUL
lefg7: !uptime
Cjiq: F
fullrook: haha
cjocol2201: nooooooooooo
MonkaSupreme: F
samtheprogram: depends on your input
cjocol2201: F
dontbeameme: Dammmmitttttttt
Lethly: @georgehotz getchar_unlocked i/o for the final push
trashtofu: WORSE LUL
piece_drake_azur: ROFL
smurfd0: that was slower
janchomath: pleeeeeease
dontbeameme: 😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡
octwopus: LUL
umps: what's the question on hacker rank?
Phott0n: wtf
janchomath: write fuckin i*i in eratosthenes
unctarheelss: INPUT DEPENDENT
kornflexx: @georgehotz Fix your sieve and put subfact back into the loop!!
Cluwe: there is a O(sqrt(n)) prime counter what complexity does yours have?
sulozor: do it in 1 assignation ? @georgehotz
samtheprogram: if n > 100000
7Locrian7: FeelsBadMan
myaocat: do it in inline!!!!!!!!!!!
janchomath: i*i in eratosthenes
swftdev: pastaThat
THX1342: startover using TDD
samtheprogram: inline
BeNiceChat: @georgehotz access the arrays with pointers in C
samtheprogram: 1
janchomath: i*i in eratosthenes please
pucki4: guitComfort
jagger_rsw: help your CPU branch predictor, help yourself :) - use Linux predicticton macros :) : #define likely(x) __builtin_expect((x),1) #define unlikely(x) __builtin_expect((x),0)
myaocat: use pointers
coProof: way too O(1) says test case 31
janchomath: spam it guys
Siim135: @georgehotz sieve should start with i*i
janchomath: yes
janchomath: i*i in i*i in eratosthenes
gt853_tv: try C 14
Klingenwetzer: use more pointers BlessRNG
Klingenwetzer: forsenO
Misiaakoo: create static array of results LUL
EkkoTheUnforgiven: ,aybe is casting on the costant?
gt853_tv: try it in C 14
Saprykinkostja: hardcode primes))
myaocat: inject german brain into code Kappa
teta_musha: your sieve is wrong from the beginning!
kornflexx: Sieve starts with i*i and put subfact back into the loop. It was faster!!
BeNiceChat: In the loop access the arrays with pointers ;)
fear_ep: @georgehotz instead of a[i] use *(a i) in C
jkpfeffer: You don't need code for the prime stuff
Lethly: @georgehotz getchar_unlocked i/o for the final push
lennyerik: inline assembly?
TheZombieKillerWhale: :(
myaocat: @BeNiceChat thats not will make it faster
Klingenwetzer: >hardcode primes
gt853_tv: try in C 14
JUST_5HEAD: put invfact back to the top loop, it was faster
sulozor: no
jkpfeffer: can do it without primes
janchomath: NO
imaginenation: so did he solve it yet?
umps: what's the question
janchomath: i*i in i*i in eratosthenes
Misiaakoo: line 86 merge for loops
BeNiceChat: @myaocat it should for large arrays
Siim135: @georgehotz sieve should start with i*i
Klingenwetzer: :)
samtheprogram: unless you're using const
Lethly: @georgehotz getchar_unlocked i/o for the final push
samtheprogram: const is different in c vs c
Klingenwetzer: LUL
smurfd0: actually before the hardcoded "loop", u had only 2 failing...
ottizy: Pog
Klingenwetzer: just try it LUL
samtheprogram: inb4 they use clang
samtheprogram: nvm...
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: LMFAO
myaocat: f
umps: what's the problem on hacker rank?
gt853_tv: LUL
coProof: :(
janchomath: write
dontbeameme: Hacker rank is super picky I guess
coProof: math ofc :)
janchomath: #include<bits/stdc .h>
Klingenwetzer: googling the include for math.h forsenThink
myaocat: f
tanoshiizo: BlessRNG
jkpfeffer: The prime thing is not essential to the task can do it with any set of 25 numbers out of 100
tybutnowyoudie: hardcoding the loop made it worse
gt853_tv: LUL
joehartshorn: oh man
Siim135: @georgehotz sieve should start with i*i
tanoshiizo: NotLikeThis
sulozor: change the power function back
Lethly: @georgehotz getchar_unlocked i/o for the final push
dorkmo: FailFish100
Klingenwetzer: LUL
myaocat: @Klingenwetzer what do you mean inlude for math?
dontbeameme: BlessRNG
Sylens__: !monitor
imaginenation: i mean the input isnt the bottleneck here
Pilo290: isnt 3 the highest
imaginenation: you could try it the getcharunlocked thing though
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
imaginenation: i*i initializez
Sylens__: @dorkmo what monitor does george use?
Lethly: @georgehotz getchar_unlocked i/o for the final push
Klingenwetzer: he googled what header to include @myaocat for sqrtn
janchomath: #pragma GCC target("avx2,fma")
MonkaSupreme: conditional pragmas Kappa
coProof: put them in a try except
Sylens__: is it 4k @dorkmo
kornflexx: Put the subfact back into the loop and start your sieve with i*i @georgehotz
dorkmo: probably mac
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Misiaakoo: you dont need 2 for loops , line 86
coProof: reroll
Klingenwetzer: 5 hours btw
andrestogas: Jebaited
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Sylens__: @dorkmo imac
swftdev: :q!
sulozor: go back to one for loop ! @georgehotz
imaginenation: try the i*i initializing trick geo
EkkoTheUnforgiven: passing constant as argument?
Iamzad: PepeLaugh
gt853_tv: read what/
joehartshorn: what were you gonna read?
timbo7io: you kept me company
janchomath: i*i in erat
timbo7io: :)
janchomath: i*i
ObscureCloud: little warm up he said
jotembruv: read what
janchomath: write i*i
imaginenation: i*i
andrestogas: warm up Kappa
Lazylion2: !uptime
imaginenation: i*i pogchamp
myaocat: inline would make it faster?
Misiaakoo: 42 *
kornflexx: Write i*I and put invfact back into the loop!
Cluwe: there is a O(sqrt(n)) prime counter
unctarheelss: i * i
JUST_5HEAD: read @kornflexx 's message !
coProof: what dos subfact do
imaginenation: chat can we all spam i*i
BeNiceChat: you can try to Unroll the loop
janchomath: write i*i geohot
janchomath: i * i
FadezzHD: chat spam i * i
joehartshorn: lol 3 cubes or some shit @Misiaakoo
teta_musha: Write i*I and put invfact back into the loop!
dontbeameme: i*I
BiscuitCoin: i * i
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
imaginenation: i*i
NostradaEU: i * i
Sylens__: i*i
Haendel: i*i
ISD_Schogol: he meant line 42 I think :)
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
ObscureCloud: this stream better be saved on here or youtube
sulozor: i * i
Siim135: @georgehotz i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
Iamzad: amateur programmer forsenHead
bsx1123: i * i
Sylens__: i * i
teta_musha: i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
markovchain21: i * i
dontbeameme: i*i
teta_musha: i * i
Klingenwetzer: forsen1
MatiGoG: I*i
unctarheelss: i*i
UNOlover68: i think he meant line 21
teta_musha: i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
trashtofu: i * i
jkpfeffer: The whole prime code is unnecessary!
myaocat: i*i
Shahin8520: i * i
pucki4: guitWut guitWut guitWut guitWut guitWut guitWut
teta_musha: i *
g____: i*i
dunehazard: i * i
fullrook: i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
teta_musha: i*i
samtheprogram: i * i
Klingenwetzer: i * i
kornflexx: i*i
smakatak: i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
teta_musha: i * i
BiscuitCoin: i * i :)
EkkoTheUnforgiven: this implementation WE DONT NEED Y AS ARG
bsx1123: i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
teta_musha: i*i
revolutionist123: i*I
imaginenation: i*i sieve
teta_musha: i * i
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
teta_musha: i*i
BiscuitCoin: i * i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
bsx1123: i * i
teta_musha: i * i
janchomath: i * i
myaocat: LUL
Sknowhite: i*i
markovchain21: i*i
BeNiceChat: @georgehotz loop Unroll :)
teta_musha: i* i
kornflexx: NotLikeThis
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
imaginenation: i*i sieve init geo
myaocat: i*i i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
Siim135: @georgehotz i*i FailFish
BiscuitCoin: i*i
janchomath: i*i
covac123: now you have the line 86
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
teta_musha: i *i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
imaginenation: i*i @georgehotz
teta_musha: i*i
Srkinko: i*j
Bombapil0t: i * i
teta_musha: i *
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
teta_musha: i*i
teta_musha: i *
Shahin8520: what does i * i mean ?
markovchain21: : i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
teta_musha: i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
dontbeameme: I*I
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
teta_musha: i* i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
kornflexx: i*i
coProof: i * i
samtheprogram: LMAO
janchomath: write i*i
teta_musha: i *i
myaocat: @Shahin8520 ^2
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
tybutnowyoudie: whats 1*2 LUL
Ziv0: LUL
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
7Locrian7: what lol
joehartshorn: tinashe 2 on, banger
g____: i*i
unctarheelss: LuL
Paladinerr: hahahhaha
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
Quev1337: i*i
BiscuitCoin: i * i Not reading chat
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
pucki4: guitVasyan guitVasyan guitVasyan guitVasyan
StrippyDrippY: i*i
teta_musha: i*i
bsx1123: i * i ....
Bombapil0t: twitchies go crazy
BiscuitCoin: LULW
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
teta_musha: i * i
dontbeameme: i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
teta_musha: i* i
coProof: mod( i, 2 )
sulozor: i * i
teta_musha: i *i
Klingenwetzer: i * i
Shahin8520: @myaocat ok how does it help ? :)
BiscuitCoin: i*i
myaocat: 92 and 93 is the same thing? WTF
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
markovchain21: i*i
Sknowhite: i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
tanoshiizo: chat ignored LUL
unctarheelss: 2 * 1 = ?
Siim135: @georgehotz i*i FailFish
Atrix321: why do people know all this ahahahaha
markovchain21: @georgehotz : i*i
JUST_5HEAD: i*i
Klingenwetzer: 11 4 = ?
Sknowhite: were being ignored chat
JUST_5HEAD: i * i
kornflexx: i*i and put the invfact back into the loop like you already had before!! @georgehotz
imaginenation: i*i init for sieve of eratos
EkkoTheUnforgiven: why passing y asa arg? coppying long long couled take some time
Quev1337: i*i xd
dontbeameme: i*i🔥
BiscuitCoin: i * i
teta_musha: i*i
Klingenwetzer: IGNORED FeelsBadMan
bsx1123: i * i ...
janchomath: i*i in eratosthenes
teta_musha: i *i
teta_musha: i*i
coProof: pow( i, 2)
janchomath: i * i in eratosthenes
teta_musha: i * i
Klingenwetzer: i * i
markovchain21: : i*i
bsx1123: i * i
unctarheelss: i * i
Lugueiro: @georgehotz LOOK AT THE CHAT
myaocat: LUL
jkpfeffer: you don't need the primes !!!!!!!!!!!
dunehazard: we did it chat
janchomath: i * i instead of i*2
umps: what about a non O(n*m) way to compute P
TheZombieKillerWhale: make it i*i
unctarheelss: finally!
myaocat: @dunehazard now where
imaginenation: instead of i*2
shieeeeeeeeet: LUL ignored
Klingenwetzer: LUL
kornflexx: Change 2*i to i*i !!!
Phott0n: instead of i*2
JUST_5HEAD: i * i instead of i * 2
christian__james: i * i instead of i*2
myaocat: i*i instead i*2
Lugueiro: =D
unctarheelss: i * 2 to i * i
myaocat: i*i instead i*2 i*i instead i*2 i*i instead i*2 i*i instead i*2 i*i instead i*2 i*i instead i*2
g____: i*i instead of i*2
tybutnowyoudie: yes
janchomath: yeaaas
christian__james: YES
janchomath: it is true
Klingenwetzer: LUL Jebaited INC
JUST_5HEAD: it is
dontbeameme: PopCorn ralliedCrack
ObscureCloud: LMAO
teta_musha: omg I just came hard
subzik_: Jebaited
christian__james: Jebaited Clap
kornflexx: @georgehotz put invfact back into the first loop like you had before. It was faster!!
imaginenation: we did it chat lol
EkkoTheUnforgiven: dont pass y as arg in the poer function
janchomath: submiit
unctarheelss: Cause Erosthenis
JUST_5HEAD: its true because thats how it is :D
myaocat: F
myaocat: OMG
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
imaginenation: damn
dalant979: F
janchomath: F
dunehazard: F
kevin__cs: F
bsx1123: F
psychicside: LUL
Klingenwetzer: forsenHead WORSE
imaginenation: SO CLOSE
unctarheelss: F
mmr_matt: F
MaamPlsMarryMe: F
joehartshorn: oooooo shit boiiiii
Cjiq: F
MonkaSupreme: I * i chat
tybutnowyoudie: write it in go
unctarheelss: gg in the chat
kornflexx: Put invfact back int othe first loop!!! @georgehotz
dontbeameme: You failed ussssss chat
pucki4: guitFP guitFP guitFP
JUST_5HEAD: keep that shit on the same loop @georgehotz
sulozor: Put invfact back int othe first loop!!! @georgehotz
myaocat: chat is shit
ProfessorMagikarp0: TakeNRG take my energy i know u can do it
christian__james: EZ
Iamzad: forsenHead WORSE
JUST_5HEAD: chat spam Put invfact back int othe first loop
unctarheelss: I like how the category is "Basic Programming" for this stream
dontbeameme: I spammed for no reason
siglopanico: what page is it?
kornflexx: Put invfact back into the first loop @georgehotz
Cluwe: there is a O(sqrt(N)) Prime counter. What complexity does george's have?
teta_musha: Put invfact back into the first loop @georgehotz
JUST_5HEAD: Put invfact back into the first loop!!!
unctarheelss: who else spammed but had no idea what is going on
serhejenos: put infact back in the first loop
FadezzHD: Lets hard code every single loop
christian__james: !uptime
dontbeameme: Me
JUST_5HEAD: Put invfact back into the first loop
myaocat: put infact back in the first loop
teta_musha: Put invfact back into the first loop
smakatak: Put invfact back into the first loop
Ziv0: please tell me that's not your sessionId
JUST_5HEAD: Put invfact back into the first loop!!!
mattrva: Put invfact back into the first loop
subzik_: Put invfact back into the first loop
unctarheelss: Try dockerizing this
longedok: I have a vague idea what's going on
tacorising3: clib has teh same function name
JUST_5HEAD: Put invfact back into the first loop
Chocho1984: Put invfact back into the first loop
myaocat: chat=crowdsourcing
Quev1337: Put invfact back into the first loop
dunehazard: Put invfact back into the first loop
bsx1123: Put invfact back into the first loop
unctarheelss: Put invfact back into the first loop
serhejenos: put infact back into the first loop
christian__james: Put invfact back into the first loop
Klingenwetzer: Put invfact back into the first loop
smakatak: Put invfact back into the first loop H
imaginenation: lol
Klingenwetzer: Put invfact back into the first loop!
bsx1123: Put invfact back into the first loop.
StrippyDrippY: Put invfact back into the first loop
fear_ep: Put invfact back into the first loop
Cjiq: Put invfact back into the first loop
imaginenation: LOL
mattrva: Put invfact back into the first loop
unctarheelss: Put invfact back into the first loop aydanHeal aydanHeal
dontbeameme: this didn’t work last time
kornflexx: LOL
leon042: MrDestructoid MrDestructoid MrDestructoid
Bombapil0t: TwitchVotes
dorkmo: lol
TheZombieKillerWhale: does someone have a bot here? LUL
Klingenwetzer: LUL
bubble07: @georgehotz can you take down these fools DDOSing Blizzard and Twitch please.
unctarheelss: We did it chat!
joehartshorn: i want a chatroom so i can outsource ideation its a fuckin great idea
jkpfeffer: You dont need any prime code for the task the answer is the same for any set of numbers with the same size!!
teta_musha: I just came hard
myaocat: write crap and all chat write it
FadezzHD: PepeLaugh
subzik_: Jebaited
joker2k999: who listens to chat nowadays...
cjocol2201: :(
youngsachi: Jebaited
teta_musha: @jkpfeffer is right you know @georgehotz
Iamzad: TWITCH CHAT PLAYS PROGRAMMING forsenHead TWITCH CHAT PLAYS PROGRAMMING forsenHead
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG
ivylions: switch category to "Twitch Plays..."
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: 2 PogChamp
myaocat: F
7Locrian7: FeelsBadMan
imaginenation: PP
JUST_5HEAD: JUST 2
janchomath: F
dalant979: PogChamp
imaginenation: HARD
EkkoTheUnforgiven: CMON
andrestogas: Jebaited
kevin__cs: PogChamp
murkythunder: HOLYU SHJI6T
christian__james: 2 Pof
subzik_: POG
Cjiq: F
TheZombieKillerWhale: SO CLOSE PogChamp
tybutnowyoudie: put inline back
myaocat: MonkaS
gt853_tv: try it agian LUL
unctarheelss: OMG
christian__james: 2 Pog
revolutionist123: PogChamp
zeroeagle1: inline back
cjocol2201: OMG
smakatak: POG
Klingenwetzer: forsenJoy 2?
joehartshorn: FUCK
7Locrian7: just keep trying until it passes PogChamp
ProfessorMagikarp0: PrideWingL BlessRNG PrideWingR
LordDaniel09: "Twitch Hacks..."
Iamzad: TWITCH CHAT PLAYS PROGRAMMING forsenHead TWITCH CHAT PLAYS PROGRAMMING forsenHead s
Lugueiro: AAAAAAA
edargorter: Oh man xD
ampluslectus: twitch chat is like shitty machine learning
dontbeameme: Oo0000000
unctarheelss: what should we spam next
JUST_5HEAD: ANY INLINERS ? SoBayed
Bombapil0t: pog
Saprykinkostja: >( >( >(
andrestogas: Saved
TheZombieKillerWhale: SAVED PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
Cjiq: Pog
smileyisdeath: HE BACK HE BACK HE BACK
myaocat: BACK
foxubu: backkkk
janchomath: Fn't
joehartshorn: fuck off subway ad
joker2k999: we back bois
fooxx753: SAVED
samtheprogram: WOOOOO
lefg7: WE BACK BOIIS
bhad: LEAKED
myaocat: BACK BACK BACK BACK BACK BACK BACK BACK BACK BACK BACK BACK
dontbeameme: L
kornflexx: Now change your power function back and only 32 should be missing. @georgehotz
Paladinerr: saved
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG WE BELIEVE
imaginenation: use streamlabs OBS
Shahin8520: Back
th3_maj0r: neightbor reset router
TheZombieKillerWhale: warm up btw LUL
7Locrian7: maybe wait a while before submitting so their CPUs can cool down :)
unctarheelss: Mcdonalds pc
amaramee1: while true: print("F")
Enoxx__: f nsa get him
timtimlkl: 5hrs for 1question !? damn
Klingenwetzer: DansGame imaginenation
dontbeameme: PopCorn ralliedCrack BibleThump
bubble07: @georgehotz can you take down these fools DDOSing Blizzard and Twitch pretty please
myaocat: omg 4
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL wtf
imaginenation: wtf
janchomath: what the F
myaocat: hackerrank is lie
unctarheelss: LuL
jagger_rsw: Mybe unroll the loop a bit more manually, by doing like 10 computations for i, i 1 .. i 9 in one loop and doing i =10
ImAventus: F the haters lol
joehartshorn: u should play tinashe 2 on while u work
imaginenation: nah
7Locrian7: no
myaocat: put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL
Klingenwetzer: no
foxubu: no
Sparks1Cx: we good
tybutnowyoudie: its back
janchomath: no
ampluslectus: no
myaocat: put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its going to be ok on youtube LUL put the music its go
Phott0n: back
siglopanico: NO
paradox109: no
abk467: we back
dontbeameme: Showsearch history
Iamzad: MALDING forsenHead
FadezzHD: Has anybody ever solved this challenge
Klingenwetzer: Jebaited
timbo7io: wooo
Bombapil0t: no
imaginenation: yes
jotembruv: did it crash again>
joehartshorn: tinashe 2 on
supplydemand88: yo
foxubu: kitty
timbo7io: yasssssss'
swftdev: music and mate
kornflexx: Now change your power function back and only 32 should be missing. @georgehotz
UniversalGeneve: CLASSIC
Klingenwetzer: chill beats PogChamp
timbo7io: hell yeah
에스엔엑스: helooo
ObscureCloud: geohotz lil peep streams
Klingenwetzer: FeelsGoodMan
joehartshorn: LOL
siglopanico: DOUU
swftdev: 6 hour warm up
subzik_: pepeJAM
imaginenation: put some animalcrossing music
ImAventus: Did we get rid of the haters 😂😂😂
ProfessorMagikarp0: Pog
mikey9988: VisLaud
JUST_5HEAD: that girl is still reading LUL
lefg7: Pog
kevin__cs: chill PogChamp
dontbeameme: Chill hop
imaginenation: animal crossing music is way better
myaocat: chill
ObscureCloud: thinks chill beats will help him solve te last 2 test cases
MatiGoG: music from speakers DansGame
sulozor: you can still inline power, just rename it powerr (power already taken by the clib) @georgehotz
JUST_5HEAD: invfact its out again
FadezzHD: @georgehotz put this please https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9iUvuaChDEg chat spam it
xiedgar: lmao u said u took 251 on lex's interview?
UNOlover68: rip inline
imaginenation: 700 viewers
janchomath: I can Ac this problem easily
Lugueiro: unboxing therapy musics is good too
imaginenation: poggers chat
jkpfeffer: the prime code is unnecessary, the prime code is unnecessary, the prime code is unnecessary, the prime code is unnecessary, the prime code is unnecessary, the prime code is unnecessary, the prime code is unnecessary, the prime code is unnecessary
Klingenwetzer: LUL
joehartshorn: shanghai symphony orchestra playing in one ear, chill beats on the other
myaocat: @jkpfeffer why?
Cluwe: @georgehotz what complexity does your prime counter have?
cjocol2201: play some mozart
imaginenation: he codes like how hollywood thinks people code
teta_musha: @jkpfeffer I think he's just too involved in that to back away now
swftdev: (n) right?
Klingenwetzer: lol
jkpfeffer: Because it doesnt matter if the numbers are primes the primes are just there to define the set size @myaocat
subzik_: (i) right?
JUST_5HEAD: fuck primes then
logi6000: your still live!!
Klingenwetzer: LUL
teta_musha: fuck primes
Brohanson: did someone say factorio?
Klingenwetzer: factorials @Brohanson
imaginenation: wash your hands
FadezzHD: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9iUvuaChDEg song is beast
Dorgesh: !uptime
imaginenation: george please
LordDaniel09: factorio?!
JUST_5HEAD: ASSEMBLY INCOMING PogChamp
foxubu: Order fooooood
BeNiceChat: gonna write it in GO :D
IMLadyBoy: it's go time
andrestogas: LUL
yusufakcesme: which language he is using
Fat_Fart_9000: he will rewrite it in go Kappa
7Locrian7: plz solves this so i can go get food FeelsBadMan
janchomath: :ddddddddddddddddddddddddddddd
joehartshorn: someone put meatspin on is comp while hes away
imaginenation: MACHINE LEARNING
WhiskeyBrisket: like a racehorse
JUST_5HEAD: LMFAO
paradox109: aahaha
Klingenwetzer: WASH HANDS BlessRNG @georgehotz
imaginenation: ML TIME
christian__james: lol
Phott0n: Kreygasm
TheZombieKillerWhale: 🚽 5Head
gt853_tv: PepeLaugh he lacks critical information
Saprykinkostja: assembly hype
Fat_Fart_9000: golang incoming Kappa
JUST_5HEAD: DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame
extracheese42: @LordDaniel09 Factorials** lLUL
zimxtv: LETS GOOOOO
gigafact: tanks empty
foxubu: Ordering food
logi6000: wash hands
JUST_5HEAD: DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame
TheZombieKillerWhale: DIDNT WASH DansGame
myaocat: @jkpfeffer i dont get it. doesnt he need to find if the number is prime?
Bombapil0t: Keepo
christian__james: didn t wash hands WutFace
UNOlover68: didnt was hands DansGame
MaamPlsMarryMe: papa wash your hands
EkkoTheUnforgiven: comma gpus incoming Kappa
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
TheZombieKillerWhale: DIDN'T WASH DansGame
Unverifieds: LUL
pentaquant: Have you made your virtual girlfriend?
FadezzHD: didn't wash hands DansGame
JUST_5HEAD: DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame
jirikmarik: PogChamp no way
gt853_tv: DansGame
imaginenation: wash hands
Shahin8520: DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame DIDNT WASH HANDS
myaocat: wash hands
dontbeameme: Didn’t wash hands
LordDaniel09: wash hands!
BeNiceChat: write your loop like i--
imaginenation: WASH UR HANDS GEORGE Kappa
subzik_: imagine washing hands in 2k19 4Head imagine washing hands in 2k19 4Head imagine washing hands in 2k19 4Head imagine washing hands in 2k19 4Head
BeNiceChat: dont increase it
janchomath: He dont need
joehartshorn: did anyone see that guy from fox news who said he never washed his hands in like ten years LMAO
smakatak: DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame DIDNT WASH HANDS
imaginenation: WASH UR HANDS GEORGE Kappa WASH UR HANDS GEORGE Kappa
aggeqt: youre missing some spaces bro?
dontbeameme: Dirty hands
myaocat: wash hands Kappa
bsx1123: wash hands
aggeqt: Kapp
cjocol2201: wash hands
7Locrian7: B) speed
Klingenwetzer: speed up BlessRNG
Chi_Nar: Still using the Happy Hacking Keyboard?
Klingenwetzer: forsenE 💿
perfectjustlikeme: Oh please how many of you wash your hands at your own house.
ObscureCloud: C-ool speed up tricks!
Shahin8520: DIDNT WASH HANDS DansGame DIDNT WASH HANDS
JUST_5HEAD: @perfectjustlikeme we just playing man :D
dontbeameme: Always wash my hands all the cool,kids do it
cjocol2201: :)
bsx1123: only wash hands with soap, otherwise dont wash
ISD_Schogol: My mom also always tells me im an invert PepoDance
joehartshorn: https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-47201923 LOL
Klingenwetzer: LUL
jkpfeffer: No @myaocat it doesn't matter.There are 25 primes below 100 thats all that matters. The final solution is the same for any set of 25 numbers below 100
myaocat: @joehartshorn OMEGALUL
Azermite: You should try vectorization instead of for loops :)
TheZombieKillerWhale: NOOOOO
imaginenation: omg
LordDaniel09: ahhhhhhhh
7Locrian7: PogChamp
imaginenation: OMG
janchomath: F
Hazor90: LUL
samtheprogram: nO WAT
dalant979: PogChamp
UNOlover68: POccc
JUST_5HEAD: SHIT
TheZombieKillerWhale: WTFFFFFFFFFFFFF
imaginenation: 1
zbrfey: hoho
janchomath: its wrong
Klingenwetzer: 1 PogChamp
imaginenation: poggers
yusufakcesme: which language he is using
gigafact: lol
Klingenwetzer: OMG
janchomath: o no
dunehazard: PogChamp
Quev1337: NotLikeThis
Shahin8520: 1 PogChamp
whichtom: Pog
imaginenation: we got this
some_kind_of_speedrun: PogChamp
siglopanico: LOL
samtheprogram: PogChamp
revolutionist123: PogChamp
Dino_hun: OMGG
ForsakenReborn: Pog
Cjiq: PogChamp
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp WTF
7Locrian7: this is it PogChamp
FadezzHD: PogChamp
Bombapil0t: PogChamp
catacata92: wow
subzik_: DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp
smileyisdeath: FKIN LPVE THIS
dontbeameme: FUCKKKKKKKKK
altic: PogChamp
thismustbekirk: What in Code Optimization
Klingenwetzer: hardcode more LUL
abk467: it's over boys. we got this
myaocat: @jkpfeffer but input are > 100
massivly: PogChamp
gt853_tv: Pog
imaginenation: MaxLOL
subzik_: DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp
octwopus: PogChamp
dontbeameme: FUCK THIS GAME
subzik_: DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp DIRTY HANDS PogChamp
JUST_5HEAD: FREEDOM IS COMING PogChamp
pspxdiso: what website is this?
andrestogas: PogChamp
myaocat: HYPE !!!!!!!!
Chi_Nar: can he get it
Quev1337: you forgot l
bsx1123: BloodTrail
gt853_tv: JUST HARDCODE THE FIRST 4
gt853_tv: LOL
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp ?
dorkmo: PowerUpL TheIlluminati PowerUpR
ObscureCloud: Basic programming they said
Saprykinkostja: try again without canging
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Jewishrambo: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
aggeqt: C WutFace
thezilion: THE HYPE IS REAL
imaginenation: wait what game is this??
EkkoTheUnforgiven: WTF
myaocat: @pspxdiso https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
Quev1337: add ;
joehartshorn: george when are you doing a hot ones interview?
gigafact: inception
JUST_5HEAD: ;
7Locrian7: PogChamp
Lottsz: @ObscureCloud LUL
Quev1337: ;;
imaginenation: we need to clip this
imaginenation: boys
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU
dontbeameme: send them a mean message George
samtheprogram: do you think this is a game?
imaginenation: PogChamp
myaocat: geohot is einstein * einstein
Bombapil0t: TriHard
jkpfeffer: then it still does not matter @myaocat just calculate the number of primes in that range once externally
codylawyer: codylawyer subscribed with Twitch Prime.
andrestogas: Jebaited
imaginenation: This is it
perfectjustlikeme: Modulus a loop and any that aren’t returning a 1 to get primes.
7Locrian7: PogChamp ❓
JUST_5HEAD: NO Jebaited
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
balkibee: yagutSmart yagutSmart yagutSmart
Lugueiro: geohot too smart
joehartshorn: WOOOOOO lets gooooooo
dorkmo: ;
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
kevin__cs: LUL
Klingenwetzer: Jebaited
whichtom: LUL
Lottsz: LUL
imaginenation: what the fuck
Klingenwetzer: LMFAO
Quev1337: LUL
joehartshorn: FUCK
gt853_tv: LUL
Iamzad: Jebaited
dunehazard: LMAO
dalant979: LUL
UNOlover68: LUL
mmr_matt: LUL
MatiGoG: slam the desk POGGERS
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL WTF
janchomath: ddd
Hazor90: Jebaited
massivly: 2?
thismustbekirk: LUL
FadezzHD: LMAO
some_kind_of_speedrun: Jebaited
gt853_tv: Jebaited
dorkmo: 2?
extracheese42: LUL
Klingenwetzer: 2 forsenHead
octwopus: LUL
takkeo: LUL
7Locrian7: variability PogChamp
imaginenation: This is random
revolutionist123: LUL
Ziv0: 27 ? LUL
tybutnowyoudie: LUL
thezilion: oh gosh
41312737214: Jebaited
altic: LUL
massivly: 2? xqcL
Bit_Mike: Twice as fast Pog
smakatak: LUL
Bombapil0t: NotLikeThis
ssh4422: LMAO
jeann2019: is random
joehartshorn: not ideal
joker2k999: LUL damn
JUST_5HEAD: THEY ARE FUCKING WITH YOU Jebaited
7Locrian7: keep trying until it works :)
Klingenwetzer: forsenJoy
trashtofu: 2?
dontbeameme: 2 errors
dorkmo: FailFish2
TheZombieKillerWhale: twice as fast Kappa
Azermite: Vectorizaaation instead of for loops
janchomath: submit agin
gt853_tv: hardcode the first 4
samtheprogram: depends on the input
gt853_tv: lul
revolutionist123: it was too fast need slower
dontbeameme: It’s trolling you
trashtofu: rajjTHICC
myaocat: @jkpfeffer so what would you change instead in the code to make it faster?
janchomath: try c 14
Lottsz: @revolutionist123 lol
cjocol2201: lol
Saprykinkostja: just do it again)))
imaginenation: ing
christian__james: you got trolled by UI
jkpfeffer: get rid of all the prime code
jkpfeffer: @myaocat
zbrfey: 97.3
EkkoTheUnforgiven: i /2 => i >> 1
Seecez: Have you tried compile time evaluation with C 11 constexpr?
7Locrian7: moon2T
Klingenwetzer: LUL
UNOlover68: its addition Kappa
AnOwlbear: 4Head
myaocat: chat write get rid of all the prime code
joker2k999: a product. lol
myaocat: get rid of all the prime code
Azermite: additions
imaginenation: well go for karatsuba multiplcation then LOL
7Locrian7: karatsuba PogChamp
timbo7io: ya
ObscureCloud: "can we think for a second about what multiplication is"
Crypod: the comments are slowing it down Kappa
ISD_Schogol: What even is math? thinking
timbo7io: its
myaocat: get rid of all the prime code get rid of all the prime code get rid of all the prime code get rid of all the prime code
thismustbekirk: you are counting sets of a number
gt853_tv: its a series of additions
mexeroserisback: PogChamp yes
WhiskeyBrisket: 2 2 = 4
timbo7io: right shift bts
kei86: its just bit wise rotations?
myaocat: @jkpfeffer what do you mean?
Klingenwetzer: hardcode more OpieOP
Azermite: Vectorization bro
myaocat: LUL
timbo7io: multi = a << b
st47ik: too many trolls in chat DansGame
dontbeameme: -1 1=0
Klingenwetzer: Jebaited
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
janchomath: wtf
imaginenation: karatsuba multiplication is a faster multiplication
wetmatch: Bit shifting
Cluwe: what complexity is the prime code?
JUST_5HEAD: you can do multiplication and division with bitshifting 4Head
joehartshorn: bukakke multiplication Kappa
dorkmo: Amazon same day compute
thismustbekirk: you have to look at the generators of the set and then determine by the power rule what will happen in the binary operation
perfectjustlikeme: Memo-ize to speed up
supplydemand88: its the prime code man
Iamzad: TROLL test forsenHead
Venald: enable AVX512 Kappa
Klingenwetzer: forsenHead
paradox109: at this point is just stupid LOL
foxubu: Confirmed. Karatsuba is insane :)
myaocat: @jkpfeffer you troll?
BeNiceChat: i-- instead of i
7Locrian7: 3-way toom cook :)
Jewishrambo: Are they base cases ?
Klingenwetzer: :)
joehartshorn: fast bukakke multiplication
Seecez: C 11 compile time evaluation with constexpr!
timbo7io: you have nice wood flooring
thismustbekirk: Runga-Kutta method
subzik_: ye @Jewishrambo
DasMastah: !uptime
abstractingagent: @georgehotz you can do it george! *wheezes behind a cloud smoke coming from his 12th joint*
Klingenwetzer: where LUL
gt853_tv: i * i makes it worse than i * 2 doesn't it
BeNiceChat: rewrite your for loop
UNOlover68: fast float arithmetic?
gt853_tv: why would i * i be faster
dorkmo: 93?
BeNiceChat: no need for the i<=n
A_McQueen: do i instead of i
zeroeagle1: karatsuba wont be usefull because of the #pragma
dorkmo: line 93?
thismustbekirk: weeabelieve
jkpfeffer: No @myaocat I looked at a solution from someone else he explained it pretty well
DasMastah: For how long has he been streaming?
JUST_5HEAD: karatsuba its insane though
ObscureCloud: when you're so close but your gf denies it...chat so quick no one will read this edging reference
lennyerik: division by 2 is a binary right shift; multiplication by 2 is a binary left shift.
myaocat: @jkpfeffer can you link?
janchomath: i*i>2*i so its faster
st47ik: almost 6 hours PogChamp
myaocat: @janchomath how?
jkpfeffer: @myaocat https://euler.stephan-brumme.com/239/
Klingenwetzer: WORSE forsenHead
jagger_rsw: #pragma GCC push_options #pragma GCC optimize ("unroll-loops")
Iamzad: WORSE forsenHead
DasMastah: Okay, ty
st47ik: is this a 24h stream PogChamp
Shahin8520: WORSE forsenHead
myaocat: @jkpfeffer thanks
Iamzad: forsenBoys 🔭 forsen1 ?
Azermite: Search vectorization instead of for loops
trubadurmester: What is this warmup for exactly?
janchomath: wtf guys of course i*i is faster
Klingenwetzer: forsen1 BAJS
BeNiceChat: i-- instead of i for the loops. and you save the i<=n check
averagesizepens: more like 96 hour steam
Azermite: Vectorization >> for loops
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink
Iamzad: forsenK
FadezzHD: !commands
trashtofu: less than a warm up and more like a marathon
Chi_Nar: AVX512?
Klingenwetzer: NotLikeThis
Seecez: Try C 11 compile time evaluation with constexpr!
A_McQueen: do i instead of i as i returns a ref
TheZombieKillerWhale: NotLikeThis
Venald: AVX512 Kappa
supplydemand88: definitely go with vectorization
tybutnowyoudie: rewrite it in go Kappa
teta_musha: @myaocat @jkpfeffer I found that solution too, it doesn't use primes
kei86: A_McQueen : shouldn't the compiler optimize that though?
Infinitelym: can someone post the leaderboard link for this problem?
ottizy: add arch pragma LuL
st47ik: rust > go Kappa
A_McQueen: no
zeroeagle1: i
trashtofu: try c 14?
mlacix: @Infinitelym https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/leaderboard?page=1
thismustbekirk: YESS
Jewishrambo: N
Infinitelym: tyvm
aggeqt: YES
Lottsz: LUL
lefg7: Yes please
Fat_Fart_9000: YEEEES
gt853_tv: can you show us the whole code
anthonyk95: yes
rkxbz: yeah
LordDaniel09: NO
Azermite: PLEASE
devm0d: we all knew this was coming
Fat_Fart_9000: LETS GOOOO
christian__james: @trashtofu he is on c 14
anthonyk95: do it in go
Iamzad: Yes forsenHead
ForsakenReborn: bruh moment
Azermite: JUST DO IT
myaocat: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
rkxbz: go
kevin__cs: rewrite it in GO!!
thismustbekirk: LETS GOOOOOOOPHER
ssh4422: do it
JUST_5HEAD: im going to pee, dont solve it
Klingenwetzer: you can't put variables into L1 cache manually? :(
Shibby834: GO for it :)
dontbeameme: Do it in go
Ziv0: you should be able to do it without Go
Sgt_Gizm0s: Can unlock iphones, hack playstations, and make self driving cars.
myaocat: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function@@@@@@@@@@@@
christian__james: @trashtofu atleast he was lmfao
Sgt_Gizm0s: Can’t solve code test
joehartshorn: i believe in u geohot
thismustbekirk: You have to treat it like a CYCLIC MOD GROUP OVER THE REALS
ottizy: #pragma GCC target "arch=haswell" PogChamp
bsx1123: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
kubectl: heyyo what is the problem?
dontbeameme: Ask gennady for help he #1 on leaderboard
jay_al97: you still stuck on the same problem?
thismustbekirk: USE JAVASCRIPT
Merwanedr: George please open Vim let us have orgasms
foxubu: stream deadd
myaocat: read the question again.. numbers are limited from 1 to 100
asaptwice: I love the keyboard sound :D
minichota: why isnt George using vim feature of hackerrank
voxelfox0125: C 14
TheZombieKillerWhale: SO CLOSE
Klingenwetzer: NotLikeThis
myaocat: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
joehartshorn: FUCK
Iamzad: 2 FeelsBadMan
Ziv0: LUL
7Locrian7: just keep submitting :)
myaocat: wont help
christian__james: I love how people are hating on him because he s struggling with this code, considering the fact they don't know how to code a Hello input.. Otherwise they would not hate, because they would know this is not easy :)
Fat_Fart_9000: LUL
Klingenwetzer: Jebaited this is worse than gambling @georgehotz
foxubu: Use Karatsuba
st47ik: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
konradmad: @georgehotz BET IF YOU SMOKED A LITTLE WEED YOU COULD SOLVE IT....EHHHHHH
Remembermyfart1: !uptime
bsx1123: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
perfectjustlikeme: Vim > emacs? Serious question.
jkpfeffer: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
kubectl: @georgehotz heyyo whats the problem definition?
julen9601: what is he doing?
Klingenwetzer: forsenK @perfectjustlikeme
Fat_Fart_9000: emacs
st47ik: uptime is almost 6 hours i guess
Merwanedr: VIM
Klingenwetzer: Nice bait
myaocat: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
Cluwe: what complexity is your prime counter?
jkpfeffer: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
ottizy: #pragma GCC target "arch=haswell" FeelsBadMan
Fat_Fart_9000: !uptime
BeNiceChat: for (int i=n; i--;)
josergdev: random tests
subzik_: 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
myaocat: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function@georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
kei86: stochastic test cases
bsx1123: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function@
st47ik: copy pasta LUL
Klingenwetzer: NO LUL
Azermite: YES
UniversalGeneve: @christian__james non-programmers hate, other programmers sympathize LUL
f00z: it's n, not 100 :|
myaocat: switch to haskell
st47ik: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
Iamzad: G OMEGALUL
BeNiceChat: decreasing loops for (int i=n; i--;)
thismustbekirk: assertion and err
bsx1123: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function@@
Cluwe: guys its n
subzik_: @georgehotz question is "A set of disks numbered 1 through 100 are placed in a line in random order" 1 < num < 100 => there are 25 prime numbers below 100. so get rid of the prime function
Iamzad: G forsenDED
Merwanedr: vvvviiim
A_McQueen: do i instead of i as i returns a ref
extr3mity: is he still trying to figure it out?
Merwanedr: Please open vim
f00z: you're looking at project euler, not hackerrank....
Azermite: Please switch to GO
Merwanedr: let us chill
christian__james: @UniversalGeneve yeah.. this shit is really hard tbh
dorkmo: letssss GO
BeNiceChat: for (int i=n; i--;) one less check
perfectjustlikeme: VERY deep in thought
Shahin8520: why GO should be better ?
janchomath: write some more pragmas
alfyfav: How much tiem has geo be coding this?
Chi_Nar: They might have arguments that no code optimization
myaocat: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Derangement
samtheprogram: switch to go
alfyfav: time*
tybutnowyoudie: @Shahin8520 because the time limit is higher
TheZombieKillerWhale: @Shahin8520 hackerrank gives more time for Go
Chi_Nar: have you tried #pragma omp for
Merwanedr: watching geohot on windows makes me depressive
gigafact: 6h
janchomath: #pragma GCC optimization ("unroll-loops")
averagesizepens: just ctrl w and done
janchomath: #pragma GCC target("avx2,fma")
thismustbekirk: model your function like a finite cyclic mod group over the reals
BeNiceChat: for (int i=n; i--;) :)
christian__james: @Merwanedr yeah me2
bhad: this is easier then installing arch linux
josergdev: Go simply has more time limit
supplydemand88: you have to remove that function part Jesus
janchomath: #pragma GCC optimize("Ofast")
Shahin8520: ah thanks guys :D @tybutnowyoudie @TheZombieKillerWhale
bhad: cmon george you got this
swftdev: its not C^w its :q!
myaocat: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Derangement
aggeqt: @georgehotz your hashtags on instagram are on point my guy
janchomath: #pragma GCC optimization ("unroll-loops")
perfectjustlikeme: Yes, FP is the shit... category theory
myaocat: read the question again! find a better solution instead of rewrite a single statement to shorter
Pilo290: ;
TheZombieKillerWhale: missing semi colon
zeroeagle1: i=3
Klingenwetzer: use more ternary operators rephtoSmile
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
myaocat: f
kevin__cs: SO CLOSE LMAO
Klingenwetzer: LUL
jagger_rsw: i might be wring but "% 100000123" is slow because its actual division operation, use '& mask' with BIG 0x...ffff
abstractingagent: ALMOSTTTTT
Klingenwetzer: no
supplydemand88: can anybody link a theory part to tell him to remove the prime function side???
EkkoTheUnforgiven: FFFFFFFFFFFF
Ziv0: no LUL
TheZombieKillerWhale: actually got my hopes up
christian__james: @georgehotz go back to pseudocode and try rethinking the issue from another angle... it's useless to rewrite 2 lines 50 times
josergdev: random tests
andrestogas: LUL
imaginenation: do more bit manipulations
BeNiceChat: for (int i=n; i--;) It will not have to perform the i<n check
mikey9988: Jebaited
janchomath: #pragma GCC optimization ("unroll-loops")
youngsachi: Jebaited
janchomath: write it
UniversalGeneve: 30 yes, not 36
TheZombieKillerWhale: WE'RE IN TOO DEEP
imaginenation: i consider this as a win
jkpfeffer: @georgehotz The answer is the same for any set of 25 numbers!
Klingenwetzer: pseudo code now when we are so close LUL
st47ik: fact: The problem of counting derangements was solved in 5 years LUL
janchomath: it matters
imaginenation: lets just leave this
revolutionist123: remove if and put i =2
abstractingagent: damn man - almost 700 people in this bitch
timbo7io: i ran out of wine
josergdev: the tests possibly are randomly genereated
bhad: just spam submit code, and wait for their computers to speed themselves up
perfectjustlikeme: Use more ternary ? “Nah” : “fuk yas”
minichota: @georgehotz why arent you using vim mode?
supplydemand88: i= 2
TheZombieKillerWhale: submit the code at night when no one is using their servers LUL
myaocat: chat pls dont troll him
Klingenwetzer: LUL That was actually a joke DUDE @perfectjustlikeme
Klingenwetzer: LUL
JUST_5HEAD: its the same, dont bother with this shit
abstractingagent: @timbo7io haha
zeroeagle1: only prettier
drewc830: so is this the problem that it's working correctly but not fast enough?
st47ik: chat Jebaited
youngsachi: Jebaited
perfectjustlikeme: Lol same
revolutionist123: @georgehotz remove if and put i =2
TheZombieKillerWhale: Jebaited
imaginenation: LOL
joehartshorn: YEBO
janchomath: Wow
KingKewpa: just one time dealer
Klingenwetzer: LUL ternary lowve
christian__james: @drewc830 yes.. the code is not optimised enough to pass apparantly
Klingenwetzer: lowVe
Iamzad: WORSE forsenHead
youngsachi: Jebaited Jebaited
st47ik: rip
imaginenation: jabaited
Klingenwetzer: yeah it doesn't
zeroeagle1: every body on hackerrank log out
drewc830: @christian__james got ya
lefg7: it doesn't
myaocat: remove if and put i =2
supplydemand88: I =2
Klingenwetzer: ofc it doesn't LUL
BiscuitCoin: LUL
Lottsz: @zeroeagle1 LMAO
코케인: ask instagram for help Kappa
myaocat: remove if and put i =2 remove if and put i =2 remove if and put i =2
NonTrivial778: ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper
Klingenwetzer: we had that before @myaocat
Vjasal: @georgehotz which challenge is it?
supplydemand88: yo George read!
imaginenation: waht is the invfact doing?
insanebaba: what's the link to the problem?
myaocat: @Klingenwetzer what is your suggestion then?
voxelfox0125: make your own Pow function
kevin__cs: go back to pseudo code and rewrite in GO
FargioFarmani: substract n from p in the while loop @georgehotz
myaocat: @insanebaba https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem
f00z: https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/projecteuler/challenges/euler239/problem @insanebaba @Vjasal
lennyerik: maybe write some stuff in inline assembly (if at all possible)?
Klingenwetzer: remove the upper half of the search area for isPrime
jagger_rsw: isn't power() slow because u use slow % with 1000..123 which cannot be optimized instead of val&0xff..ff mask ?
Chi_Nar: sieve of Eratosthenes untilo n
TheZombieKillerWhale: time to switch to Go
jkpfeffer: @georgehotz The answer is the same for any set of (25-22) numbers! You don't need any prime code.
Azermite: vectorization instead of for loops
Equalizer_olo: Any Russian?
insanebaba: @myaocat thank you
myaocat: inline assembly would generate the same opcodes and not a different algorithm which will make i fasster.
myaocat: it*
AnOwlbear: Let's go upgrade the server processors 4Head
7Locrian7: maybe try again at a time where their CPUs aren't being used Kappa
Klingenwetzer: LUL
perfectjustlikeme: Thank you Clifford Claven...
TomFordNY: moon2BRAIN
iCraftNaked: pls sir hack the WoW servers back online
serhejenos: 700 viewers
bhad: Code it in swift
minichota: rewrite in all assembly
serhejenos: POG
massivly: 700 viewers PogChamp
imaginenation: lol we should try approximating factorials using the sterlings approximation
Klingenwetzer: WutFace
myaocat: @minichota assembly wont help
perfectjustlikeme: Swift in code
aggeqt: ctrl s LUL
Hooterrr: f
Vinndy: ctrl s syndrome
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
imaginenation: make it O(1)
bhad: just spam submit code, and wait for their computers to speed themselves up
joehartshorn: FUCK
imaginenation: bro
mikey9988: Jebaited LUL
myaocat: @imaginenation tell him how then
imaginenation: do you even O(1) BRO?
Hazor90: 2 NotLikeThis
supplydemand88: will not make difference in terms of opcodes in assembly
joehartshorn: YOU CAN DO THIS GEO
Klingenwetzer: approximating factorials :)
supplydemand88: Jesus...
myaocat: do you even O(1) BRO?
imaginenation: look up sterlings approx
unctarheelss: compute the cloud and call it
janchomath: #pragma GCC optimize("Ofast") #pragma GCC target("avx2,fma")
Klingenwetzer: O(1) @imaginenation LUL
perfectjustlikeme: O(1) bother...
trashtofu: YOU GOT THIS
st47ik: Big O brother
imaginenation: O(n) is bad
Shahin8520: do you even O(1) BRO?
zeroeagle1: is static_cast<>() faster then (ll) cast?
imaginenation: LOL
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp WTFFFFF
imaginenation: WTfAHAHAH
ProfessorMagikarp0: PogChamp
LordDaniel09: really?!
JUST_5HEAD: WTFF
imaginenation: OMGAD
7Locrian7: PogChamp
Causevd: PogChamp
CondomsWontFit: PogChamp
myaocat: hype
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp YES!
gigafact: gggg
massivly: PogChamp
thezilion: HOLLY
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
SlayerX1: PogChamp
bsx1123: OMGGG
SamMyB_53: OMFG
youngsachi: PogChamp
whichtom: holy shit YES
trashtofu: LETS GO
tybutnowyoudie: PogChamp
Shahin8520: PogChamp
FadezzHD: PogChamp
janchomath: holy shiiiit
EkkoTheUnforgiven: POOOOOOOOOOOOOOOG
Klingenwetzer: OMFG
oldggregg: POG
Causevd: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
clubmate42: PogChamp
BiscuitCoin: PogChamp
Chi_Nar: Chi_Nar subscribed with Twitch Prime.
41312737214: PogChamp
st47ik: PogChamp
Ziv0: PogChamp
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp AMAZING
Cluwe: Cluwe subscribed with Twitch Prime.
sad__boi_: Pog
Cjiq: PogChamp
WhiskeyBrisket: Pog
Azermite: gg
voxelfox0125: YAAAAAAAAAAA
Causevd: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
tybutnowyoudie: what did you change?
JUST_5HEAD: FINALLY BRO
lefg7: Pog
FargioFarmani: LMAO
revolutionist123: PogChamp
Bombapil0t: POG
joehartshorn: FUCK YEAAAAAA
Causevd: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Vinndy: PogChamp
abstractingagent: EYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY
johnvika: JonCarnage
eim64: gg
christian__james: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
ObscureCloud: WE DID IT
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp WTF
gorgai: I WAS HERE Pog
eaterenrgy: POG PGO POG
extracheese42: yesssssssssssssssssssss
altic: PogChamp
thehypocite: PogChamp
supplydemand88: oooooooooooo
nip10: POG
gigafact: gggggggggggggggggg
Causevd: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
joehartshorn: WOOOOOOOO
mmr_matt: PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU
kevin__cs: PogChamp
Bombapil0t: 1337
DasMastah: PogChamp
TomFordNY: moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN
Fat_Fart_9000: Poooound
amaramee1: yeaaa
Cjiq: YAY
DerZemba: PogChamp
janchomath: F F F F F F
phil800: WOW
johnvika: StoneLightning
joehartshorn: HAHAHAHAHHAHA
YoinkMineNow: PogChamp
DeviL58: PogChamp
dalant979: VoHiYo
Srkinko: YEET
nip10: HELLO
smurfd0: easy :P
Siandemm: LETS FUCKING GOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
xSynchronizeD: PogChamp
supplydemand88: fuuuuuuuuuuuuucckkkkk
myaocat: HYPE
SpiritHNTR: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
Hazor90: PogChamp
phil800: GG
ObscureCloud: HERE WE GO BOYS
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE
WhiskeyBrisket: pogChamp
bsx1123: YEAAAAaa
imaginenation: CLIP
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU
andrestogas: PogChamp
Zacharycht: nice
eaterenrgy: POG POG POG POG
st47ik: 1337 PogChamp
Bombapil0t: PogChamp
joker2k999: damn. we in here bois
johnvika: B)
Flaxe_: nice
abstractingagent: HAHAHAHAH LETS GOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
youngsachi: PogChamp PogChamp
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE
supplydemand88: orgasm
phil800: NICE
EkkoTheUnforgiven: pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG
balkibee: apxHi
aggeqt: lol
subzik_: 6 hours LUL 6 hours LUL 6 hours LUL 6 hours LUL 6 hours LUL 6 hours LUL 6 hours LUL
joehartshorn: WEWWWWWWW
ProfessorMagikarp0: this is y u make the big bucks PogChamp
Shahin8520: PogChamp PogChamp
amaramee1: haxor
samtheprogram: PogChamp
7Locrian7: moon2S
Cluwe: GGG
UniversalGeneve: EZclap
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp I WAS HERE
timbo7io: PokPikachu
abk467: missgHYPE missgHYPE missgHYPE missgHYPE timbeaTROPHY timbeaTROPHY timbeaTROPHY timbeaTROPHY MrDestructoid
abstractingagent: YEAHHH BABBEHHHH
KingKewpa: WORLD FIRST PogChamp
averagesizepens: PogChamp
BiscuitCoin: PogChamp I was HERE
Causevd: @georgehotz dance dance dance
Bombapil0t: blazin60POG
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp @georgehotz
myaocat: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
ObscureCloud: FUCK YES
phil800: GG
mikey9988: PogChamp
Mohdsalah: BibleThump
fear_ep: gg wp
joehartshorn: HYPE
eaterenrgy: I WAS HERE!!!
WhiskeyBrisket: PogChamp
timbo7io: hell yeah
st47ik: we're here PogChamp
myaocat: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
ObscureCloud: 6 HOURS
Cjiq: I WAS HERE PogChamp
datmaddiew: yea
Zacharycht: man of the people
Jewishrambo: PogChamp PogChamp Kreygasm PogChamp Kreygasm PogChamp
liesai: good job
stykk: HI MOM
janchomath: GG
Cluwe: Good job
whichtom: 'warm up'
insanebaba: SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood
eaterenrgy: POG POG POG POG POG
FargioFarmani: CLAP CLAP CLAP
TheZombieKillerWhale: PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE
takkeo: FINALLY
Klingenwetzer: FeelsGoodMan
JUST_5HEAD: I WAS HERE PogChamp
joker2k999: GOOD SHIT
timbo7io: WOOOOOOOOOOOO
extracheese42: pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD pepeD
dalant979: #10
Kjjj11223344: PogChamp
spanilith: DoritosChip
bhad: ANOTHER 😡
ObscureCloud: GREAT WARM UP
JUST_5HEAD: I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp I WAS HERE PogChamp
st47ik: 7 hours! PogChamp
supplydemand88: fuuuuuuuuuuuuuucccck
Billybofilly: PogChamp
Vjasal: @georgehotz run it again
kucha1122: EZ Clap
Bombapil0t: TwitchVotes twitchRaid
timbo7io: prase the lord
supplydemand88: yessssssssss
christian__james: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU
TomFordNY: moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN moon2BRAIN
timbo7io: hellz ya
youngsachi: PogChamp
timbo7io: ior
JUST_5HEAD: the primes
spjud: cbrah420Pepe cbrah420Pepe cbrah420Pepe
joker2k999: now time for the hard ones
abstractingagent: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
samtheprogram: run it again
imaginenation: THIS IS AGOOD DAY
th3_maj0r: 707 viewers
supplydemand88: orgasmic
timbo7io: iou
dorkmo: Party5000
janchomath: submit again it wont AC
iSaNsOT: xokDO xokNE
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU
gn110: on hackerrank this problem is medium difficulty NotLikeThis , how a hard one looks like
joehartshorn: WOOOOOO
janchomath: submit again
EkkoTheUnforgiven: pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG
imaginenation: WE CAN HAVE SOME MORE SUBSCRIPTIONS
st47ik: 700 viewers PogChamp
nip10: nice warmup.. lets go to the real challenge now ?
timbo7io: PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu
ProfessorMagikarp0: nice warm up Kappa
UniversalGeneve: EZclap
imaginenation: https://clips.twitch.tv/BlightedCorrectSashimiANELE
Klingenwetzer: Run it again Kappa @georgehotz
myaocat: next problem
TheZombieKillerWhale: LUL
timbo7io: PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu PokPikachu
Iamzad: THIS WAS THE EASY ONE forsenHead
janchomath: submit aggain
georgehotz: Success! Just solved Project Euler #239: Twenty-two Foolish Primes on @HackerRank. Can you complete the challenge? Tried too many times seeking an available slug #programming
josergdev: i missed the solution :( for 1 second
Klingenwetzer: LUL
imaginenation: https://clips.twitch.tv/BlightedCorrectSashimiANELE check it
joehartshorn: BIG = TRU
kucha1122: Go hard problem tomorrow
janchomath: you cant get AC ith teh same code
TheZombieKillerWhale: "medium" LUL
myaocat: git push
Iamzad: THIS WAS THE EASY ONE forsenHead THIS WAS THE EASY ONE forsenHead THIS WAS THE EASY ONE forsenHead
Klingenwetzer: Kappa
bhad: ANOTHER 😡
st47ik: nice warm up PogChamp
dorkmo: warm up finished, time for the real thing!
myaocat: wash hands!
Klingenwetzer: ofc its faster
st47ik: ^
mikey9988: pp[BIG] LUL
imaginenation: now go wash your hands
Klingenwetzer: yes
christian__james: 7 hours warmup PogChamp
massivly: real thing PogChamp
StrippyDrippY: no balls, run it again LUL
Iamzad: THIS WAS THE EASY ONE forsenHead THIS WAS THE EASY ONE forsenHead THIS WAS THE EASY ONE forsenHead x
myaocat: LUL
extracheese42: LUL
ObscureCloud: Warm up doen boys time for the actual game now?
7Locrian7: is this the only problem he did?
st47ik: 7 hours LUL
trubadurmester: Yeah, let's go to the real thing now
imaginenation: pp[MASSIVE]
EkkoTheUnforgiven: pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG pharaohPOG
Bombapil0t: LUL
UNOlover68: He washed his hands PogChamp
WhiskeyBrisket: YEAHHHHH
zbrfey: damn missed it
KingKewpa: Warm over, time for the real stuff
joehartshorn: its not about the ram, thats what i always say
supplydemand88: now you need a bitch
andrestogas: Now let's solve the real problem Kappa
UniversalGeneve: washing hands. finally, the true problem is solved
KingKewpa: Warm up over, time for the real stuff
joker2k999: minecraft will be much tougher
imaginenation: lets fuck a hoe now
xolanig: Aaahhh this fucking wi-fi
ObscureCloud: int pp [Massive 6 hours of edging]
DavilaFQ: How tall are you?
Klingenwetzer: have the same problem when I calculate primes with unsigned long long LUL the runtime doubles
kei86: Now for the hard ones
aggeqt: pp[BIG]
dontbeameme: He got it?
trubadurmester: Warmup over, real stuf now - Warmup over, real stuf now - Warmup over, real stuf now
myaocat: now next problm
st47ik: sOap
myaocat: or play mario
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
Quev1337: pp[BIG]
TheZombieKillerWhale: @dontbeameme yes he did
sulozor: Cooking stream PogCHamp
trollnrollnrocknroll: does he have youtube ?
revolutionist123: @georgehotz Niw explain what we where watching!
imaginenation: lets play some minecraft
st47ik: Minecraft time PogChamp
Vinndy: COOKING STREAM PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU
dontbeameme: Dammit
janchomath: it wasnt enough form warm up
dontbeameme: Clip it
st47ik: cooking stream PogChamp
dalant979: GG
myaocat: mario?
Bitcoin__: Bitcoin__ subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 6 months, currently on a 6 month streak! Never been able to hear u read my sub message
nanodanger7: what are you reading?
WhiskeyBrisket: lmfao
CaptainAshtar: You will have what to tellyour friends now
supplydemand88: bro I can cook Italian food
extracheese42: GG geo
Klingenwetzer: FeelsGoodMan
imaginenation: man
FargioFarmani: great warmup, now lets solve some hard problems @georgehotz
imaginenation: this is so inspiring
devm0d: You're the best Geo. Love the programming streams!
JUST_5HEAD: lmfao
myaocat: mario stream??
abhb09: What is his twitter handle?
st47ik: bitcoin subscribed PogChamp
Iamzad: THIS WAS THE EASY ONE forsenHead
dorkmo: Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1
MaamPlsMarryMe: go off king
FadezzHD: Mad followers on instagram
TheZombieKillerWhale: that was a true feat
myaocat: @imaginenation gg
devm0d: Keep the streams coming!
balkibee: HackerMan
joker2k999: cheers bro
dontbeameme: Gg
Klingenwetzer: LUL
joehartshorn: what a legend
imaginenation: never give up
myaocat: ggs
imaginenation: bruh
Klingenwetzer: NEVER GIVE UP LUL
myaocat: ggs everyone
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp I BELIEVED IN YOU
Chi_Nar: family guy?
st47ik: LUL
imaginenation: lol
abk467: ggs
Lugueiro: nice
abstractingagent: yeah boiiiiiii
joehartshorn: wow no pope
Hazor90: I was here PogChamp
7Locrian7: bye :)
ObscureCloud: LMAO
whichtom: peace man
Klingenwetzer: cya lowHi DAD
dalant979: peace
phil800: bye
myaocat: NEVER SURREDNER
st47ik: bye :)
imaginenation: is he going ?
joehartshorn: love u bye
devm0d: Never say Never
aggeqt: NEVER GIVE UP
Cluwe: gj
dontbeameme: A.i has no chance against geo
TheZombieKillerWhale: HeyGuys
EkkoTheUnforgiven: pharaohPOG
eaterenrgy: CYA
Bombapil0t: SeemsGood
UniversalGeneve: peace
Lugueiro: bye
devm0d: never show your cock on stream
myaocat: NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER
NonTrivial778: NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER
Zacharycht: bye mr hotz
joker2k999: peace bois
imaginenation: bust a rap
ObscureCloud: SAVE THIS STREAM
Andrejmokris: Bye
revolutionist123: LUL
imaginenation: bust a rap dude
konradmad: <3
myaocat: Q&A
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3
Klingenwetzer: lowHi lowVe bye DAD :)
dontbeameme: Economics
FadezzHD: Do a rap
abhb09: Your twitter hanle
imaginenation: LOL
WhiskeyBrisket: look at the solution
imaginenation: HAHA
JUST_5HEAD: LMFAO
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3
dorkmo: HeyGuys100
myaocat: NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER
imaginenation: this was insane
ObscureCloud: SAVE THIS STREAM GEO
gigafact: gg
st47ik: LUL
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 .
abstractingagent: eyyyyyyyyyyyyy
josergdev: where is the tweet?
imaginenation: https://clips.twitch.tv/BlightedCorrectSashimiANELE
Klingenwetzer: lowHi lowVe bye DAD :) lowHi lowVe bye DAD :)
samtheprogram: 100 starts
lefg7: Nice stream
FargioFarmani: gg
tacorising3: LUL
supplydemand88: save the stream bro
abstractingagent: <3
myaocat: NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER
dontbeameme: ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️
serhejenos: never give up
eaterenrgy: GG
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3 @georgehotz <3
KingKewpa: so wat did he hack with that, the pentagon?
joehartshorn: that was mad
myaocat: NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER @NEVER GIVE UP NEVER SURRENDER @georgehotz